<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 06:35:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Testing — 13th November 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm still doing ZOE tests.  Monday was the roughest day, involving eating 5 specially crafted muffins.  What's wrong with muffins?  They were fine, but I felt very strange the entire day.  There was a blood-test too.  It…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/32353f5b-c6a6-4983-85ad-4ebce675693e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/32353f5b-c6a6-4983-85ad-4ebce675693e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 20:57:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&apos;m still doing &lt;a href=&quot;https://joinzoe.com/&quot;&gt;ZOE&lt;/a&gt; tests.  Monday was the roughest day, involving eating 5 specially crafted &lt;a href=&quot;https://joinzoe.com/post/muffin-metabolism-predict&quot;&gt;muffins&lt;/a&gt;.  What&apos;s wrong with muffins?  They were fine, but I felt &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; strange the entire day.  There was a blood-test too.  It didn&apos;t help.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The rest of the week I&apos;ve been doing their blood-sugar challenges, meaning eating specific foods at specific times and watching the impact on a glucose monitor.  Today that was a breakfast of plain white rice with almond butter.  Was it a weird food combination? Yes.  Was it delicious?  &lt;em&gt;Oh my god&lt;/em&gt; yes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I messed up and accidentally deleted my Substack account &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/4a1f26b1-6ac4-4300-9867-1265b5946bdb&quot;&gt;and wrote about it here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wednesday meant Pisco-sours: What an excellent cocktail.  Dinner at &lt;a href=&quot;http://mirafloreslondon.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Miraflores&lt;/a&gt;, anybody?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Friday I went to Brighton for ffconf, both for the first time.  Brighton is great (the fish &amp;amp; chips are actually better) and I now totally get why people keep moving there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ffconf was a real vibe: The talks were all bangers and I took away lots of ideas &amp;amp; frameworks for building a better, more-ethical &amp;amp; &lt;em&gt;more-fun&lt;/em&gt; web.  I spent the entire time catching up with FT colleagues old-and-new (we were probably the biggest group there) and slightly regret not meeting anyone new.  But…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/32353f5b-c6a6-4983-85ad-4ebce675693e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How I recovered my newsletter subscriptions]]></title><description><![CDATA[How many Substack accounts do you have?  Or rather, how many email addresses do you have?  This is the story of how collecting a few of both surprised me, how I recovered and how you can too. Disclaimer: Substack is not…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/4a1f26b1-6ac4-4300-9867-1265b5946bdb?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/4a1f26b1-6ac4-4300-9867-1265b5946bdb</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 18:33:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;p&gt;How many Substack accounts do you have?  Or rather, how many email addresses do you have?  This is the story of how collecting a few of both surprised me, how I recovered and how you can too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: Substack is not at fault here, this was entirely my own doing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
Summary
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Substack implements &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ietf.org/rfc/rfc2919.txt&quot;&gt;RFC-2919&lt;/a&gt; allowing us to programmatically get every list we&apos;ve ever been subscribed to as &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;List-Id&lt;/code&gt; in any mail client.  Standards are &lt;em&gt;fantastic&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With Gmail&apos;s search or API, we can retrieve emails from Substack using &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;from:substack.com&lt;/code&gt;.  And, to filter by payment receipts: &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;subject:&quot;your payment receipt&quot; from:substack.com&lt;/code&gt;.  Using Google Apps Script we can programmatically aggregate these messages into a handy list, &lt;a href=&quot;https://script.google.com/d/1SbHnmBnbn_MJohHDoV0DIGNpa4PDTIiidBBg0BQIY8Jn9MhnPK7GRC0X/edit&quot;&gt;like this&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Newsletters being emails made it easy to retrieve this information, but, by backing this data up sooner I could have avoided the trouble altogether.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
How I messed up
&lt;p&gt;Over the years I&apos;ve used a few different email addresses.  With newsletters growing in popularity and so many being sent via Substack, that &lt;em&gt;also&lt;/em&gt; meant I&apos;d collected several Substack accounts.  Thankfully &lt;a href=&quot;https://support.substack.com/hc/en-us/articles/360037489072-How-do-I-change-my-email-address-&quot;&gt;it&apos;s easy to merge these accounts&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/4a1f26b1-6ac4-4300-9867-1265b5946bdb?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Oscillating — 6th November 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[November is here and the weather has taken a turn. Pumpkin spice lattes are over. This weekend I’ve been reading web standards in the rain. Highlights at work this week included several away-days. We opened one with a…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c4d13db3-73ca-4a6d-95fd-90f358429aad?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c4d13db3-73ca-4a6d-95fd-90f358429aad</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 19:53:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;November is here and the weather has taken a turn. Pumpkin spice lattes are over. This weekend I’ve been reading &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.w3.org/TR/?status=REC&amp;amp;version=latest&quot;&gt;web standards&lt;/a&gt; in the rain.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highlights at work this week included several away-days. We opened one with a vulnerability exercise: Bringing in deeply-meaningful personal items and telling their (really our) stories. We closed the day reflecting using &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.praxisframework.org/en/library/lencioni&quot;&gt;Lencioni’s model&lt;/a&gt; and all cited the opening exercise as having been a big boost.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consecutive away-days compressed the time available for other work. The rapid oscillation between the safety of away-day conversations &amp;amp; now-pressured (already difficult) day-job activities made this week one of the most confusing all year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Although maybe &lt;em&gt;that’s&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://joinzoe.com/&quot;&gt;ZOE&lt;/a&gt; talking: I started the trial this week meaning sticking a glucose monitor into my arm, eating controlled foods and taking various samples. My mood is definitely a bit weird. We won’t talk about Day 2. Genuinely excited to see the results, although they’re probably a next year thing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c4d13db3-73ca-4a6d-95fd-90f358429aad?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Spooking — 30th October 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reader, I ventured back into the world this week after recovering from - something - I caught returning from Bulgaria. Turns out that travel can be dangerous after-all. After not running much during the trip and then…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/feba9390-1e9d-41ce-98e4-8d4bcc9e6fba?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/feba9390-1e9d-41ce-98e4-8d4bcc9e6fba</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 22:37:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reader, I ventured back into the world this week after recovering from - &lt;em&gt;something&lt;/em&gt; - I caught returning from Bulgaria. Turns out that travel can be dangerous after-all.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After not running much during the trip and then staying mostly indoors for a week, I ran &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.strava.com/activities/8042925740&quot;&gt;once&lt;/a&gt; this week and it was a real struggle. Lesson learned: stick to the habit - &lt;em&gt;even while travelling&lt;/em&gt;. The upshot is that all my health stats are still tracking up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At work I spent a lot of time on recruitment-shaped activities for a few roles. On top of going through - &lt;em&gt;a lot&lt;/em&gt; - of CVs, I designed a new interview process for a specialised role, leaning heavily on behavioural questions (with a few discussion-based technical questions) and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annashipman.co.uk/jfdi/interviewing-fairly.html&quot;&gt;this GDS-inspired technique&lt;/a&gt; and so far it’s performing quite well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the evenings I’ve split my time between writing, coursework and drinking. Hoping to publish a few blog posts over the course of the rest of the year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This term I’m using three languages as part of my course - Python &amp;amp; JavaScript, which I’m comfortable with, and C++17 which is mostly new to me. Learning a new language, even formally (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/36708350-beginning-c-17&quot;&gt;with this textbook&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/feba9390-1e9d-41ce-98e4-8d4bcc9e6fba?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Reuniting — 16th October 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Writing this from Sofia Airport, after a pretty intense working week. Lots of time catching up with colleagues new and old. I’m pretty wiped. Against the background symphony of assorted sniffles & coughs in both airports…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/b9027aac-00a6-4c48-a68c-a83f4f6f765f?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/b9027aac-00a6-4c48-a68c-a83f4f6f765f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 11:37:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing this from Sofia Airport, after a pretty intense working week. Lots of time catching up with colleagues new and old. I’m pretty wiped.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Against the background symphony of assorted sniffles &amp;amp; coughs in both airports, there’ve been hardly any masks in sight. Travelling feels like a real adventure right now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My main objective this week was to talk about my team’s upcoming work for 2023. We started the process remotely by sharing some docs, but discussing in-person meant we could discuss finer points (and some creative ideas) over coffees and ad-hoc walk-ups, so by the end of the week we were fully aligned. Refreshing after previous planning cycles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Over many technical conversations, one major theme was about how to scale our enablement functions across multiple teams. Today we all repeat some of our work, e.g. Continuous Integration. More interestingly, the topic of doing native app enablement in the future came up, which is very different to anything I’ve ever done before and is…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/b9027aac-00a6-4c48-a68c-a83f4f6f765f?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Sunrising — 9th October 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[There's something quite magical about watching the sunrise from an airport lounge.  It brings a kind-of existential clarity to your priorities and your life.  The (usually) sleepless night before really helps in setting…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/8e4c8a4b-0f13-4665-9e22-e08ac1657b15?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/8e4c8a4b-0f13-4665-9e22-e08ac1657b15</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 05:59:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There&apos;s something quite magical about watching the sunrise from an airport lounge.  It brings a kind-of existential clarity to your priorities and your life.  The (usually) sleepless night before really helps in setting the mood to answer such difficult questions as “What am I even doing with my life?”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It was beautiful though.  Wish you could have seen it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week was largely spent in spreadsheets, changing (&lt;em&gt;occasionally&lt;/em&gt; moving) cells.  And then speaking to people about the changes.  I also spent some time doing some targeted deep-dives into our tech-stack, to look at personalisation and caching logic.  A pull-request may have been produced, and subsequently rejected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;M﻿y new vice this week is sudoku.  I reinstalled &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.playgoodsudoku.com/&quot;&gt;Good Sudoku&lt;/a&gt; while watching the final season of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt7016936/&quot;&gt;Killing Eve&lt;/a&gt;, and then a day later caught myself doing one during a slightly more talk-y meeting.  According to screentime I have over 24 hours in-game.  &lt;em&gt;Yikes&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;R﻿eally disappointed at where Killing Eve went BTW.  Not sure…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/8e4c8a4b-0f13-4665-9e22-e08ac1657b15?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Anecdotalizing — 2nd October 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Working for a newspaper, it's impossible not to feel connected to the news.  But with Skandal! on everybody's lips this week, that connection feels more real than ever.  In many ways it's exciting being on the periphery…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/2f9fe94e-668a-4ce7-bbc7-592ab21db0f1?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/2f9fe94e-668a-4ce7-bbc7-592ab21db0f1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 11:49:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working for a newspaper, it&apos;s impossible not to feel connected to the news.  But &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt21836620/&quot;&gt;with Skandal!&lt;/a&gt; on everybody&apos;s lips this week, that connection feels more real than ever.  In many ways it&apos;s exciting being on the periphery of this kind of work, holding so many to account.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generally excited right now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The UK economy, huh?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We had two fairly major (but brief) outages on the website this week.  One was caused by a recent breaking change within NodeJS and the other by an experimental feature-flag, both which slipped within our error boundaries.  On top of the excellent cooperation between teams, what was very exciting to see is how our &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/ft-product-technology/next-chapter-on-our-journey-to-achieve-and-maintain-operational-excellence-of-ft-com-7dd9c7871347&quot;&gt;recent focus on reliability&lt;/a&gt; allowed us to learn from both.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two more pumpkin-spices in btw.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For a few years, what has stopped me from getting a &lt;a href=&quot;https://remarkable.com/&quot;&gt;Remarkable&lt;/a&gt; is the lack of backlight and lack of Kindle support.  On Thursday everything changed with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aboutamazon.com/news/devices/amazon-announcing-kindle-scribe&quot;&gt;the Kindle Scribe announcement&lt;/a&gt;.  I&apos;m genuinely excited about this device: It&apos;s the e-ink tablet which genuinely does…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2f9fe94e-668a-4ce7-bbc7-592ab21db0f1?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Pumpkin Spice — 25th September 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reader, Autumn is here, marking the much-anticipated return of pumpkin spice.  While writing I'm drinking my first (and maybe last) latte and can already feel the power of being so, so basic surging through my veins. At…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/d60799c7-a664-4f25-974c-c36f17880854?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/d60799c7-a664-4f25-974c-c36f17880854</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 14:14:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reader, Autumn is here, marking the much-anticipated return of pumpkin spice.  While writing I&apos;m drinking my first (and maybe last) latte and can already feel the power of being so, so basic surging through my veins.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At work, more and more teams have begun blogging semi-regularly.  It&apos;s very energising reading about their progress (and I &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; the occasional deep-dives).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I upgraded to the iPhone 14 Pro, going for the smaller model after I found the 11 Pro Max a shade too big.  So far I&apos;m really enjoying it.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/08/iphone-14-pro-dynamic-island/&quot;&gt;Dynamic Island&lt;/a&gt; is a joy.   Unfortunately I have one gripe: The always-on screen is &lt;strong&gt;really&lt;/strong&gt; distracting, so, I&apos;ve started laying it upside down.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recently I finished watching &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt12851524/&quot;&gt;Only Murders in the Building&lt;/a&gt;.  Overwhelmingly wholesome.  Really just a treat from end-to-end.  Imagine being &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; into true-crime podcasts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A new term starts in a few weeks.  I&apos;m not ready.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week also &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-62920969&quot;&gt;marked a mini-budget in the UK&lt;/a&gt;, doubling-down on &quot;trickle-down&quot; economics.  Mostly I&apos;ve avoided writing…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/d60799c7-a664-4f25-974c-c36f17880854?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Lying — 18th September 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[It’s hard to say how long it’s been now. We lost the South Bank of the Thames to The Queue on Wednesday. Thursday we had The Queue contained to Southwark Park.  Sleep came easy that night. But somewhere along the way we…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/0d17eff9-a290-4381-8c22-feb75babeb3e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/0d17eff9-a290-4381-8c22-feb75babeb3e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 14:15:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s hard to say how long it’s been now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We lost the South Bank of the Thames to The Queue on Wednesday.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thursday we had The Queue contained to Southwark Park.  Sleep came easy that night.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But somewhere along the way we got cocky - containment failed.  The breach rapidly expanded north.  Green Park, St James&apos;s Park &amp;amp; Hyde Park Corner have all fallen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We think some famous footballer (from the 2000s) was involved in the containment breach: Anything for a knighthood.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Queue was five miles long before we lost the ability to measure it.  Our equipment doesn&apos;t work anymore.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s like 2020 all over again: Next week, we’re closing the shops, the schools and the encouraging people not to work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The republicans warned us.  We should have listened.  It may now be too late.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/0d17eff9-a290-4381-8c22-feb75babeb3e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Accessioning — 11th September 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[A lot has happened in the UK this week - we have a new prime minister, a new king - and - the queen passed away during the week.  The new people are where the title is from btw. Wishing I were on holiday. Still running…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c950ebe9-d857-4c5f-817a-8bc33aa9ac75?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c950ebe9-d857-4c5f-817a-8bc33aa9ac75</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 13:29:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A lot has happened in the UK this week - we have a new prime minister, a new king - and - the queen passed away during the week.  The new people are where the title is from btw.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wishing I were on holiday.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Still running!  Now with new shoes which I can’t decide if they’re too small or not.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I took off Wednesday afternoon for an exam which I estimated would take between 6 and 8 hours, but I finished in ~4.  So I went to a birthday party which with hindsight was a mistake.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Thursday I left the office at 6:15PM to join some people at a nearby pub, and around 6:30PM was back in the office in an incident room as we made tweaks to messaging on the site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An interesting thing about working at a newspaper is that we sort-of knew the news was coming. What confirmed it for me - wasn&apos;t the request we pause push-notifications, nor the rumours of notes being passed around the House of Commons. It was the building staff standing by to move our flags to half-mast.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crikey.  Editing the website isn’t…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c950ebe9-d857-4c5f-817a-8bc33aa9ac75?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>