<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:14:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Candle — Week 17, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[When leaving the UK, I got a lot of advice. One bit stood out above the rest. “Find somewhere to live which reminds you that you’re in Japan”.  This week I moved into that place.  It’s within spitting distance of a…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/5432df00-8120-44ea-8b7d-b4de3ff5174c?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/5432df00-8120-44ea-8b7d-b4de3ff5174c</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 11:58:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When leaving the UK, I got a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt; of advice. One bit stood out above the rest. “Find somewhere to live which reminds you that you’re in Japan”.  This week I moved into that place.  It’s within spitting distance of a centroid and from my window I can &lt;em&gt;just about&lt;/em&gt; see the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/NTT_Docomo_Yoyogi_Building&quot;&gt;NTT Docomo Yoyogi building&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There was some work stuff too this week, but I’ll spare you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The actual move was very, very easy.  Faster than last time.    The hard part was actually cleaning my last apartment (by my count, making it the third time this year!).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&apos;ll miss living in Azabu though.  It made me nostalgic for my flat in Sofia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only trouble with moving in for the first time, during peak moving season, is that I own no furniture.  Zip.  Nothing.  Nada.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So anyway, I’m temporarily sleeping on AB’s old futon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bought some essentials: Blinds, towels, kettle and a hair dryer which looks &amp;amp; sounds like a Dyson Supersonic but definitely isn’t.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some reprieve at a Sushiro dinner (which was considerably more reasonably priced…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/5432df00-8120-44ea-8b7d-b4de3ff5174c?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Eggs — Week 16, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This was a cyclical week. Went to Microsoft HQ for hands-on training with Azure AI services. There I built a tool for getting answers from a large collection of technical documentation.  It comprised a processing…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/67faf168-26d5-4f38-8aa1-df86622e0f06?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/67faf168-26d5-4f38-8aa1-df86622e0f06</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:18:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This was a cyclical week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went to Microsoft HQ for hands-on training with Azure AI services. There I built a tool for getting answers from a large collection of technical documentation.  It comprised a processing pipeline and an agent, and because I have trust issues, I extended it to issue citations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This actually blew my mind.  A few years and a few teams ago, I worked on a similar problem so I’m familiar with the NLP problem space: Long months of experimentation were reduced to a few keystrokes and clicks over an afternoon.  The commodification of tooling right now is impressive, and I walked out shocked.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shipped the largest codebase change I’ve made recently affecting 364 files, which required a few weeks of lead-in and planning.  OMG I&apos;m so relieved it’s over.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went for dinner with some folks working data where we talked news and I tried my very very best to sell the UK and London as places to &lt;em&gt;at least&lt;/em&gt; visit.  Unfortunately &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Birmingham_bin_strike&quot;&gt;recent headlines about Birmingham&lt;/a&gt; made it impossible to sell going there.  C’mon people, how else are we getting people to visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.purecraftbars.com/&quot;&gt;PureCraft&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/67faf168-26d5-4f38-8aa1-df86622e0f06?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Flowering — Week 13, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cherry blossom season is upon us, and it’s gorgeous.  The parks are chokka.  Unfortunately the same cannot be said of the weather: It has been cold, and dark, and damp, and miserable all week. Between the weather and…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/d12df8f8-cc9d-4463-a51b-fc44dad1e16e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/d12df8f8-cc9d-4463-a51b-fc44dad1e16e</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 12:51:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cherry blossom season is upon us, and it’s gorgeous.  The parks are chokka.  Unfortunately the same cannot be said of the weather: It has been cold, and dark, and damp, and miserable all week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Between the weather and immediately jumping back into work, even though it was a few days, I was suffering a proper holiday hangover this week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Many years ago I read &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/44919&quot;&gt;“Working Effectively with Legacy Code”&lt;/a&gt;, and it excited me to work with gnarly codebases.  Well, let’s just say I burned a lot of that excitement this week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After missing 3 lessons in a row, Japanese class was &lt;em&gt;incredibly&lt;/em&gt; rough.  We made it, in the end, but wow there were moments where I doubted myself.  Who’d have guessed that learning a language is hard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very thought provoking catch-up on Wednesday evening. 😅&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had a university final during the week.  It caught me by surprise, but luckily it was in an area I know well.  Finished with hours to spare.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Omiyage of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sweetheart_cake&quot;&gt;sweetheart cake&lt;/a&gt; (老婆餅) was very well received.  I had a spare which I stuck…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/d12df8f8-cc9d-4463-a51b-fc44dad1e16e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Sharp Sandspit — Week 12, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[If last week marked my first serious travel since the big move, this week marked my proper first holiday - and with it, more travel.  Thursday was a bank holiday and together with Friday made for an extended “long…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/b2f53898-7914-40dc-b0a9-40f75e49b09a?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/b2f53898-7914-40dc-b0a9-40f75e49b09a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 12:43:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If last week marked my first serious travel since the big move, this week marked my proper first holiday - and with it, more travel.  Thursday was a bank holiday and together with Friday made for an extended “long weekend”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maximum height: 332.6m&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kowloon Dairy products consumed: 7&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After work on Tuesday evening I went to the top of Landmark 81 - the tallest building in Vietnam, the 2nd tallest in SEA and the 17th tallest in the world. It is also, by at least 100 meters, the highest I have ever been.  Reaching the top, they strapped me to a pole and let me walk right up to the edge, where I took a few precarious photos and a selfie, right before scurrying right back down to ground level.  Gorgeous view though, well worth the nerves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wrestled with some NodeJS meta-programming which I really didn&apos;t enjoy. Sometimes I think we had it good with n-gage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And on Wednesday, REDACTED.  All I’m saying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Thursday I packed up, picked up some laundry, had some emergency banh mi, and swatted away the biggest cockroach you ever did see, before collapsing into an airplane seat.  Onboard I watched &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt8368368&quot;&gt;The Apprentice (2024)&lt;/a&gt;, which I really rate, it’s a very good movie.  Solid 3/5.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/b2f53898-7914-40dc-b0a9-40f75e49b09a?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Thanh — Week 11, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week was spent in Ho Chi Minh City 🇻🇳 for both a business trip, and my first trip outside of Tokyo since the big move. This week in data: 🌞 Average temperature: 31°C 🌫️ Average humidity 67.36% 🤢 Cockroaches…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c7240558-389b-4c05-ae04-09839bf081ca?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c7240558-389b-4c05-ae04-09839bf081ca</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week was spent in Ho Chi Minh City 🇻🇳 for both a business trip, and my first trip outside of Tokyo since the big move.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🌞 Average temperature: 31°C&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🌫️ Average humidity 67.36%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🤢 Cockroaches spotted: 34&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monday begins mega early in Narita and possibly the slowest airport check in I’ve ever done.  Nearly an hour.  Thankfully the rest of the journey to the gate was speedy, but, reader, I’d be lying if I didn’t say that this felt mega dicey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Immediately on landing I’m struck by the heat.  It’s hot.  It’s so hot that every minute feels like five.  By the time we get to a taxi my brain has nearly adjusted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our first meal is Phở at a local place, and it ends up being one of the tastiest meals of the week as well as due to my choice of toppings probably the least healthy.  We get oodles of free vegetables which - coming from Tokyo - is amazing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bikes.  Bikes everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With many of us colocated in the same space for the first time in a while, we ran through lots of workshops ranging from talking about our backgrounds to experiencing what it’s like for users to use one of our products.  Great energy all around and I enjoyed the time with people I don’t normally work with.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c7240558-389b-4c05-ae04-09839bf081ca?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Searching — Week 10, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello from Narita.  I took three trains and a bus to get here — normally it’s only one train — so, not in a great mood.  Hopefully tomorrow’s breakfast will make the journey worth it! With next week being my first real…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/0297a9c9-c802-45c1-99a9-8b09fd099349?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/0297a9c9-c802-45c1-99a9-8b09fd099349</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 15:07:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hello from Narita.  I took three trains and a bus to get here — normally it’s only one train — so, not in a great mood.  Hopefully tomorrow’s breakfast will make the journey worth it!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With next week being my first real travel since moving to Japan, this week was all about working through a shopping list and a todo list of preparation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It snowed on Tuesday!  Proper snow!  In March!  I don’t even own snow boots anymore!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepping a workshop for next week really didn’t take long.  Finding the right brand of insect spray, surprisingly, did.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For lack of having the ingredients, to celebrate Pancake Day I bought some premade pancakes, some honey and some sour cream.  It wasn’t until too late in the process that I realised I’d made glorified doriyaki, reader, but damn were they good.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Still running!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is it me or is there a secret second last train which doesn’t appear on the train timetable, immediately after the last train?  It’s either that or I believed a bunch of ghosts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The phrase “cost…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/0297a9c9-c802-45c1-99a9-8b09fd099349?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Deepening — Week 09, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This was the week when I tried every single commodity LLM, and a few other things we’re labelling “AI”.  And let me tell you, oh boy have my opinions on AI flip-flopped like the integrity of a career politician. More on…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/884e3748-4fa8-4d6d-a261-684f3ac848fb?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/884e3748-4fa8-4d6d-a261-684f3ac848fb</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 13:12:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was the week when I tried every single commodity LLM, and a few other things we’re labelling “AI”.  And let me tell you, oh boy have my opinions on AI flip-flopped like the integrity of a career politician. More on &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; after the break.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Papers read: 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Distance run: 13.29km&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gigs attended: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To put it mildly, it really hasn’t been a good week from a current affairs perspective. On Thursday I started writing a message to someone and by the time I sent it on Sunday I had to redraft it, twice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This &lt;em&gt;has&lt;/em&gt; been a good week for paperwork on Planet Alex.  I signed the lease for my long-term apartment this week, which was a much more involved process than any other contract signing I’ve ever done, including the ones through [&lt;em&gt;name of a random previous employer&lt;/em&gt;]’s procurement system.  10 sheets of A3 paper.  My &lt;em&gt;wonderful&lt;/em&gt; agent even had a pen and a bottle of water ready for my troubles.  If anyone is looking for property in Tokyo, I will definitely connect you, please ask.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/884e3748-4fa8-4d6d-a261-684f3ac848fb?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Boxes — Week 8, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Headline this week is that I moved at the weekend.  Goodbye Shibaura and hello Azabu.  It’s a considerably different experience: Some streets round here don't feel like Tokyo.  And amongst other things, I traded a work…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/b0430239-285c-4f63-b620-731c634aaa08?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/b0430239-285c-4f63-b620-731c634aaa08</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 14:07:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Headline this week is that I moved at the weekend.  Goodbye Shibaura and hello Azabu.  It’s a considerably different experience: Some streets round here don&apos;t feel like Tokyo.  And amongst other things, I traded a work desk for a dining table.  I haven’t had a dining table since August 2021.  Now my breakfasts feel somehow dignified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Papers read: 0&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Distance run: 10.82km&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gigs attended: 0&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Class is going well.  We formally began the Kanji.  At some point I have learned to handwrite most of the katakana and hiragana.  And at Tuesday lunchtime I managed to order in a non-English-speaking restaurant without any aids, and it didn’t &lt;em&gt;seem&lt;/em&gt; very awkward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second month in a row that I’m deep-cleaning a flat.  This one was a bit easier at least: Three months is a lot less than four years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MA helped me move by renting a van and helping me shift 3 bags, 2 suitcases and 1 box all in one go.  This was by far the easiest inter-city move I’ve ever done — the hard part was sourcing the bags — and I hope the next one goes just as smoothly.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/b0430239-285c-4f63-b620-731c634aaa08?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Settling — Week 7, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This was a pretty good week.  I had a moment where I thought back to a question someone asked me, and I realised, that I couldn’t fault a single day this week.  Considering the number of big changes that have happened in…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/dbadbdda-2f45-4088-ab21-82f809d87b50?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/dbadbdda-2f45-4088-ab21-82f809d87b50</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 13:05:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a pretty good week.  I had a moment where I thought back to a question someone asked me, and I realised, that I couldn’t fault a single day this week.  Considering the number of big changes that have happened in the past 12 weeks alone, that&apos;s pretty huge.  This felt good in a calm way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🚶 Distance walked: 115,895 steps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🧉 Jasmine tea drunk: 3 litres&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To solve an incredibly annoying migration problem in a repeatable way, I wrote some code which parses the ES AST to extract its exports.  And, it, worked?  Normally I don’t do something so low-level and cursed until &lt;em&gt;at least&lt;/em&gt; summer?  So I’m pretty chuffed with that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Had two stand-out work lunches, only one of which was probably unhealthy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Got accepted for the apartment I applied for, which is &lt;em&gt;wonderful&lt;/em&gt; news, but the move-in date is a little ways off.  So during the week I signed another short-term lease, this one for a flat in Minami-Azabu.  It’s not the most convenient for going to other parts of Tokyo, but it’s an extremely nice area I’ve always enjoyed passing through, and being just on the cusp of walkable to work, I’ll probably never again have the opportunity to stay there.  I’m mega excited to explore a new neighbourhood.  Move-in next weekend.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/dbadbdda-2f45-4088-ab21-82f809d87b50?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Emdashing — Week 6, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Class update: Katakana are happening and they’re happening fast.  I’m staying (mostly) on top of vocab, at least. Learning katakana is making grocery shopping significantly easier, mind.  I finally found oatmeal, and in…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/b91a5f27-b922-428d-9cb2-58daa9d17911?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/b91a5f27-b922-428d-9cb2-58daa9d17911</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 13:18:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Class update: Katakana are happening and they’re happening fast.  I’m staying (mostly) on top of vocab, at least.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learning katakana &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; making grocery shopping significantly easier, mind.  I finally found oatmeal, and in case the picture wasn’t enough, I know enough letters to now know that it says “OATMEAL”.  So that’s neat.  Lessons are already paying for themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🍣 Sushi consumed: 21 pieces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🥣 Oatmeal consumed: 270g&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of my periodic LinkedIn doomscrolling (to reach &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/games&quot;&gt;their daily puzzle games&lt;/a&gt; I must open the feed) I read an incredibly bad take that using emdashes is a tell-tale sign of the use of artificial intelligence in writing, because obviously nobody uses emdashes.  I remember being taught to use them in school, but, unfortunately, I do not remember &lt;em&gt;how&lt;/em&gt;.  Nonetheless I continue to use them.  I hope the inaccuracies are proof enough that, at least for now, my posts are still hand-cranked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Part of joining a new job is learning how the goal-setting and evaluation systems work, and I’ve just about crossed that threshold this week by setting my half-yearly objectives.  I’m quite happy with the approach, and the output.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/b91a5f27-b922-428d-9cb2-58daa9d17911?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>