<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 06:07:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Migrating to the Next.js App Router (or: how I learned to stop worrying and love Server Actions)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi, I’m Alex Wilson and I’m a Staff Engineer in the Business Platform Development Division of Money Forward.  Welcome to day 5 of our 2025 advent calendar. In 2025, we overhauled one of our customer-facing products to…]]></description><link>https://global.moneyforward-dev.jp/2025/12/04/migrating-to-the-next-js-app-router-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-server-actions/?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://global.moneyforward-dev.jp/2025/12/04/migrating-to-the-next-js-app-router-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-server-actions/</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:30:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;p&gt;Hi, I’m &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech&quot;&gt;Alex Wilson&lt;/a&gt; and I’m a Staff Engineer in the Business Platform Development Division of Money Forward.  Welcome to day 5 of our &lt;a href=&quot;https://adventar.org/calendars/11946&quot;&gt;2025 advent calendar&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2025, we overhauled one of our customer-facing products to make it faster, more secure and more reliable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We achieved this by consolidating business logic to run on the server, server-rendering with React Server Components, and unlocking both of these things by migrating to the Next.js App Router.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this post I want to talk about how we did this, and about the challenges we faced along the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Chapter 1. The Challenge&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We build many web applications with Next.js, which is a framework for building full-stack React applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Next.js and its routers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before Next.js version 13, its primary architecture was called the Pages Router, which would detect React Components in a &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;src/pages&lt;/code&gt; directory, allow them to do some data-fetching and then compile these into the actual pages/views shown to users.  For most applications, this means that the…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://global.moneyforward-dev.jp/2025/12/04/migrating-to-the-next-js-app-router-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-server-actions/?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Not Assembling — Week 49, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[It’s December, I now have a Christmas tree and it’s freezing. Consequences of a week about furniture?  This week I spent a lot of time at home waiting for deliveries, assembling furniture and preparing recycling…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/ecf648ef-8334-4d3d-b59f-14b8f66abac9?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/ecf648ef-8334-4d3d-b59f-14b8f66abac9</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 14:39:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s December, I now have a Christmas tree and it’s freezing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consequences of a week about furniture?  This week I spent a lot of time at home waiting for deliveries, assembling furniture and preparing recycling materials from all the packaging.  More of it was that last one than I’m proud to admit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New monitor &amp;amp; desk means I can now work from home.  Actually, this time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week I founded a new team which will be accountable for technical architecture.  On top of wrap-up activities for my previous area, I did requirement-gathering with my new stakeholders and I began developing a 3-pillar strategy.  Next step is writing a charter and drafting objectives - exciting stuff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Naturally I’m re-reading “&lt;a href=&quot;https://gilest.org/books/ach.html&quot;&gt;The Agile Comms Handbook&lt;/a&gt;” one of the most useful business books of all time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went to the taco placed that must not be named.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Friday there was a major Cloudflare incident. You’ve probably heard about it.  This blog was unaffected, I’m not sure why.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wrote a 3000-word blog post this week…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ecf648ef-8334-4d3d-b59f-14b8f66abac9?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Shaka Brah — Week 48, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Well reader, how do you follow Nagoya?  The answer, apparently, is by buying more furniture. I now use Kagi.  Unlike many other products I use, it Just Works™ and honestly I love it.  It has restored my faith in the web…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/650e9d98-b00a-4d1f-a8be-df156ea025b2?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/650e9d98-b00a-4d1f-a8be-df156ea025b2</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 13:11:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well reader, how do you follow Nagoya?  The answer, apparently, is by buying more furniture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I now use &lt;a href=&quot;https://kagi.com/&quot;&gt;Kagi&lt;/a&gt;.  Unlike many other products I use, it Just Works™ and honestly &lt;em&gt;I love it&lt;/em&gt;.  It has restored my faith in the web, and I find myself using web search again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A year ago I was sitting in an empty apartment, wondering what I’d got myself into.  Today I haven&apos;t yet decided where I’m at, but I do know that this will be a banger yearnotes post.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Major release this week, which was heaps of fun and in-part put my Japanese to the test because it is &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; customer facing.  I think that part went well.  The todo list I assembled is now complete.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Almost immediately after the release I found myself thinking about the weeks leading into the start of this project, and a tactical error I made.  I don&apos;t have many regrets but I do wish I could go back and change things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We visited the Taco factory and gave them a run for their money.  Much garlic shrimp was consumed that night.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What began as a…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/650e9d98-b00a-4d1f-a8be-df156ea025b2?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Packing — Week 47, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week marks a year since I left the FT, and my 51st week in Tokyo. Where is my head at a year after stepping away from journalism?  I still feel an incredible passion for the news and I miss it (and, of course, my…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/8fa394fb-c8f0-494e-8bc9-020d1ad0b63f?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/8fa394fb-c8f0-494e-8bc9-020d1ad0b63f</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week marks &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/198b3ab3-2b8d-4da8-8881-1262d3eb2366&quot;&gt;a year since I left the FT&lt;/a&gt;, and my 51st week in Tokyo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Where is my head at a year after stepping away from journalism?  I still feel an incredible passion for the news and I miss it (and, of course, my beloved former coworkers) &lt;em&gt;every day&lt;/em&gt; but I am also enjoying some distance from the cutting edge of current affairs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’ve now got braces, sort-of, step-one of many, and getting ahead of future issues.  They are &lt;em&gt;slightly&lt;/em&gt; limiting.  Pronouncing “Th” and “F” have become an adventure.  I’m sure you’d find it funny.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did a second batch of Pizza dough, this time with the same flour I previously used, and it went OK.  Still many variables to perfect.  Hydration was off, but the final bake was very good.  Future batches will be much smaller.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BTW there is good Pizza in Tokyo. And sangria, and limoncello. Oh no.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How better to celebrate almost a year in Japan than to finally visit the Japanese equivalent of my hometown of Birmingham?  You may know it as Nagoya.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What took me to Nagoya…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/8fa394fb-c8f0-494e-8bc9-020d1ad0b63f?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Hey Jude — Week 46, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome to my 200th weeknote!  This week felt particularly long, but I don’t have all that much to say. Experimentally I deleted all my social media apps, except for Instagram.  I’d already lowered engagement so this isn…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/48ba913e-2d6e-47b9-8e84-46300804e0d3?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/48ba913e-2d6e-47b9-8e84-46300804e0d3</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 14:40:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Welcome to my 200th weeknote!  This week felt &lt;em&gt;particularly&lt;/em&gt; long, but I don’t have all that much to say.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experimentally I deleted all my social media apps, except for Instagram.  I’d already lowered engagement so this isn’t a huge change, but even scrolling passively was negatively affecting my mood.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First attempt in years at making pizza from scratch went well.  Better return-on-investment than pizzerias I’ve been to here, but between my dough not being &lt;em&gt;quite&lt;/em&gt; right and my oven not getting hot enough, there’s lots of variables to tune ~ which is a fun side-project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Impromptu nominkai on Tuesday was very, very good.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What if Bertha, but good?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of my accounts was locked, and to fix it I had to send many emails and make one phone-call.  The phone-call involved iOS’s new live-translation feature, and I felt ashamed using it because the translation &lt;em&gt;from&lt;/em&gt; English was not very good and didn’t convey any of my feeble attempts at keigo.  Good for emergencies, but I can&apos;t do that again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/48ba913e-2d6e-47b9-8e84-46300804e0d3?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Taco Spice Chips — Week 45, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This has been a delicious and expensive week. Lots of Terraform this week.  I mean lots.  Terraform is one of my favorite things in tech right now because it’s a single, simple declarative language for describing nearly…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/db5ad2be-8419-457c-90ab-ea56bc724531?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/db5ad2be-8419-457c-90ab-ea56bc724531</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This has been a delicious and expensive week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lots of Terraform this week.  I mean &lt;em&gt;lots&lt;/em&gt;.  Terraform is one of my favorite things in tech right now because it’s a single, simple declarative language for describing nearly everything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amazing Thai food for dinner on Monday in Ebisu.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had a few unexpected interesting conversations at work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Taking advantage of a few circumstances from recent weeks, I am going deep on self-improvement and have upgraded my 7-year-old Apple Watch, bought sweat-proof fitness earphones, procured more kitchen equipment - and finally - obtained a dining table. Phew.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skipped papers club to go to a sauna for the first time in months.  My heat tolerance has dipped a lot, but that’s OK, I’ll get back there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We have found the best Tacos in Tokyo.  It is a closely guarded secret so I can’t advertise it, but ask me and I will take you there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In words never uttered by a human before: I had a fun dental appointment. And I’m going in for a much longer session later this…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/db5ad2be-8419-457c-90ab-ea56bc724531?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Stateful — Week 44, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[A new floor opened at work this week, bringing a few cool new things including an automatic coffee machine.  Our office is now twice as big as it was when I joined and I love finding interesting nooks for focus work…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/ae8f6c8f-a97d-402d-b6a7-ce4066989682?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/ae8f6c8f-a97d-402d-b6a7-ce4066989682</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 13:18:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A new floor opened at work this week, bringing a few cool new things including an automatic coffee machine.  Our office is now twice as big as it was when I joined and I love finding interesting nooks for focus work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What can only be described as the helicopter version of a motorcade flew of my office a few times this week.  It was the US state visit.  Strange thinking about it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I re-did the AI agent stuff from the other week, and made it considerably simpler/better.  More extensible, if you will.  Now it outputs a pretty report and I&apos;m delighted with it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;During the week I got some bad news.  It wasn’t unexpected, but it did still hurt.  But it’s in these moments when our real friends reveal themselves, and we christened a wonderful new bolt-hole I scouted (but hadn’t needed) inches away from my favouite photo-spot of Tokyo tower.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had a few extremely-basic-yet-coherent conversations in Japanese which was immensely rewarding.  I can’t have imagined being able to do this a year ago, but…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ae8f6c8f-a97d-402d-b6a7-ce4066989682?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Remember the milk — Week 43, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[We’re in big coat season. The temperature is dropping and suddenly my wardrobe is significantly more stylish. Got approval on my all-time biggest PR, huzzah! Lots of project meetings this week. It’s funny: things feel…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/3c4e07f1-6f3c-490e-be9e-ef4ebc45ff7f?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/3c4e07f1-6f3c-490e-be9e-ef4ebc45ff7f</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 14:40:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We’re in big coat season. The temperature is dropping and suddenly my wardrobe is significantly more stylish.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Got approval on my all-time biggest PR, huzzah!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lots of project meetings this week. It’s funny: things feel slow until suddenly they aren’t, and this always brings me a lot of energy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Japanese class was fun this week. I’m enjoying the speaking practice a lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HUB, Donki and Jose Cuervo are currently doing a day-of-the-dead themed collaboration. One thing led to another and I was given their 1L watermelon cocktail. It was OK. I got a funny photo out of it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had some legendary biryani in Toranomon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Samgyetang is unlike anything I’ve ever eaten. An entire chicken is added to a pot, and moments later it is transformed into something resembling a stew.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learned a lot about credit cards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday’s todo list had three items and I’m pleased to say that I checked off all three, including buying the milk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With the upcoming US state visit, my neighborhood has a noticeably increased police…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/3c4e07f1-6f3c-490e-be9e-ef4ebc45ff7f?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Primordial — Week 42, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[What a week, huh? Monday was a bank holiday.  I wanted to find spicy soup and I’m pleased to say that I found some. Still recovering.  Each day I felt more myself, and each day returned some clarity which I hadn’t…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/e3232bc6-6ac7-401e-a325-ce2cd630a44d?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/e3232bc6-6ac7-401e-a325-ce2cd630a44d</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 14:17:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What a week, huh?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monday was a bank holiday.  I wanted to find spicy soup and I’m pleased to say that I found some.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Still recovering.  Each day I felt more myself, and each day returned some clarity which I hadn’t noticed I lost.  Unfortunately not in time for me to have potentially bungled something.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At work I held a kick-off meeting which went OK, although my facilitation skills feel very rusty.  Gotta re-sharpen them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Built an “AI Agent”. Can honestly say I’ve worked on nothing quite like this before - and the results are good - although integrating it into workflows is proving challenging: Sometimes I miss Bertha.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had my second annual health check this week. It ran smoothly albeit long even if the phlebotomy left me feeling woozy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday the Yotsuya lxds drank orange wine and practiced zen buddhism.  I spelt my name right this time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/p/DPc7v_wiZje/&quot;&gt;“Ephemeral” at Such As&lt;/a&gt; which was a hybrid data-visualisation &amp;amp; art installation.  It charted bloom dates in Japan, and shows how changing…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/e3232bc6-6ac7-401e-a325-ce2cd630a44d?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Shin-can’t-sen or shin-won’t? — Week 41, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi, it’s me, I’ve been properly in the weeds of Google Docs and YAML.  Alas I will continue to primarily exist in these for a little while longer. I really liked this post on using AI to generate image captions by Matt…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/56a25482-5d02-4c96-b848-cc943bd431ed?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/56a25482-5d02-4c96-b848-cc943bd431ed</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 14:55:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hi, it’s me, I’ve been properly in the weeds of Google Docs and YAML.  Alas I will continue to primarily exist in these for a little while longer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I really liked this post on &lt;a href=&quot;https://tk.gg/posts/ai-alt-text&quot;&gt;using AI to generate image captions&lt;/a&gt; by Matt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Now that I’ve got the equipment I cooked at home a lot this week, which meant braving buying ingredients I didn’t 100% understand and re-learning how to cook without the luxury of counter-top space.  Never before have I missed owning a dishwasher as much as I do now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Didn’t do much last week, which is why there’s no week 40.  What began as feeling run-down blossomed into full blown sickness.  By the time I saw my doctor I tested negative for everything, but whatever this was took a serious toll on my energy levels, mood and focus and I’m still recovering bit-by-bit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;That meant staying in and playing &lt;a href=&quot;https://thegamesdb.net/game.php?id=85013&quot;&gt;The Great Ace Attorney&lt;/a&gt; which is cheesy as all hell and goes hard on stereotyping England.  Doubling-down, I watched some &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/name/nm0005363/&quot;&gt;Guy Ritchie&lt;/a&gt; movies: It &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; wasn’t a good week…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/56a25482-5d02-4c96-b848-cc943bd431ed?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>