<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 04:33:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Generating — Week 30, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week marked the FT's first hackday in two years.  The theme was AI and we had just over a day to try and build something interesting.  It was loads of fun! My team of EH, AC, OO, FS and I started out by trying to…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/6dcc00c2-ac66-4569-b76b-e17c3114c264?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/6dcc00c2-ac66-4569-b76b-e17c3114c264</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 20:55:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week marked the FT&apos;s first hackday in two years.  The theme was AI and we had just over a day to try and build something interesting.  It was loads of fun!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My team of EH, AC, OO, FS and I started out by trying to generate video accompaniments to articles - but after realising that the videos were rather long, we pivoted towards video shorts (think: tiktok).  To enable our hack, I wrote a cursed integration between google sheets and our internal LLM.  We managed to create a few videos but it&apos;s nowhere near ready for prime-time: we didn&apos;t win, but we did get a few laughs and a shout-out from the judges!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some teams built some really cool stuff!  Including a novel chat based UI for interacting with the site (one that actually seemed quite fresh) and a Nikkei team built a tool for geolocation for use in investigative journalism.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuesday marked Arjun&apos;s birthday and for lack of rain we went on a mission to infiltrate another drinks: In the end we were invited and so the mission failed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuing the theme of Machine-Learning, I picked &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.credly.com/badges/0bc35463-7478-4b67-88b3-0060d78feee8&quot;&gt;IBM&apos;s AI Engineering certification&lt;/a&gt; back up (having paused it in 2020) and finished the whole thing over the weekend.  Lots of repeated content, but also…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/6dcc00c2-ac66-4569-b76b-e17c3114c264?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Microwaving — Week 29, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Another busy week, week 2 of midterms.  But they're over now, for now. On Monday, in part to celebrate handing in my first two midterm assignments, and in part because I'd already made these plans, I went to see the new…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/5ede8da6-7556-4e74-bd8c-ce5c9de3bbad?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/5ede8da6-7556-4e74-bd8c-ce5c9de3bbad</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 20:38:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Another busy week, week 2 of midterms.  But they&apos;re over now, &lt;em&gt;for now&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Monday, in part to celebrate handing in my first two midterm assignments, and in part because I&apos;d already made these plans, I went to see the new Mission Impossible movie with AD and CR.  It was good!  Lots of build, especially in the run-up to Part 2.  I couldn&apos;t stop noticing that in every shot Tom Cruise managed to make himself look so tall.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spent a lot of time this week talking to people about how to staff an upcoming technical strategy initiative.  And then the rest doing the first of a few interviews with people who worked on similar projects in the past, where I learned loads.  A major theme was finding novel ways to remove the felt constraints of our organisational structure - moving past &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Conway%27s_law&quot;&gt;Conway&apos;s law&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thegadhian.com/posts/rolling-out-cms-pandemic/&quot;&gt;Spark team&lt;/a&gt; ran a hack-week this week, and I joined their presentation on Friday to see some of the results.  All great stuff, but my favourites were an experimental implementation of push-notifications…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/5ede8da6-7556-4e74-bd8c-ce5c9de3bbad?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Hoisting — Week 28, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Busy week. No video-games for Alex this week. Summarised a few months of design-work into a technical-design-doc this week, and circulated it around to get a bunch of feedback.  It speaks to including code in FT articles…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/706b48da-5725-4748-98ae-868b04a208d2?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/706b48da-5725-4748-98ae-868b04a208d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 22:40:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Busy week. No video-games for Alex this week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summarised a few months of design-work into a technical-design-doc this week, and circulated it around to get a bunch of feedback.  It speaks to including code in FT articles, in a similar way to something I&apos;m considering doing on this blog.  Very excited about this work!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Had my first 1:1 with &lt;a href=&quot;https://alicebartlett.co.uk&quot;&gt;Alice&lt;/a&gt; this week which was great. Given that it was one of the first meetings in her new role, it prompted me to write what I&apos;m calling reverse-manager-README: It&apos;s an experimental document inspired by a conversation with &lt;a href=&quot;https://nickramsbottom.com&quot;&gt;Nick&lt;/a&gt; about how bringing context about the quirks of managing you would be nice for managers. I&apos;ve never written a &lt;a href=&quot;https://svnk.github.io/manager-READMEs&quot;&gt;manager-readme&lt;/a&gt; because they seem a bit impersonal, but this exercise has given me second thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Thursday evening I went to a Nikkei dinner with &lt;a href=&quot;https://lukeblaney.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Luke&lt;/a&gt; and JK at a steakhouse where - after talking about how it&apos;s a long-term aspiration - I was floored by someone asking me &quot;What&apos;s your strategy to move to Japan?&quot;.  I hope I handled it well!  For now I am only focusing on language.  We talked a little bit about cyber-attacks and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/49247043-this-is-how-they-tell-me-the-world-ends&quot;&gt;This Is How They Tell Me The World Ends&lt;/a&gt; came up — an absolutely phenomenal read.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/706b48da-5725-4748-98ae-868b04a208d2?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Sidelining — Week 27, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Huh, we're past the Summer Solstice. Tuesday morning I showed up bright and early at the radiology unit for a follow-up scan.  I really wasn't looking forward to the cannula but it was all fine, and the nurses added and…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/ed2283bb-3b96-4405-9325-eec9db20b7f5?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/ed2283bb-3b96-4405-9325-eec9db20b7f5</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 22:07:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Huh, we&apos;re past the Summer Solstice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuesday morning I showed up bright and early at the radiology unit for a follow-up scan.  I really wasn&apos;t looking forward to the cannula but it was all fine, and the nurses added and removed it without leaving any bruising - which is a genuine first for any of the needles stuck in my arm this year.  The contrast dye made me feel nauseous — unfortunately I didn&apos;t pick up any super-powers from the process.  &lt;em&gt;Yet&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work was a blur this week and I somehow picked up extra assignments while trying to mind my own business, but the main highlight was OKR day.  Just over three hours of presentation spread out over an entire day, leaving lots of room for coffees, an impromptu team lunch and a social in the tiny room above Watling Street.  Recharged (or drained?!) my social battery in a good way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday marked Ant day.  Happy Ant day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Picked up &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetfighter.com/6&quot;&gt;Street Fighter 6&lt;/a&gt; this weekend and on top of going through Arcade Mode, I&apos;ve eclipsed the 100 online matches mark.  It&apos;s so goddamn fun, and is making for a nice break from Zelda.  It definitely feels like at least one character is unbalanced so I&apos;m hoping Capcom will continue working at it.  What&apos;s most interesting is an entirely new build-your-own-fighter mode, which comes with a cringey single-player campaign.  Also the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_UKlVx16mx4&quot;&gt;music slaps&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nmv8HwUvc-k&quot;&gt;like seriously&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ed2283bb-3b96-4405-9325-eec9db20b7f5?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Lightroots — Week 26, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Two last days in one week, working absolute wonders for my separation anxiety. I tried blocking off time this week to focus on an area of technical strategy, but with the influx of end-of-q2 and end-of-h1 activities…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/2815bfca-621e-4c87-b237-4e19a87e5a47?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/2815bfca-621e-4c87-b237-4e19a87e5a47</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 20:07:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two last days in one week, working absolute wonders for my separation anxiety.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I tried blocking off time this week to focus on an area of technical strategy, but with the influx of end-of-q2 and end-of-h1 activities couldn&apos;t really make any.  Slightly annoyed at that.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annashipman.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Anna&apos;s&lt;/a&gt; last actual day was on Monday - we went for lunch to Lina Stores which was lovely even if the affogato was bittersweet.  Anna has been a great boss, and with the move to CTO I&apos;m really excited for her.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We gave an update to our Nikkei counterparts about the progress we&apos;ve made in enabling new story formats for the FT, and seeing just how much we&apos;ve achieved in a year is pretty phenomenal.  We also gave a sneak-peak at a new secret article page feature we&apos;re working on which I&apos;m super-excited about and believe will be &lt;em&gt;game-changing&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My entire team went to &lt;a href=&quot;https://leaddev.com/events/leadingeng-london-2023&quot;&gt;LeadingEng&lt;/a&gt; this year which was fantastic, if only because it meant the we could form a meta-clique between the current and former FT people, just like we did last year at &lt;a href=&quot;https://ffconf.org/&quot;&gt;FFconf&lt;/a&gt;.  The talks were great - I&apos;ve got some notes but am not sure if I should do a full write-up since there was so much overlap with last year.  My main takeaway was actually on better ways of…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2815bfca-621e-4c87-b237-4e19a87e5a47?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Spinning — Week 25, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[On Monday I woke in Sofia and went to bed on Tuesday in London.  Still reeling from that change.  Said several hurried "Goodbyes" after lunch, and then after getting a row to myself on the plane, said several-more…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/76280b08-2b55-40c1-ba70-f74c29ec13d1?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/76280b08-2b55-40c1-ba70-f74c29ec13d1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 19:57:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Monday I woke in Sofia and went to bed on Tuesday in London.  Still reeling from that change.  Said several hurried &quot;Goodbyes&quot; after lunch, and then after getting a row to myself on the plane, said several-more hurried &quot;Hellos&quot; in London before dragging some people to see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/jurikohno/&quot;&gt;Juri&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/city-academy-voices-choir-back-in-business-tickets-611005342427&quot;&gt;sing&lt;/a&gt;.  Great concert and friendly band.  Should have skipped the chuhi.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OK now that I&apos;ve padded out the word-count for previews, I shall attempt to bury the lede: I experienced a close loss this weekend and it&apos;s still sinking in.  What&apos;s most painful is not having said goodbye.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of my teams had a team-day this week.  I missed the retrospective because it was in the morning, but got to join in with the session around reviewing the mission and trying to write some team behavioural principles.  We wrapped with &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/umbobabo&quot;&gt;Umberto&lt;/a&gt; hosting a game of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Would_I_Lie_to_You%3F_(game_show)&quot;&gt;Would I Lie To You&lt;/a&gt;, where I successfully(?) managed to convince everybody that I was &lt;em&gt;lying&lt;/em&gt; about bringing a backup sandwich to long drinks and parties.  What did &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; achieve…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/76280b08-2b55-40c1-ba70-f74c29ec13d1?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Pouring — Week 24, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Monday started early with a hectic call with Egencia and finished with me repeating history in 2019 by going straight from lunch at Côte St Pauls to Sofia, via Heathrow.  The Lizzy line made it significantly less…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/2738e9a1-e757-4e68-8ab8-46a7ad450799?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/2738e9a1-e757-4e68-8ab8-46a7ad450799</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 18:00:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monday started early with a hectic call with Egencia and finished with me repeating history in 2019 by going straight from lunch at Côte St Pauls to Sofia, via Heathrow.  The Lizzy line made it significantly less stressful.  But the flight was 2 hours late so all that stress came right back when we landed at 1AM and I couldn&apos;t find a cab.  That bit didn&apos;t happen last time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What brings me to Sofia this week is to work in-person (again) on the product coexistence problem.  We&apos;ve spent a long time examining architecture for the general case of deploying features across teams, and for a product pilot that we&apos;re kicking off next quarter.  The approach we&apos;re taking and evaluating will involve writing contracts, allowing systems to include components from other systems, and so far it seems like a sensible, pragmatic cut-back approach to micro-frontends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Also lots of progress with the exercise to enrich interactive content on FT.com.  We had a small workshop to pitch an OKR, and my group…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2738e9a1-e757-4e68-8ab8-46a7ad450799?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Routing — Week 23, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[It's air-con season again baby. I've been context-switching like crazy between several things on my plate, while trying to make room for some focussed technical strategy work. Went to Nick's house for a BBQ.  Lost at…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/24f7e0cc-1cfb-4d90-b3ad-edb07da883c4?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/24f7e0cc-1cfb-4d90-b3ad-edb07da883c4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 18:00:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&apos;s air-con season again baby.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&apos;ve been context-switching like crazy between several things on my plate, while trying to make room for some focussed technical strategy work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went to &lt;a href=&quot;https://nickramsbottom.com/&quot;&gt;Nick&apos;s&lt;/a&gt; house for a BBQ.  Lost at many board-games that I&apos;ve never played before.  Lovely BBQ though.  Saw a fox trying to climb the wall.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doing the maths late one evening I figured out that I could save a lot of money by buying coffee and alcoholic beverages in-bulk.  So anyway, on Wednesday evening a crate of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pocari_Sweat&quot;&gt;Pocari Sweat&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Boss_Coffee&quot;&gt;Suntory Boss Coffee&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Strong_Zero&quot;&gt;Suntory Strong Zero&lt;/a&gt; arrived.  For a relaxing time, make it Suntory time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stayed late in the office on Friday, and ended up watching &lt;a href=&quot;https://uxrconf23.joinlearners.com/&quot;&gt;UXRCon&lt;/a&gt; with several researchers.  Pretty interesting stuff, I really enjoyed the different perspectives on examining personal and systemic biases in research.  I also really enjoyed most of the sponsor talks where they framed a sales-pitch for a product as a talk, and actually conveyed some pretty good stuff.  Don&apos;t get that at…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/24f7e0cc-1cfb-4d90-b3ad-edb07da883c4?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Standing — Week 22, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[I last left you in a field.  It was a nice field.  I've been thinking about that field a lot. Got into the office quite early one morning for a conversation with the ABC about the technical work I'm doing to improve how…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/9da78967-f8c4-49eb-9597-15757d50c4d7?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/9da78967-f8c4-49eb-9597-15757d50c4d7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 18:00:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I last left you in a field.  It was a nice field.  I&apos;ve been thinking about that field a lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Got into the office quite early one morning for a conversation with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.abc.net.au/&quot;&gt;ABC&lt;/a&gt; about the technical work I&apos;m doing to improve how we build interactives, and learned &lt;em&gt;lots&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of my teams did a design sprint this week, and on Thursday afternoon I was invited to the &quot;jury&quot; to feed back on their ideas - some of which seemed like novel iterations of things we already had, and some of which were just fantastic ideas that really might push how journalists tell stories.  Felt pretty hyped afterwards!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kicked off some technical-strategy work, and spent a lot of time refining documents for senior stakeholders.  I&apos;ve decided my new favourite font for these documents is Work Sans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finally went to one of the Bulgarian restaurants in London - it was &lt;em&gt;fantastic&lt;/em&gt;.  Missed Шкембе чорба a lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Someone bullied &lt;em&gt;politely encouraged&lt;/em&gt; me into doing a bit of work to fix the mailing list on this blog, which I have now done…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/9da78967-f8c4-49eb-9597-15757d50c4d7?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Camping — Week 21, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[The trouble with doing a long hike on Sunday and then immediately walking to work from Waterloo the following day is that you get massive cramp. Writing this to the sound of “Cotten-Eyed Joe” in a field in the middle of…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/d971117e-ff1f-45cc-a976-23d1437da3be?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/d971117e-ff1f-45cc-a976-23d1437da3be</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 22:44:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The trouble with doing a long hike on Sunday and then immediately walking to work from Waterloo the following day is that you get massive cramp.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing this to the sound of “Cotten-Eyed Joe” in a field in the middle of Hertfordshire.  How did we get here?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Career progression in engineering is heavily on my mind this week.  Both the general case, and my own (I think they call this career planning) - and I’ve started writing down some thoughts. It’s hard to write something that includes both a diagnosis of difficulties and some suggestions without it reading a bit like a manifesto but I’m trying.  And also to not make it just about me.  And here we are.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Furthering a reputation I’d rather I not have, I discovered that a cache of discount cards for the sea-creature pub and started distributing them.  Sorry Euan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gee, the first season of this Succession show is pretty good.  Yes I know I&apos;m several years late.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There&apos;s a lot more to write but I don&apos;t want to miss my inconsequential self…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/d971117e-ff1f-45cc-a976-23d1437da3be?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>