<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 13:36:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Accessioning — 11th September 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[A lot has happened in the UK this week - we have a new prime minister, a new king - and of course - the queen passed away during the week.  The new people are where the title is from btw. Still running!  Now with new…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c950ebe9-d857-4c5f-817a-8bc33aa9ac75?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c950ebe9-d857-4c5f-817a-8bc33aa9ac75</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 13:29:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A lot has happened in the UK this week - we have a new prime minister, a new king - and of course - the queen passed away during the week.  The new people are where the title is from btw.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Still running!  Now with new shoes which I can’t decide if they’re too small or not.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I took off Wednesday afternoon for an exam which I estimated would take between 6 and 8 hours, but I finished in ~4.  So I went to a birthday party which with hindsight was a mistake.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Thursday I left the office at 6:15PM to join some people at a nearby pub, and around 6:30PM was back in the office in an incident room as we made tweaks to messaging on the site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crikey.  Editing the website isn’t very stressful compared to rewriting the frontpage of the paper.  A few surprisingly long (18 minutes!) deployments are nothing in comparison.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We had an open tab which was quickly repurposed into dinner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday evening I met some friends at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eattokyo.co.uk/covent-garden&quot;&gt;Spiritland&lt;/a&gt; - you know, the big one near Waterloo - and we migrated from there to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eattokyo.co.uk/covent-garden&quot;&gt;Eat Tokyo&lt;/a&gt;.  Honest review of Spiritland: It’s just okay.  They made a decent Old Fashioned…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c950ebe9-d857-4c5f-817a-8bc33aa9ac75?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Toting — 4th September 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reader, this week I’ve been engaged in battle with my bathroom sink: On the verge of calling in reinforcements (a plumber) I had a mild victory involving a plunger.  Now I know how the Daleks must feel. This was a…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/90ef6cce-d31a-4cac-8f61-98e4b48209c3?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/90ef6cce-d31a-4cac-8f61-98e4b48209c3</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 20:35:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reader, this week I’ve been engaged in battle with my bathroom sink: On the verge of calling in reinforcements (a plumber) I had a mild victory involving a plunger.  Now I know how the Daleks must feel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This was a shorter week at work and it felt pretty hefty at times, but already far better than last week.  Reflecting, something I need to do a lot more of is time-blocking: Some documents just need to be written.  It’s like being in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2022/08/26/15-tech-leaders-on-why-and-how-ctos-should-find-time-to-code/&quot;&gt;critical-path of code&lt;/a&gt;, only, without the code - and usually docs can’t “just” be passed onto someone else.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Wednesday, I went to an impromptu leaving drinks for a conspicuously-anonymous friend moving to NYC the next day.  Our small group merged with another and I left having had one of the top-ten strangest conversations of all time - and with a job offer for a non-existent company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My new mission is to make highballs happen because they’re more refreshing than beer, and make me look cooler than drinking wine.  If you hear me ordering “Whiskey…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/90ef6cce-d31a-4cac-8f61-98e4b48209c3?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Stacking — 28th August 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week I won at Calendar-Tetris, which is to say that I sat in a near-solid block of gatherings from Monday through to Friday. It hasn’t been quite that packed since 2020. New objective: Never let it quite get that…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/0f78ea83-2c98-464c-b6bf-59198e415dbe?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/0f78ea83-2c98-464c-b6bf-59198e415dbe</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 22:18:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week I won at Calendar-Tetris, which is to say that I sat in a near-solid block of gatherings from Monday through to Friday. It hasn’t been quite that packed since 2020. New objective: Never let it quite get that bad again - which probably means starting to do &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.rescuetime.com/time-blocking-101/&quot;&gt;time-blocking&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Wednesday lunchtime I learned something semi-secret which totally broke my brain. And I think I gave a slightly disastrous presso afterwards - although people were awfully nice about it. Spent the evening at one of London’s rare Izakayas eating okonomiyaki: They made a decent highball.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thursday evening involved product chatter and cocktails at a speakeasy - one of the few spaces in the City which isn’t always packed. They made a decent highball.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reading about the community coming out of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L0pht&quot;&gt;early hacker-spaces&lt;/a&gt; or places like &lt;a href=&quot;https://gds.blog.gov.uk/2013/05/01/govuk-in-pictures/&quot;&gt;GDS&lt;/a&gt;, I feel a little sad (&lt;em&gt;and, perhaps a phantom pang of loneliness&lt;/em&gt;) that with more remoteness and less time in second or &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Third_place&quot;&gt;third places&lt;/a&gt;, that for a while there will be fewer of these…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/0f78ea83-2c98-464c-b6bf-59198e415dbe?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Conditioning — 21 August 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reader I have a confession: While I’ve referenced it plenty in the past, it’s only very recently that I started consciously compartmentalising. And it is a very useful tool indeed. On Saturday Sunday Monday Tuesday my…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c4e91546-1955-4145-ad09-e9af4cf9802f?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c4e91546-1955-4145-ad09-e9af4cf9802f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 21:18:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reader I have a confession: While I’ve referenced it plenty in the past, it’s only very recently that I started consciously &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/ryanblair/2012/06/26/5-steps-of-compartmentalization/&quot;&gt;compartmentalising&lt;/a&gt;. And it is a very useful tool indeed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Saturday Sunday Monday &lt;em&gt;Tuesday&lt;/em&gt; my new air conditioner arrived and &lt;em&gt;immediately&lt;/em&gt; brought my apartment below 30°C - and my bedroom below the 25°C - both for the first time in long over a week. Huzzah.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At work on Thursday afternoon we had our first Show &amp;amp; Tell across all of Product &amp;amp; Technology. It’s pretty bananas seeing how much interesting work is going on once it’s all presented in one place.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It fell on the day of a Rail strike, meaning fewer people came in person than had signed up. So after the few of us who were there commandeered the extra bottles of wine &amp;amp; chewed the fat: True influencer moment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Tube &amp;amp; Rail strikes have been inconvenient (I guess that’s the purpose of a strike) but for me amounted to walking a bit more - which is no bad thing. I am now mildly obsessed with buying an electric bike though. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vanmoof.com/en-GB/electric-bikes&quot;&gt;Look it&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c4e91546-1955-4145-ad09-e9af4cf9802f?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Atsuatsu — 14th August]]></title><description><![CDATA[Writing these from my “balcony”. It isn’t big enough for a chair so I’m leaning against a wall and pretending that passing cars can’t see me. It’s been pretty hot in the UK this week, and my newly instrumented apartment…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/42725480-8772-4491-b5cb-172b10e188c5?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/42725480-8772-4491-b5cb-172b10e188c5</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 18:30:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;p&gt;Writing these from my “balcony”. It isn’t big enough for a chair so I’m leaning against a wall and pretending that passing cars can’t see me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s been pretty hot in the UK this week, and my newly instrumented apartment peaked at 34.2°C (or 93.6°F). The root cause is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Heat_dome&quot;&gt;heat dome&lt;/a&gt; which reminds me of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0462538/&quot;&gt;Simpsons Movie&lt;/a&gt;. Not because of the dome - but because I can’t wait for it to be over.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know what really is an excellent movie though? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt11866324/&quot;&gt;Prey&lt;/a&gt;. Best Predator movie yet. And on the theme of media about predatory behaviour, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt10166622&quot;&gt;The Dropout&lt;/a&gt; is a great adaptation of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/37976541-bad-blood&quot;&gt;John Carreyrou’s original book&lt;/a&gt; - although unfortunately it left out &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodreads.com/notes/50253296-bad-blood/90636253-alex-wilson/42f8123f-9a03-4982-b65c-d3a33866b8a0&quot;&gt;my favourite scene&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hi Alex!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regrettably the heat has prevented me from getting much done - there’s reading I can’t concentrate on and coursework I haven’t even started. So I caved and bought an air conditioning unit - which helpfully arrives after the heatwave is over.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oh well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/42725480-8772-4491-b5cb-172b10e188c5?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Instrumenting — 7th August 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week at work felt quite heavy in terms of operational activities - it flew by and I had only really made progress in one discrete area. Some people from Nikkei were in town this week. As the two most established…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/48e0bf88-d974-4db6-9af7-2f07b74d0114?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/48e0bf88-d974-4db6-9af7-2f07b74d0114</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 21:48:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;p&gt;This week at work felt quite heavy in terms of operational activities - it flew by and I had only really made progress in one discrete area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some people from Nikkei were in town this week. As the two most established London teams, Customer Products &amp;amp; Internal Products combined our monthly team-wide showcases to welcome them. I’m glad we did it if only to see how different teams organise &amp;amp; run similar cultural events. And &lt;em&gt;so far&lt;/em&gt; it’s already given rise to at least one inter-departmental table-tennis feud and/or tournament.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As always, hugely impressive seeing the sheer skill of Japanese-English interpreters. Both during the snapshot, and later in an impromptu one-on-one, that is a level of multi-lingual mastery which needs to be seen to be believed. Meanwhile, nearly Wanikani level 3 - huzzah.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alicebartlett.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Alice&lt;/a&gt; started a book club at work, where &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/ft-product-technology/book-club-the-pragmatic-programmer-2886fe053ef&quot;&gt;we read a chapter of the revised Pragmatic Programmer and talk about it weekly&lt;/a&gt;. First week was fun. My favourite note from the conversation was: &lt;em&gt;“Stone frog soup - what???”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;…&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/48e0bf88-d974-4db6-9af7-2f07b74d0114?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Anniversarial — 31st July 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[They say it takes 21 days to form a habit, even if disappointingly it turns out that there’s no such magical number. Still, this post marks a consecutive year since resuming weeknotes and so I’m in a celebratory mood…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/dba70898-ee94-4ec8-b852-926630ce18f8?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/dba70898-ee94-4ec8-b852-926630ce18f8</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 21:27:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;p&gt;They say it takes 21 days to form a habit, even if disappointingly it turns out that &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/ejsp.674&quot;&gt;there’s no such magical number&lt;/a&gt;. Still, this post marks a consecutive year since &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/278059da-8c59-4a6e-8992-1530f9630ab8&quot;&gt;resuming weeknotes&lt;/a&gt; and so I’m in a celebratory mood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One helpful tweak was slightly systemising the process, leading to the format you’re reading now. Sticking to a few themes and expanding on them in bullet-points contains thoughts and avoids editorialising.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the past weeknotes were about forming a writing habit - so in the past I wrote about tech, sometimes at a stretch. But this past year they’ve been a chance to write about things going on in my life, and things I find interesting with as little censorship as possible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engagement on Twitter is also way down compared to 2018, which others have pointed out is for mostly algorithmic reasons and there’s a whole slightly-ranty essay in there. But major kudos to all you RSS folk: I don’t know who you are but - one-time offer - drop me a note and I’ll buy you a coffee.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/dba70898-ee94-4ec8-b852-926630ce18f8?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Sudoriferous — 24th July 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[It’s been rather hot this week and for lack of air conditioning at home, I’ve been eating lots of spicy food – and espresso soft-serve — to survive. Dan Dan Noodles (担担面) are the best things ever: A small amount of spicy…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/f046bb2d-0f3a-46c0-a279-2eef56f50164?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/f046bb2d-0f3a-46c0-a279-2eef56f50164</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 21:13:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;p&gt;It’s been rather hot this week and for lack of air conditioning at home, I’ve been eating lots of spicy food – and espresso soft-serve — to survive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chinesefoodwiki.org/Dan_Dan_Noodles&quot;&gt;Dan Dan Noodles&lt;/a&gt; (担担面) are the best things ever: A small amount of spicy soup and pork which comes out perfect nearly every time. Goes well paired with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thekitchn.com/sichuan-smashed-cucumber-salad-recipe-23173272&quot;&gt;Smashed Cucumber Salad&lt;/a&gt; (凉拌黄瓜) which — served cold and drizzled in Sichuan chilli oil — make the temperature melt away.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cooklikepriya.com/2013/09/varutha-kozhi-masala-spicy-chicken.html&quot;&gt;Kozhi Varutha&lt;/a&gt; is a new discovery — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ashasrestaurant.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Asha’s&lt;/a&gt; serves a similar fish curry which is my go to whenever I’m in Birmingham, and this is even easier to make. Lots of chilli and creamy chicken: Perfect.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://foodandmeal.com/kara-miso-tonkotsu-ramen&quot;&gt;Kara-Miso Ramen&lt;/a&gt; (辛味噌ラーメン) for whatever reason isn’t that well known but is utterly delicious. I think I overdid the ginger and chilli because it came out a much deeper red, but, &lt;em&gt;oh my god&lt;/em&gt; was it good. If you’re ever in Tokyo &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tripadvisor.co.za/Restaurant_Review-g1066443-d1698900-Reviews-Karashibimisoramen_Kikanbo_Kanda-Chiyoda_Tokyo_Tokyo_Prefecture_Kanto.html&quot;&gt;be sure to check out the place I discovered it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the heat however, haven’t got a whole lot done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For fun I’ve been writing small slack bots to automate journal entries and news digests, although maybe I should &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z3xPIYHKSoI&quot;&gt;re-write them in Rust&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt9660182/&quot;&gt;Resident Evil&lt;/a&gt; on Netflix was surprisingly good. Video-game stories don’t tend to work in film (&lt;em&gt;e.g. the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0120804/&quot;&gt;Resident Evil&lt;/a&gt; series of movies&lt;/em&gt;) but this is a great exception. Highly recommended.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have you heard about the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Curse_of_the_ninth&quot;&gt;curse of the ninth&lt;/a&gt;? Wondering if Gabe Newell is worried about a curse of the third in video-games.&lt;/li&gt;…&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/f046bb2d-0f3a-46c0-a279-2eef56f50164?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Acclimatizing — 17th July 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[With record high temperatures in the UK, I regret moving to a place with such good insulation. Winter was wonderful and the heating stayed off, but, now I’m craving the cool touch of air conditioning. Current life-hacks…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/ba074770-eea7-429f-9fe2-36c19df392d7?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/ba074770-eea7-429f-9fe2-36c19df392d7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 22:27:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;p&gt;With record high temperatures in the UK, I regret moving to a place with such good insulation. Winter was wonderful and the heating stayed off, but, now I’m craving the cool touch of air conditioning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Current life-hacks involve shorts and bootleg iced-coffees, which is to say refrigerated milk and whatever form of concentrated caffeine I can find.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What a time to begin reading John Doerr&apos;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://speedandscale.com/&quot;&gt;Speed &amp;amp; Scale&lt;/a&gt;. From an author known for OKRs, it’s a book with case studies and an action plan for tackling climate change. The website includes much of the same information and &lt;a href=&quot;https://speedandscale.com/tracker/&quot;&gt;an interactive tracker for each objective&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Happy to stop eating beef, but it’s slightly disheartening to see that many big objectives are off-target: Perhaps the heat will stop us bickering and supporting populists? One can only hope.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lots happening at work right now, too much to mention:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Tuesday &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@carolinej.is&quot;&gt;Caroline&lt;/a&gt; left our team, and we marked the occasion with our first in-person team lunch which was lovely - until we got kicked-out to make room for a networking event!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/DimityrTerziev&quot;&gt;Dimitar&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; I are both taking on short-term interim tech-director roles which is exciting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s mid-year review season at work, and I think it’s been uplifting for everybody? I’m on-target with most of my objectives and have nice feedback which will help me (slightly) course-correct.&lt;/li&gt;…&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ba074770-eea7-429f-9fe2-36c19df392d7?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Revising — 10th July 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Last week I was preoccupied with SGDQ so didn’t write anything — this week was genuinely exhausting in a nice way. SGDQ was tonnes of fun, and in particular Ocarina of Time: Triforce% is one of the genuinely coolest…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/6f9856e3-eef0-47c1-970b-9dc1dbaa6252?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/6f9856e3-eef0-47c1-970b-9dc1dbaa6252</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 20:55:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;p&gt;Last week I was preoccupied with &lt;a href=&quot;https://gamesdonequick.com/&quot;&gt;SGDQ&lt;/a&gt; so didn’t write anything — this week was genuinely exhausting in a nice way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SGDQ was tonnes of fun, and in particular &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PNbkv_DJ0f0&quot;&gt;Ocarina of Time: Triforce%&lt;/a&gt; is one of the genuinely coolest things I’ve ever seen. Also after contributing for years, for the first time one of my donations got announced out in front of 100k people: It felt &lt;em&gt;weird&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;During the work week, the recently formed API Rationalisation team ran a in-person office-hours where they talked about their current thinking. Really cool, not only because it’s similar to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/d1a4a7bb-fc4d-41f2-8482-8a7afe1af0e6&quot;&gt;approach we took in FT Specialist&lt;/a&gt; and it’s always nice being validated, but because their communication style is brilliantly engaging &amp;amp; transparent in a way unlike anything I’ve ever experienced. Hoping for an eventual write-up!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Every year the FT does rounders in Regents Park and this year I went along for the first time. Genuinely fantastic seeing so many people (many for the first-time) and discovering how competitive some teams were. Highlights included light gossip, discovering a secret jägerbomb bar in the bushes and being massively sunburnt. &lt;em&gt;Fairly sure I got recruited as a wedding DJ&lt;/em&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/6f9856e3-eef0-47c1-970b-9dc1dbaa6252?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>