<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:53:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Lightning — Week 39, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[My iPhone 16 Pro Max preorder arrived this week, and it’s glorious.  New iOS is great and I’m enjoying the new button + camera control, but the best thing is that I no longer have any devices that use a Lightning Cable…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/84384a91-f760-4d74-9589-a3a843df7317?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/84384a91-f760-4d74-9589-a3a843df7317</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 22:03:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My iPhone 16 Pro Max preorder arrived this week, and it’s &lt;em&gt;glorious&lt;/em&gt;.  New iOS is great and I’m enjoying the new button + camera control, but the best thing is that I no longer have any devices that use a Lightning Cable!  We are a USB-C only house.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of my main focuses has been rolling forward a bunch of low-intervention changes which, once live, will make it far easier to monitor and reduce the usage of a legacy system.  It isn’t all done, but I’ve got it written up with a TDD and a lengthy living todo document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work hosted a “safety skills seminar” this week which featured an ex-copper coming in and talking about how to identify and avoid being the victim of phone thefts, etc. Lots of examples and lots learned, but my main takeaways are to take a breath before going into a new place (eg leaving the office) and to think like an adversary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made some headway with feedback loops: Model feedback as a hand-off in kanban terms, and when planning as a generic dependency.  Set some…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/84384a91-f760-4d74-9589-a3a843df7317?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Griddling — Week 38, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[An audible sigh emerged after I re-ran a Jupyter notebook and saw a result meaning I will have to delay some work. Loud enough to turn TK’s head. I got (only) one question wrong in our tech all-hands quiz, and am feeling…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/bbd1b132-2373-4c64-bda4-6b67ea47c051?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/bbd1b132-2373-4c64-bda4-6b67ea47c051</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 19:23:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An audible sigh emerged after I re-ran a Jupyter notebook and saw a result meaning I will have to delay some work. Loud enough to turn TK’s head.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I got (only) one question wrong in our tech all-hands quiz, and am feeling slightly salty about it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quite hyped about a few new features and bits of tech that are going live soon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Over the week I had a side-quest to assemble what I’m calling “lo-fi black-tie attire”: Including a casual black jacket, a clip-on tie and grand court 2.0s. With student discounts the whole set was silly cheap.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thursday evening I went to the Business Book Awards where my mum’s book “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.co.uk/dp/191138385X&quot;&gt;From Grenades to Griddles&lt;/a&gt;” won the second place award (“highly commended”) in its category - the judges were &lt;em&gt;super&lt;/em&gt; complimentary and I&apos;m so proud.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The awards were a gala dinner pulling in interesting people from all over the world.  Dinner was a selection of Indian cuisine; naturally I binged on chaat.  It was too spicy for some but the staff were under the impression it was mild…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/bbd1b132-2373-4c64-bda4-6b67ea47c051?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Pills & Tape — Week 37, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[In my head this week had two big themes: CP day and housework. CP day fell on Wednesday: it is my team’s quarterly all-in-office day. This round I was one of the organisers, and between holidays (and illness) we didn’t…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/16761d87-7f56-44a8-aff5-fd93383aaefe?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/16761d87-7f56-44a8-aff5-fd93383aaefe</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 20:45:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In my head this week had two big themes: CP day and housework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CP day fell on Wednesday: it is my team’s quarterly all-in-office day. This round I was one of the organisers, and between holidays (and illness) we didn’t have much time to prepare. We split the day in two (as a proven format), with the first half being talks and a workshop with the theme of reviewing/discontinuing features, and the second half being a supported OKR session.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Like with other events (eg &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/335131d2-edd3-4fc1-96da-e3aef0b5232d&quot;&gt;ENGINEROOM&lt;/a&gt;) there’s preparation, and the day itself. A few things needed tweaking in the days running up (including changing our prizes, corralling speakers and encouraging people to bake). The day-of ran &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; smoothly - so smoothly in-fact that we actually lengthened some sessions without (hopefully) anyone noticing. I planned in buffer time for time-keeping in a little spreadsheet, but we never needed any of it!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remember &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2536c4b8-a8a9-48cf-a337-e1f5ed1fae1b&quot;&gt;the thing about the wallet&lt;/a&gt;? I forgot to transfer over my corporate card which meant I had to open the…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/16761d87-7f56-44a8-aff5-fd93383aaefe?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Gastropod — Week 36, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Experimentally this week I switch from a card-holder to a chunky bifold wallet. On Monday I buy lunch in the canteen, and one of the servers chases after me to give me the wallet I’ve just dropped.  Awkward!  Right, that…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/2536c4b8-a8a9-48cf-a337-e1f5ed1fae1b?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/2536c4b8-a8a9-48cf-a337-e1f5ed1fae1b</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 21:36:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experimentally this week I switch from a card-holder to a chunky bifold wallet. On Monday I buy lunch in the canteen, and one of the servers chases after me to give me the wallet I’ve just dropped.  Awkward!  Right, that’s why no to wallets. This trial continues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Between planning work that involves talking, reflecting and writing (and waiting) - this week I spent focussed time cleaning up old systems and code to simplify the planning. One involved removing a hack that Rhys, Luke and I did in 2019 which had made it into production, and another involved removing an entire line in our architecture by closing a Kinesis stream.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Later MS, MT and I meet up for dinner. We encounter an excitable man who eagerly expresses his sheer dismay at how quiet London is tonight, before asking us if we might know why - and - where he might find a crazy party. He pauses for long enough for us to send him on his way to Soho. As he walks away, I spot a toothbrush in his pocket. Dinner is fine: Katzenjammers…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2536c4b8-a8a9-48cf-a337-e1f5ed1fae1b?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Pandora — Week 35, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[We begin on a momentous day: the beginning of Pumpkin Spice season.  Naturally It’s a Bank Holiday too. I down a PSL from a business park and read some papers. Watched Emily the Criminal (2024) on the train back to…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/ee798553-8a47-4994-94b6-02163dba69b2?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/ee798553-8a47-4994-94b6-02163dba69b2</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We begin on a momentous day: the beginning of Pumpkin Spice season.  Naturally It’s a Bank Holiday too. I down a PSL from a business park and read some papers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watched &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt15255876&quot;&gt;Emily the Criminal (2024)&lt;/a&gt; on the train back to London, which featured an unusually emotive Aubrey Plaza for a 3/5.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nearly go to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://lu.ma/p73046vr&quot;&gt;Bluesky meet&lt;/a&gt;, but LF &amp;amp; I get so lost in Liverpool Street that we arrive fashionably late.  Dan has started his talk and everyone seems engrossed, so instead of sheepishly barging in, we hit up a Beigel shop and head to the counting house.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The week’s drama peaks as a nearby building experiences a full callout of the London Fire Brigade with 7 whole fire-engines arriving within minutes.  If there &lt;em&gt;was&lt;/em&gt; a fire, they put it out so quickly we never even saw it.  The whole thing was awe-inspiring to watch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Z and I end up trying out 3C’s new dinner menu. It’s a strange model: Instead of hiring a chef, the bar seems to have sublet their kitchen to a family-run restaurant.  Their Pad Thai is decent…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ee798553-8a47-4994-94b6-02163dba69b2?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Symmetrical — Week 34, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[There’s a buzz in London’s rarefied air this week, and it isn’t the Notting Hill Carnival: Swifties from all over are in town to see the tail-end of the Eras tour.  The trains are not ready, and on Monday evening they…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/50d1a37a-2d49-44a1-a3ef-d85460324df1?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/50d1a37a-2d49-44a1-a3ef-d85460324df1</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 21:31:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There’s a buzz in London’s rarefied air this week, and it isn’t the Notting Hill Carnival: Swifties from all over are in town to see the tail-end of the Eras tour.  The trains are not ready, and on Monday evening they give out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In sharp contrast, the office feels quiet - putting into perspective my deep-dive into Google Drive’s permissions and API.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive API?  Not a fan.  The documentation is riddled with random jargon, implied behaviours and inconsistencies.  I learn a lot about things that even Google just aren’t able to do, and CR confirms that fixing or adding a few of them are “on their roadmap... eventually”.  And that some things aren’t.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I hardly sleep on Tuesday night for reasons I never fully work out, but it seems like there’s a correlation with the pollen forecast?  Wednesday goes OK but I feel fragile.  But I give up on spot plans to travel at the weekend.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feeling the telltale signs of seasonal allergies, I resume Fexofenadine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Over the week I fiddle with a research…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/50d1a37a-2d49-44a1-a3ef-d85460324df1?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Yvaga — Week 33, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[My love-hate relationship with Google Colab continues: I’m back to loving it, brought on by its secrets management which makes it easy to repeat sensitive analysis. A new trick which made my week is writing a dataframe…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/07374c72-69b6-4353-8d3a-0ead50324933?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/07374c72-69b6-4353-8d3a-0ead50324933</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 20:32:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My love-hate relationship with &lt;a href=&quot;https://colab.research.google.com&quot;&gt;Google Colab&lt;/a&gt; continues: I’m back to loving it, brought on by &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/GoogleColab/status/1719798406195867814&quot;&gt;its secrets management&lt;/a&gt; which makes it easy to repeat sensitive analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A new trick which made my week is writing a dataframe to Google Sheets for wrangling/sharing: &lt;a href=&quot;https://gspread-dataframe.readthedocs.io/&quot;&gt;gspread-dataframe&lt;/a&gt;’s &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;set_with_dataframe&lt;/code&gt; makes it so easy I can’t believe I hadn’t used it before!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/music/article/2024/jun/06/charli-xcx-brat-review-insecurity-obliterating-anthems-by-pops-most-human-superstar&quot;&gt;It’s a brat summer&lt;/a&gt;, late I know. I &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; 365’s acid line.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highlight of the week was NL’s birthday which started at The George, featured some wholesome conversations and ended at &lt;a href=&quot;https://mallowlondon.com/&quot;&gt;Mallow&lt;/a&gt;, who do a pretty mean burger.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thursday saw both the formation of the Coxinha Crew, and me getting a detailed Zodiac reading so close-to-home (yet seemingly devoid of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Barnum_effect&quot;&gt;Barnum statements&lt;/a&gt;) that I’m &lt;em&gt;still&lt;/em&gt; reeling all the way over here on Sunday.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ate some mid pizza and then watched &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt18412256&quot;&gt;Alien: Romulus (2024)&lt;/a&gt; with TM &amp;amp; LF: Loved the vibe, it felt a lot like the first film. ScreenX added nothing. “That Scene” was A Lot. Computers went bleep. Synthetics were thought-provoking. “Non…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/07374c72-69b6-4353-8d3a-0ead50324933?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Mending — Week 32, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Not much happened this past fortnight. I came down with Covid, and reader, it hit me hard. Like not leaving the apartment hard. 25/25 on Joe two weeks in a row tho. Wrote some pretty cool Splunk queries: Did you know…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/40fcf41f-757b-4312-8229-2bcddc303db9?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/40fcf41f-757b-4312-8229-2bcddc303db9</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 22:53:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not much happened this past fortnight. I came down with Covid, and reader, it hit me &lt;em&gt;hard&lt;/em&gt;. Like not leaving the apartment hard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;25/25 on Joe two weeks in a row tho.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wrote some pretty cool Splunk queries: Did you know that after adding categories to your events (&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;eval category=case(like(), &quot;Category 1&quot;, like(), &quot;Category 2&quot;, 1=1, &quot;Default&quot;)&lt;/code&gt;) you can then use an &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;xyseries&lt;/code&gt; to transform them into a columnar structure?  A few &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;transpose&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;table&lt;/code&gt;s later and now you’re cooking. &lt;em&gt;(without a spreadsheet!)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With not much I could actually do, I picked &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.igdb.com/games/the-legend-of-zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom&quot;&gt;Tears of the Kingdom&lt;/a&gt; back up after &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2815bfca-621e-4c87-b237-4e19a87e5a47&quot;&gt;unlocking all the Lightroots last year&lt;/a&gt; and beat all 120 shrines, all 32 sky shrines and a bunch of side-quests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuing the streak, I booted up &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.igdb.com/games/the-legend-of-zelda-breath-of-the-wild&quot;&gt;Breath of the Wild&lt;/a&gt; for the first time since 2017 and completed all 120 shrines there too and some of the EX shrines.  At some point the game design started to feel so tedious that my inner completionist took over and now here we are.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To keep my distance from the screens, I finally split the Switch&apos;s joycons. It&apos;s a really liberating play-style and I now really wish &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/40fcf41f-757b-4312-8229-2bcddc303db9?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Jubilation — Week 30, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Highlight of the week was our first-ever away-day for tech-leads and principals in my team. After a great ice-breaker we ran through many group activities including charting all the technical interactions needed to serve…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/d5d8284c-ca98-4242-bfb0-2ba590465b87?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/d5d8284c-ca98-4242-bfb0-2ba590465b87</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 21:51:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highlight of the week was our first-ever away-day for tech-leads and principals in my team. After a great ice-breaker we ran through many group activities including charting all the technical interactions needed to serve articles to users, which I loved but which pulled on enough of my esoteric knowledge that it was surprisingly draining: We covered an entire wall. Conversations over the day were all a genuine joy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For a proposal I’m working on, I’ve been combing through many systems and codebases to identify how they interact with a notorious area of our architecture.  I’ve learned a fair bit about the methodology: I tried to automate classification several ways but found the results &lt;em&gt;consistently&lt;/em&gt; variable and unreliable.  In the end generating dependency trees starting with our software catalogue, charting in a spreadsheet and then reading parts of source-code by hand has been far more effective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s always DNS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No improvements to the site this week, instead I focussed on the CMS: I write a lot on my phone and for the longest time have been unable to write on this website without a computer.  This week I &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/alexwilson/frontend/pull/2730&quot;&gt;moved my CMS to the Decap distribution&lt;/a&gt; and added in &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/alexwilson/frontend/issues/2731&quot;&gt;styles to make it mobile friendly&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/d5d8284c-ca98-4242-bfb0-2ba590465b87?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Calculating — Week 29, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[A week of noteworthy lunches. Even my Sainsbury’s meal-deal on Wednesday cooccurred with fun chat.  Spent a lot of time in VCV Rack in the evenings working on dangerous new hobby. My team had our first all-in-person…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/275ba2af-ae17-4cfe-bc40-4543f41510cc?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/275ba2af-ae17-4cfe-bc40-4543f41510cc</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 22:39:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A week of noteworthy lunches. Even my Sainsbury’s meal-deal on Wednesday cooccurred with fun chat.  Spent a lot of time in VCV Rack in the evenings working on dangerous new hobby.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My team had our first all-in-person retro in a little while and after our normal retro app refused to work, got to use real post-it notes on a whiteboard.  So analogue - I loved every second.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What brought on the in-person retro?  We welcomed a new member to our team this week, and I’m incredibly excited to work with him: We’re working across the same areas and there’s so much interesting work coming up!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;You see, it all comes back to google sheets?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had a 2-hour debrief on my &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facet5global.com/&quot;&gt;Facet5 profile&lt;/a&gt;, and while I suspect I answered some questions strangely and potentially distorted my scores, the general gist felt bang-on.  I’m a “&lt;a href=&quot;https://family.facet5gps.com/promoter/&quot;&gt;Promoter&lt;/a&gt;”.  Lots of interesting things that I can now work on, because I see my blindspots more clearly than after exercises &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/cdf6575f-d01f-43bb-8a26-eb1530ca9952/&quot;&gt;like the Johari window&lt;/a&gt;.  I’m hyped.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week’s major update to the blog was &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/alexwilson/frontend/pull/2715&quot;&gt;an overhaul of the typography, implementing a fluid scale&lt;/a&gt;, meaning text is now bigger and more legible for…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/275ba2af-ae17-4cfe-bc40-4543f41510cc?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>