<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 23:27:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: SkyTweeting — Week 17, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Upward trajectory this week: Started out feeling fairly unenthused and ended in a much better place.  There's power to figuring out what's bothering you, west-winging it and then trying to work through it.  Highly…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/ca79da85-4fca-4434-9e6c-9f975b0a9121?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/ca79da85-4fca-4434-9e6c-9f975b0a9121</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 22:35:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upward trajectory this week: Started out feeling fairly unenthused and ended in a much better place.  There&apos;s power to figuring out what&apos;s bothering you, west-winging it and then trying to work through it.  Highly recommended.  Bias for action is coming back, slowly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week started with a live-coding exercise with one of our journalists.  Quite often technologists will shadow or do various business processes (famously, Nandos encouraging people into kitchens) - so flipping it on its head is a bit novel and I hope we pulled it off?  Maybe we can do more?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We also had several major outages impacting the homepage this week.  Mostly out-of-hours and all slightly different.  All exhausting.  I got to write a bit of code to help mitigate the last one.  This long weekend is well-deserved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/efinlay24/&quot;&gt;Euan&lt;/a&gt;&apos;s last day was Friday.  Over forty people stopped by for his Thursday send-off - which speaks volumes - it&apos;s probably the most fun I&apos;ve had in a pub all year.  Friday was a very quiet day.  I&apos;ll miss…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ca79da85-4fca-4434-9e6c-9f975b0a9121?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Alarming — Week 16, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Had a blast writing up how one of our systems (Magnet, for the interested) works.  Went in knowing a lot about how two parts of it worked.  I wrote out an outline around what its main request/response lifecycle worked…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/29cfad30-e864-4142-aad8-e66540df88c6?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/29cfad30-e864-4142-aad8-e66540df88c6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 21:42:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had a blast writing up how one of our systems (Magnet, for the interested) works.  Went in knowing a lot about how two parts of it worked.  I wrote out an outline around what its main request/response lifecycle worked like and started a deep-dive to fill it out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;While eating a lunch of katsu curry outside &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thened.com/&quot;&gt;The Ned&lt;/a&gt; on Monday, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.willhoward.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Will&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; I became unwitting participants of a China protest.  People walked past waving placards and handing out flyers with QR codes.  The chicken was pretty good, although the portion was huge and I struggled to finish.  Solid 8/10.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Men literally only want to talk about two things (Religion &amp;amp; History) and it&apos;s disgusting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuesday evening I left the office to meet the people at the boozy golfing social, and met the other people at the other boozy golfing social instead.  Then ran from the Seahorse to Nandos: You can do it in ~7 minutes on a good day, I did it in 8.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My group made an afternoon of teams running through their OKRs.  Genuinely heartwarming seeing so many…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/29cfad30-e864-4142-aad8-e66540df88c6?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Running — Week 15, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[This was a short week, but it didn't feel like a short week.  It really didn't feel like a short week. [This week's soundtrack is R﻿unning: a minimal, layered banger that gives me real producer envy] “What are you doing…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/789ef44b-fb44-47b3-9477-8b7717dea1e4?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/789ef44b-fb44-47b3-9477-8b7717dea1e4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 22:13:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This was a short week, but it didn&apos;t feel like a short week.  It really didn&apos;t feel like a short week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;[This week&apos;s soundtrack is &lt;a href=&quot;https://teenagemutants.bandcamp.com/track/running&quot;&gt;R﻿unning&lt;/a&gt;: a minimal, layered banger that gives me real producer envy]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“What are you doing?” came a voice from across the office.  “Looking for isopropyl alcohol” I replied, manner-of-factly, as if it was the most normal thing in the world to be doing in a workplace.  Folks, it was only a matter of time: I spilled some coffee onto a keyboard and needed something non-conductive to clean with.  The keyboard hasn&apos;t been the same since.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&apos;m a &lt;a href=&quot;https://logseq.com/&quot;&gt;Logseq&lt;/a&gt; person now.  &lt;em&gt;I think&lt;/em&gt;.  It&apos;s another one of these knowledge-management tools (like Obsidian), including the cute little graph, but what&apos;s drew me is that it&apos;s block-based and driven by daily journals.  I try to write notes as I go - either in Notion or on pen &amp;amp; paper (❤️ BuJo) - so this fits my style perfectly.  Giving it a proper go.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://codebar.io/workshops/2630&quot;&gt;The FT hosted Codebar on Wednesday&lt;/a&gt;.  I signed up, either to speak or coach, and…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/789ef44b-fb44-47b3-9477-8b7717dea1e4?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Plumbing — Week 14, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Week has flown by.  Made some small tweaks to this site, reviewed a few technical documents and have started exploring how to do dynamic imports of one-shot code into articles (which is both a personal and a work problem…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/4f2baa24-3c62-490a-b63b-0a9acfcf3160?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/4f2baa24-3c62-490a-b63b-0a9acfcf3160</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 22:37:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Week has flown by.  Made some small tweaks to this site, reviewed a few technical documents and have started exploring how to do dynamic imports of one-shot code into articles (which is both a personal and a work problem).  There&apos;s a pull-request I need to finish at work that brings more caching improvements.  Writing this mostly for personal accountability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Met &lt;a href=&quot;https://alicebartlett.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Alice&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://georgecrawford.com/&quot;&gt;George&lt;/a&gt; for what we&apos;re calling a &lt;em&gt;power-breakfast&lt;/em&gt; on Wednesday.  Who needs drinks after work when you can just talk life, shop and gossip at 8AM.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ended up at a nomikai (飲み会) with Japanese colleagues.  Fun chatter.  Reminded me of going to these regularly years ago, only now I understand much more.  Wish I could keep up with more complex conversation though: It&apos;d be nice to practice simpler Japanese with people at my level.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Someone pointed out that Kanji are complicated for &lt;em&gt;everyone&lt;/em&gt; and so I shouldn&apos;t let them hold me back, so I installed &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/FooSoft/yomichan&quot;&gt;Yomichan&lt;/a&gt; (basically a dictionary?) and have been able to read (and write) a little…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/4f2baa24-3c62-490a-b63b-0a9acfcf3160?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Blossoming — Week 13, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Celebrating 2 consecutive years of not being tricked on April fools day.  Maybe it's a good thing that it fell on a weekend this time. Spring is here!  I left the office on Monday and for the first time all year it was…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/10983003-89c5-421e-bb18-790c786ea968?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/10983003-89c5-421e-bb18-790c786ea968</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 14:26:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Celebrating 2 consecutive years of not being tricked on April fools day.  Maybe it&apos;s a good thing that it fell on a weekend this time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spring is here!  I left the office on Monday and for the first time all year it was still light.  I tied both of my Martenitsi onto a tree that was blossoming directly opposite St Pauls, and then made it my mission this week to convince others to add theirs to the same tree.  My mission was successful.  It is now &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Martenitsa&quot;&gt;Martenitsa&lt;/a&gt; tree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went on a tour of the infrastructure supporting our office on Wednesday. The amount of behind-the-scenes work going into keeping the building running is just incredible and in particular the climate-control: Some of the chonkiest machines are controlling variables like CO2 balance, humidity, temperature and more are all continuously across many small zones for all five tiny floors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday was &lt;a href=&quot;https://cityjsconf.org/&quot;&gt;CityJS conference&lt;/a&gt;, set in the delightful Royal Geographical Society.  Most of the talks were bangers, although my clear fave was Mike Hartington&apos;s talk on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/live/RdiXuoMPtUA?feature=share&amp;amp;t=21435&quot;&gt;Delighting Users with Performant Apps&lt;/a&gt;.  Great examples of how to make the UI/UX of web-apps fantastic.  Still more difficult to get to a great state than it should…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/10983003-89c5-421e-bb18-790c786ea968?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: ManHou — Week 12, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Started the week with a workshop introducing our new technology strategy to the tech-leads and senior engineers working on FT.com. After Anna ran through the strategy and its background, and the other technical directors…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/4ba59b0c-47c4-497c-a6b4-60be30496b57?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/4ba59b0c-47c4-497c-a6b4-60be30496b57</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:39:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Started the week with a workshop introducing our new technology strategy to the tech-leads and senior engineers working on FT.com. After &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annashipman.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Anna&lt;/a&gt; ran through the strategy and its background, and the other technical directors added their insights, we split out into break-out groups to discuss the the two most impactful areas of the strategy.  I think it went well?  Although, I struggled a bit with facilitating because we spoke a little more about process than I was prepared for.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In less interesting news I finally made a small tweak to this blog to improve bullet-point spacing, which should make these imminently more readable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wrote a product release this week for the first time since 2020, and people have been rather nice about it.  I&apos;ve got another one in-draft but am struggling with narrative.  This is why you write your product hypotheses before building anything folks!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday brought many of my old colleagues from various Nikkei programmes to the office, and it was really nice to catch…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/4ba59b0c-47c4-497c-a6b4-60be30496b57?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Administrating — Week 11, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Loved that on budget day all I saw on various news channels was teacher & train strikes.  Sums up the mood of the nation right now. Wednesday saw a workshop about current and future ways of publishing interactive…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/8fa9f24d-624e-411e-9691-ca628c901946?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/8fa9f24d-624e-411e-9691-ca628c901946</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 22:23:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Loved that on budget day all I saw on various news channels was teacher &amp;amp; train strikes.  Sums up the mood of the nation right now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wednesday saw a workshop about current and future ways of publishing interactive journalism. We ideated and diverged in all the ways a good design sprint should and wrapped up with a series of case-studies including &lt;a href=&quot;https://observablehq.com/&quot;&gt;Observable&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://svelte.dev/&quot;&gt;Svelte&lt;/a&gt; at the NYT and web-components in mid-2010s Methode.  Next steps are deeper dives into the tech and orchestrating some kind of reconvergence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phew.  I made it to the end of one administrative labyrinth.  It took a surprising amount of time.  Ready for another.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week I started using &lt;a href=&quot;https://zed.dev&quot;&gt;Zed&lt;/a&gt; a bit for development.  It&apos;s not as fully-featured as VSCode, but, it does support language servers and &lt;em&gt;it&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;fast&lt;/em&gt;.  Like so fast.  It&apos;s bringing me back to the days when I used Sublime Text for everything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mixed mental health week this week.  Some of the tools I&apos;ve picked up recently &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; helping and I&apos;m feeling less anxiety and apathy, but, I&apos;ve also been particularly bad at masking and people have noticed - which is - &lt;em&gt;ehhhhhhhh&lt;/em&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/8fa9f24d-624e-411e-9691-ca628c901946?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Noodling — Week 10, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[One of the trees outside my living room window went into bloom last month.  This week it was covered with snow.  I don't think this is how spring is supposed to start, but, for the few hours it lasted, it was beautiful…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/6cfaf4aa-f550-4aa1-9bb2-d4a4954bf0b9?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/6cfaf4aa-f550-4aa1-9bb2-d4a4954bf0b9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 13:56:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of the trees outside my living room window went into bloom last month.  This week it was covered with snow.  I don&apos;t think this is how spring is supposed to start, but, for the few hours it lasted, it was beautiful.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recently I joined a Reforge product management cohort: This week we ran through product strategy frameworks, and discussed the difficulties of translating internal-facing products into frameworks/structures, as many are designed for external-facing products with clear commercials.  Strangely the industry prioritises growth over &lt;em&gt;everything&lt;/em&gt; else.  But improvements to organisational efficiency and efficacy (eg in acquiring/retaining users) &quot;lowers the floor&quot; in ARPU (annual revenue per user) which seems just as effective as growth.  Maybe I&apos;m unique in finding this exciting?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excited about news this week that I&apos;m taking on a new team, meaning that I will now oversee all of the engineering teams involved in showing journalism to readers. Have done this before (on a smaller…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/6cfaf4aa-f550-4aa1-9bb2-d4a4954bf0b9?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Shrinkflating — Week 9, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[A small change I quietly released to ft.com last week has received such positive reception that people I wouldn't even expect to know about it have commented. I'm used to people celebrating improvements, but this seems…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/81f4ad1c-d6e4-4d6f-8a92-b8e74a10d9d9?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/81f4ad1c-d6e4-4d6f-8a92-b8e74a10d9d9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 17:34:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A small change I quietly released to ft.com last week has received such positive reception that people I wouldn&apos;t even expect to &lt;em&gt;know&lt;/em&gt; about it have commented. I&apos;m used to people celebrating improvements, but this seems really disproportionate!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week has been very much about trying to get on with it.  Bias for action and all that.  With the year starting out the way it did, I&apos;ve felt like suboptimal physical &amp;amp; mental health have held me back.  Ahead of planning/reviewing/refining full personal objectives, I&apos;m making decisions towards an intentionally vague &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.themesystem.com/&quot;&gt;theme&lt;/a&gt; I drafted last year.  This month&apos;s priority is getting back on track.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inspired by that I started taking private Japanese lessons.  Even with a hundred-odd kanji memorised, we&apos;ve deliberately started with the basics, following a highly-structured approach because &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/5bcff697-194c-48a1-a439-9fdc789f6cf1&quot;&gt;last year&apos;s feedback&lt;/a&gt; left me very aware that I don&apos;t sound natural.  Next stop: N5.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Also had a therapy session this week.  CBT hasn&apos;t really been doing much for me…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/81f4ad1c-d6e4-4d6f-8a92-b8e74a10d9d9?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Procuring — Week 8, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reader, this week I've been navigating many teams, systems and process going through a procurement process.  The process itself is actually great and I'm enjoying how far it's come since the days of endless spreadsheets…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/2eb20c54-1cf0-4801-8733-ab7a4a481f96?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/2eb20c54-1cf0-4801-8733-ab7a4a481f96</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 22:30:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reader, this week I&apos;ve been navigating many teams, systems and process going through a procurement process.  The process itself is actually great and I&apos;m enjoying how far it&apos;s come since the days of endless spreadsheets and Salesforce.  What&apos;s confusing is the specific arrangement I&apos;m pursuing where I can&apos;t find any one person who can tell me what to do or how to do it.  So this week you may call me &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.britannica.com/topic/Josef-K&quot;&gt;Josef&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Soon I start working on the problem which I&apos;ve previously referred to as the &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/topic/product-coexistence&quot;&gt;“Product Coexistence problem“&lt;/a&gt;, which through reframing has become about pragmatically introducing support for extending front-ends.  It&apos;s exciting and should result in pushing technical boundaries in a constructive way.  I&apos;m excited about the implications for one-shot content, like, say, the interactive charts we publish.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Last week when I mentioned I was coming down with something, it turned out that I had mostly-asymptomatic Covid, which I wouldn&apos;t have caught without routine testing. Other than a sore throat on Saturday I didn&apos;t have a single trace. Goes to show that testing helps. And this net trend towards milder symptoms is &lt;em&gt;probably&lt;/em&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2eb20c54-1cf0-4801-8733-ab7a4a481f96?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>