<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 11:33:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Exposition — Week 38, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[The two big themes of this week are: Kafka and the 2025 World Expo.  Both have been prompted much thought. Kafka is a technology I’ve used indirectly a lot over the years. A deep dive this week helped me understand it…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/904396c1-32e8-4cd6-a491-1afa98b74b34?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/904396c1-32e8-4cd6-a491-1afa98b74b34</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 14:20:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The two big themes of this week are: Kafka and the 2025 World Expo.  Both have been prompted much thought.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kafka is a technology I’ve used indirectly a lot over the years. A deep dive this week helped me understand it better, and so I’ve been reimagining how some big systems might work if built on Kafka with Event Sourcing, which has been very exciting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A big dinner during the week turns out to be a big miss, which is a good thing because it reminds me just how good the service and food is in most places.  Important not to take anything for granted!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday night karaoke is pretty good.  We start at dinner and end up in a booth where I discover Pendulum is on the docket and that it &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; possible to do Karaoke to Drum ‘n Bass.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My subsequent adventure to find hard techno starts on a high note: I meet interesting people and have eclectic conversations.  But one interaction brings me vividly back to a night in Germany, which raises the question: Is this still fun?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Over the week I also go on…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/904396c1-32e8-4cd6-a491-1afa98b74b34?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Banking — Week 37, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This was a good week?  22.53km of running. Part of this week went into a messy incident and data-recovery operation.  I’m actively thinking about architectural interventions to prevent scenarios exactly like this one, so…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/8a12f155-bdf5-4b5e-9d92-7ee4ad0f0513?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/8a12f155-bdf5-4b5e-9d92-7ee4ad0f0513</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 14:13:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This was a good week?  22.53km of running.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Part of this week went into a messy incident and data-recovery operation.  I’m actively thinking about architectural interventions to prevent scenarios exactly like this one, so this was very timely.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With my plate clearer, I had an uninterrupted day to work on strategy, and made good progress.  The hardest part is always starting, so I’ve begun with Will Larson’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://lethain.com/good-engineering-strategy-is-boring/&quot;&gt;“Write five, then synthesize”&lt;/a&gt; approach which is &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; JFDI-minded.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One afternoon, instead of lunch, on the way to the office I make a pit-stop in Toranomon Hills for a long-anticipated coffee where I learn a lot about fin-tech, a lot about founding a company in Japan and also get a great pep-talk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amongst serious songs, at karaoke I do &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZZ5LpwO-An4&quot;&gt;the He-Man duet of “What&apos;s Up?”&lt;/a&gt; with DS.  Later I pray that the only recording of this moment is the one now forever etched into my brain.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After two false starts - which involve walking to okubo and helping set up a bunch of accounts - Friday night we…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/8a12f155-bdf5-4b5e-9d92-7ee4ad0f0513?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Painting — Week 36, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[September is here, meaning I’ve now been here 9 months.  September also means summer is ending, but nobody has told the cicadas yet, or thought to turn down the temperature-dial outside. Self-introductions this week in…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/cb4e8d65-7cfd-440e-acc5-04801be33427?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/cb4e8d65-7cfd-440e-acc5-04801be33427</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 11:57:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;September is here, meaning I’ve now been here 9 months.  September also means summer is ending, but nobody has told the cicadas yet, or thought to turn down the temperature-dial outside.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-introductions this week in my new class.  Did you know that the word for clown is ピエロ or pierō?  Derived from a French cartoon and since enshrined in katakana.  Useful word to know for my future self-introductions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Levelled up my home coffee game: This week I made my first &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hometown_tax&quot;&gt;furusato nōzei&lt;/a&gt; contribution (to Aichi, obviously, since it’s the closest thing to West Midlands), and received a mahoosive bag of coffee for my troubles.  Procured an Aeropress to make it with, and I’m pretty chuffed with the results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m running again: It’s going OK, and I’ve nearly caught up on all the progress I lost this past month.  I’ve worked out why I keep injuring myself — my right heel strike is off — and so now am looking for a coach &amp;amp; physio to correct it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finished a big migration: It happened piece-by-piece and…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/cb4e8d65-7cfd-440e-acc5-04801be33427?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Hazing — Week 35, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Memorable week. Managed a 3 day Tantanmen streak: One in Shibaura, one in Ebisu and one in Tamachi.  All were different but all were good. Reconnected with a few key people this week.  One night in Ebisu over tacos and…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/e1abdf65-9ebc-42a6-8c71-f485307e844e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/e1abdf65-9ebc-42a6-8c71-f485307e844e</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 14:37:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Memorable week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managed a 3 day Tantanmen streak: One in Shibaura, one in Ebisu and one in Tamachi.  All were different but all were good.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reconnected with a few key people this week.  One night in Ebisu over tacos and pineapple highballs, and the other near Tokyo station.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tokyo station was me breaking my “no-meetups” rule, because I was invited.  It was great!  Had a few nice conversations, remembered why the “Always try to ask a question” rule carries important nuance and later received some overdue and worthy validation on how I approached a technical project many years ago.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experimentally I have trialling a new type of aggressive prioritisation (where 80% of other work is either deferred or delegated) instead of time-blocking, and I’m finding it both enjoyable and useful.  It’s something like a more extreme version of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Time_management#Eisenhower_method&quot;&gt;Eisenhower matrix&lt;/a&gt;, inspired by some highly effective former colleagues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But as an exception to these priorities, I’m preparing a new &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/ft-product-technology/thinking-through-our-changes-with-design-documents-35c93bf0938b&quot;&gt;Tech-Design-Document template&lt;/a&gt; and have been pleasantly surprised at the diversity of feedback I’ve received, and how much this has taught me about different ways-of-working and engineering philosophies.  Ranging from the naming &lt;em&gt;(TDD is a bit like test-driven-development, ne?)&lt;/em&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/e1abdf65-9ebc-42a6-8c71-f485307e844e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Carding — Week 34, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lately I’ve been distracted.  In previous chapters of life I prioritised work above all else and I tied it to my sense of self-worth.  There’s lots to say on that subject, but, not today.  Lessons in-hand, in this…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/ad4581f8-b83b-422d-bf5b-c44b1eb8d78f?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/ad4581f8-b83b-422d-bf5b-c44b1eb8d78f</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 14:31:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lately I’ve been distracted.  In previous chapters of life I prioritised work above all else and I tied it to my sense of self-worth.  There’s lots to say on that subject, but, not today.  Lessons in-hand, in this chapter I’m now prioritising life too, and am re-learning some things including my self-worth, which is bringing new ups-and-downs.  But I’m enjoying them, a lot.  So, yes, I’ve been distracted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My highlight of the week was a team dinner with one of my teams, which we realised was the first time we’d all assembled in person.  We discovered many things including a shared love of Mexican food - which led to a recommendation of &lt;a href=&quot;https://tabelog.com/tokyo/A1303/A130302/13309222/&quot;&gt;3 Hermanos&lt;/a&gt; - and to my discovery of a new lunch spot near the office.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Getting a chance to learn about more advanced framework features in &lt;a href=&quot;https://rubyonrails.org&quot;&gt;Rails&lt;/a&gt; has been fun.  After I clocked out for the week, I connected some dots and realised a mistake in my work which I now get to fix.  It’s been a while since I had a moment like this with a novel tech-stack, so this…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ad4581f8-b83b-422d-bf5b-c44b1eb8d78f?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Suffocating — Week 33, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[A while ago I said that my tag-cloud would’ve highlighted “Lunch“, this week it would’ve highlighted “Coffee”.  Several memorable coffee catch-ups (without incident, this time).  My current side-quest involves one of the…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/a767410e-0706-4a55-bb67-091b6a31f7fb?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/a767410e-0706-4a55-bb67-091b6a31f7fb</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 14:55:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A while ago I said that my tag-cloud would’ve highlighted “Lunch“, this week it would’ve highlighted “Coffee”.  Several memorable coffee catch-ups (without incident, this time).  My current side-quest involves one of the less walked (and, documented?) roads of being a senior IC: networking.  More about this another time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nothing too exciting to report.  Got involved in some discussions, and tried to create focus-time to ship something.  Made some progress.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tragedy struck at Sonicmania after the epiphany that I was dancing to Drum ’n Bass but I hadn’t brought my brand new &lt;a href=&quot;https://kneecap.backstreetmerch.com/products/logo-bucket-hat&quot;&gt;Kneecap bucket hat&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But, it was was &lt;strong&gt;brilliant&lt;/strong&gt;.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.summersonic.com/sonicmania/&quot;&gt;Sonicmania&lt;/a&gt; is the all-nighter pre-party for &lt;a href=&quot;https://summersonic.com/&quot;&gt;Summer Sonic&lt;/a&gt;.  It was mostly electronic acts, and it let me finally tick &lt;a href=&quot;https://theprodigy.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;The Prodigy off my bucket list (somehow I missed them completely when I lived in London).  I &lt;em&gt;loved&lt;/em&gt; their set.  Many memorable moments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I saw... &lt;em&gt;sharp inhale of breath&lt;/em&gt; ... &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Perfume_(Japanese_band)&quot;&gt;PERFUME&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2hollis&quot;&gt;2HOLLIS&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kyary_Pamyu_Pamyu&quot;&gt;Kyary Pamyu Pamyu&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/floatingpoints&quot;&gt;Floating Points&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/prodigythe&quot;&gt;The Prodigy&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/gesaffelstein&quot;&gt;Gesaffelstein&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/shioriybradshaw&quot;&gt;Shiory Bradshaw&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/minna-no-kimochi&quot;&gt;Minna-no-Kimochi&lt;/a&gt;.  All were great performances with high production value, and great energy in the room.  I had major FOMO for the acts I &lt;em&gt;couldn’t&lt;/em&gt; see.  [&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/stories/highlights/18073701635098980/&quot;&gt;highlight reel&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/a767410e-0706-4a55-bb67-091b6a31f7fb?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Blues — Week 32, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[I really enjoyed this week, but, I didn’t have a good week.  Looking back, in many ways it reminds me of that week when we went to the Wolf. This week I shipped some code, wrote some documents and chatted with some other…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/41ef9228-75ba-4a91-8a20-78149d2e5f74?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/41ef9228-75ba-4a91-8a20-78149d2e5f74</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 12:37:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I really enjoyed this week, but, I didn’t have a good week.  Looking back, in many ways it reminds me of that week when we went to the Wolf.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week I shipped some code, wrote some documents and chatted with some other teams about their problems.  Spoke a bit with some colleagues about a monkey’s paw I’ve been offered and came to a conclusion.  (This is the post I put on &quot;&quot;&quot;The Gram&quot;&quot;&quot; the other week)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had an unfortunate incident involving a Starbucks Venti latte.   The less said, the better, but it happened in an &lt;em&gt;incredibly&lt;/em&gt; public place and now I keep chatting to people who “heard about [it]”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attempted to check out fireworks this weekend, and here’s how that went: Saturday - cancelled due to heavy rain.  Sunday - cancelled due to a fire.  Sign from the universe?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seems like everyone is sick this week.  Hope it’s nothing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.asagaya.or.jp/tanabata/tanabata.html&quot;&gt;Asagaya Tanabata festival&lt;/a&gt; at the weekend which was hella crowded but was lined with good food.  That’s where the paper-mache statues were.  [&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.asagaya.or.jp/tanabata/100selection.html&quot;&gt;It goes back ages&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/41ef9228-75ba-4a91-8a20-78149d2e5f74?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Allocations — Week 31, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[A week of doing things I'd meant to do for literally years. After battling with some Kubernetes configuration, I ran a (very!) large data migration job late this week.  From a purist perspective - in GitOps - even one…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/60ea6f5a-918b-4e71-8b3b-b32fbaea649e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/60ea6f5a-918b-4e71-8b3b-b32fbaea649e</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 14:24:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A week of doing things I&apos;d meant to do for literally years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After battling with some Kubernetes configuration, I ran a (very!) large data migration job late this week.  From a purist perspective - in GitOps - even one-off tasks need to go into Git.  And these operations are supposed to be immutable so you can’t just &lt;a href=&quot;https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/12/introducing-suspended-jobs/&quot;&gt;suspend&lt;/a&gt; them and come back later.  I’m sure I’ve misunderstood something?  There has to be a better way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learned some very interesting and exciting familial lore, which led me into discovering that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tartanregister.gov.uk/&quot;&gt;there is a tartan registry&lt;/a&gt;, and to realising that the GDS lot still haven&apos;t got to it.  Starting to understand the complaining about the Londoners.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The word &quot;Allocations&quot; has been sitting rather ominously at the top of these notes, which I have been completely unable to decipher.  And so it has become the title of this week’s notes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accidentally talked myself into a lunch invite, and am very glad I did because the conversation was great, but the discovery of a brand new lunch place offering an &lt;em&gt;above-average&lt;/em&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/60ea6f5a-918b-4e71-8b3b-b32fbaea649e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Pressure — Week 30, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[For me, it was the water pressure.  After a week of dribbling taps & spluttering shower-heads in England, the contrasting flow when I got home was the starkest and most visceral reminder that I wasn’t in England anymore…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/e1e629e1-9f78-4de1-b077-7df9deb3e91f?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/e1e629e1-9f78-4de1-b077-7df9deb3e91f</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:55:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For me, it was the water pressure.  After a week of dribbling taps &amp;amp; spluttering shower-heads in England, the contrasting flow when I got home was the starkest and most visceral reminder that I wasn’t in England anymore.  I guess I was too tired to notice all the others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monday was a &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; long day. I went for a run to get breakfast, did some work, and then headed to Paddington where I met Z and JW for a quick lemonade in the sun.  It started raining.  Heathrow was the fastest it’s ever been, I was at my gate in under 20 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The direct plane journey back is no picnic: I napped but 14 hours is far too long and I regret not having a layover.  Managed 5 films, of which by far the most interesting was &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt12299608&quot;&gt;Mickey 17 (2025)&lt;/a&gt; which I’m giving a 3.5/5.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt1745960/&quot;&gt;Top Gun Maverick (2024)&lt;/a&gt; also gets 3.5/5 but in a different way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have created a new question-bank for job interviews, building on my last one.  Each question is split by competency and level (although I need to better script follow-ups) and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annashipman.co.uk/jfdi/interviewing-fairly.html&quot;&gt;scored with a rubric based on the 0-3 scale I learned from Anna&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/e1e629e1-9f78-4de1-b077-7df9deb3e91f?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Diners Club — Week 29, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week’s story is best told through its dinners. Monday we find ourselves at The Indian Brewery.  We order two naans and a side of fish.  This is pit-stop on the way to cocktails after a few hours in the sun. Tuesday…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/a118ee8a-9154-4390-b43d-9c44720df964?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/a118ee8a-9154-4390-b43d-9c44720df964</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 22:31:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week’s story is best told through its dinners.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monday we find ourselves at The Indian Brewery.  We order two naans and a side of fish.  This is pit-stop on the way to cocktails after a few hours in the sun.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuesday ends at Birmingham’s most notorious institution: Maccies on the Ramp.  We have a tradition, born in darker days, which always finds us either here or Temple Row.  We meet near Ikon and take the long way round discussing startups and runners.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wednesday’s dinner is a humble Meal Deal: It’s a cost-effective way of powering our mini-celebration of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.co.uk/newsround/48991574&quot;&gt;St Swithin’s day&lt;/a&gt;. There’s two excellent coffees - I haven’t had espresso drinks in a hot minute so these keep me up into the wee hours.  The night ends with me extolling the virtues of powdered jasmine tea - which is perfectly proportioned to blend with a pint of iced water.  Then I go for a (very) long walk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thursday is a killer serving of Falafel &amp;amp; Halloumi with a side of Ayran.  It caps AN’s leaving drinks - which are…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/a118ee8a-9154-4390-b43d-9c44720df964?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>