<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 04:35:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Procuring — Week 8, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reader, this week I've been navigating many teams, systems and process going through a procurement process.  The process itself is actually great and I'm enjoying how far it's come since the days of endless spreadsheets…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/2eb20c54-1cf0-4801-8733-ab7a4a481f96?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/2eb20c54-1cf0-4801-8733-ab7a4a481f96</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 22:30:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reader, this week I&apos;ve been navigating many teams, systems and process going through a procurement process.  The process itself is actually great and I&apos;m enjoying how far it&apos;s come since the days of endless spreadsheets and Salesforce.  What&apos;s confusing is the specific arrangement I&apos;m pursuing where I can&apos;t find any one person who can tell me what to do or how to do it.  So this week you may call me &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.britannica.com/topic/Josef-K&quot;&gt;Josef&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Soon I start working on the problem which I&apos;ve previously referred to as the &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/topic/product-coexistence&quot;&gt;“Product Coexistence problem“&lt;/a&gt;, which through reframing has become about pragmatically introducing support for extending front-ends.  It&apos;s exciting and should result in pushing technical boundaries in a constructive way.  I&apos;m excited about the implications for one-shot content, like, say, the interactive charts we publish.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Last week when I mentioned I was coming down with something, it turned out that I had mostly-asymptomatic Covid, which I wouldn&apos;t have caught without routine testing. Other than a sore throat on Saturday I didn&apos;t have a single trace. Goes to show that testing helps. And this net trend towards milder symptoms is &lt;em&gt;probably&lt;/em&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2eb20c54-1cf0-4801-8733-ab7a4a481f96?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Incanting — Week 7, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[There's a genuine spark of wonder that I've been feeling recently as I've been discovering and learning about the more obscure parts of the FT.com stack.  Last year my assignments kept me away from the less maintained…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/0ca489c6-34ba-4571-84b9-4084c8ae318f?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/0ca489c6-34ba-4571-84b9-4084c8ae318f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 14:14:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There&apos;s a genuine spark of wonder that I&apos;ve been feeling recently as I&apos;ve been discovering and learning about the more obscure parts of the FT.com stack.  Last year my assignments kept me away from the less maintained systems and so it&apos;s been surprisingly fun seeing how people approached problems several years ago - and years later, seeing how t approach aged.heir&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;That isn&apos;t a popular opinion and it definitely isn&apos;t how I&apos;ll always feel.  Years ago I&apos;d actively &lt;em&gt;sworn&lt;/em&gt; at old code (although in my defence I defy anyone not to swear at the logic of recursive cURL calls in PHP!).   But, there&apos;s a big difference between spelunking through systems in an exploratory way, and doing so while trying to ship a specific feature on a deadline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CBT is, you know, fine.  I&apos;m in it for the long-haul I guess.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bear with me: &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/6f2c2faa-cc8d-4c83-b2e4-048d5d893a27&quot;&gt;Last year I got an Analogue Pocket&lt;/a&gt;.  And, last week I got a copy of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Urbz:_Sims_in_the_City&quot;&gt;The Urbz&lt;/a&gt;.  It seemed like a good way to all this spend time in recovery.  Only one problem, some unlocks in the game require multiplayer.  So I bought a GBA linker cable for £3, dumped my save file and re-read &lt;a href=&quot;https://problemkaputt.de/gbatek.htm#gbacartbackupids&quot;&gt;how GBA saves work&lt;/a&gt; so I could…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/0ca489c6-34ba-4571-84b9-4084c8ae318f?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Depending — Week 6, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week someone said "it's almost March".  Mate.  I've barely noticed it's not January any more.  Not cool. The trouble with changing old systems is that sometimes you end up navigating a Kafkaesque confusion of…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/fe0bdfa4-dc79-4e18-b77e-ae8d9c1761e5?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/fe0bdfa4-dc79-4e18-b77e-ae8d9c1761e5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 23:42:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week someone said &quot;it&apos;s almost March&quot;.  Mate.  I&apos;ve barely noticed it&apos;s not January any more.  &lt;em&gt;Not cool&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The trouble with changing old systems is that sometimes you end up navigating a Kafkaesque confusion of package managers.  I wrote some code, improved some tests and while trying to deploy it all fell into a battle with nested dependencies.  At time of writing, the dependencies are winning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&apos;m glad that the promotions round is over.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alex.mullr.net/&quot;&gt;Alex&lt;/a&gt; bakes a pretty mean cookie!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In a slightly welcome distraction, Mum stayed the weekend and we spent the time exploring Barnes and Fulham.  Ended up eating Golubtsy/Голубцы for dinner and being surprised at the season 2 finale of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt7016936/&quot;&gt;Killing Eve&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.polygon.com/23589160/nintendo-direct-2023-february-date-time-zelda-advance-wars&quot;&gt;Nintendo direct this week&lt;/a&gt; was pretty cool.  Expect to hear more gushing about it imminently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oh crap, I should probably get to doing that write-up of 2022 huh?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have had trouble sleeping this week.  I can&apos;t place if it&apos;s random, stress or something else.  But with this journey I&apos;ve been on recently…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/fe0bdfa4-dc79-4e18-b77e-ae8d9c1761e5?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Tarrying — Week 5, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[F﻿irst week all year not involving time in a hospital. Mixed feelings. Hopefully first of many. In a nice recovery milestone, during the week I've been working on a small improvement to caching for the website to improve…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/b5392b1f-fe08-42dc-93c8-e01ec8a052d5?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/b5392b1f-fe08-42dc-93c8-e01ec8a052d5</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 23:56:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;F﻿irst week all year not involving time in a hospital. Mixed feelings. Hopefully first of many.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a nice recovery milestone, during the week I&apos;ve been working on a small improvement to caching for the website to improve the durability and predictability of article pages, which I&apos;m hoping to start testing over the next week or so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.londonwinterrun.co.uk/news/2023-london-route-revealed/&quot;&gt;that race I signed up for&lt;/a&gt;?  Today was race day.  The running group invited me to join them for food, but I couldn&apos;t quite stomach it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although I did end up eating out a lot this week: &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/PK8JvUoKJSgTZ3Z28&quot;&gt;Champor-Champor&lt;/a&gt; served up the best Massaman curry I&apos;ve ever tasted, &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/k4CrU1NUSqso4jgE7&quot;&gt;Taro Pimlico&lt;/a&gt;&apos;s miso soup stole the show &amp;amp; Wagamama&apos;s new billing system is a kafkaesque nightmare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Never thought I&apos;d say this: I miss cardio.  Weirdly, I don&apos;t miss booze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt10986410/&quot;&gt;Ted Lasso&lt;/a&gt; is abnormally good and I&apos;m highly disappointed it took me so long to discover. &lt;em&gt;“Beard After Hours”&lt;/em&gt; hit hard. Thanks &lt;a href=&quot;https://thegadhian.com/&quot;&gt;Arjun&lt;/a&gt; for nudging me to push through the pilot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/b5392b1f-fe08-42dc-93c8-e01ec8a052d5?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: A-Nick-ating — Week 4, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week I properly started on my next big assignment, which is to refine and improve how visual and data stories are produced.  It's slightly messy (and big) work since it fits between several teams, but I'm already…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/a95f0389-50ab-4fc4-9d67-1da093a0b5cd?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/a95f0389-50ab-4fc4-9d67-1da093a0b5cd</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 14:03:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week I properly started on my next big assignment, which is to refine and improve how visual and data stories are produced.  It&apos;s slightly messy (and big) work since it fits between several teams, but I&apos;m already seeing major opportunities to make things significantly better - and am thrilled to have a brand new problem space to explore.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nickramsbottom.com/&quot;&gt;Nick&lt;/a&gt; left the FT this week, and given the chance to say a few words during his goodbye so I plugged a few anecdotes into ChatGPT. &lt;a href=&quot;https://gist.github.com/alexwilson/7b0d9b1a68a7d25ee7191f8be354f3c1&quot;&gt;The resulting speech&lt;/a&gt; was surprisingly good and got a few laughs.  However it really started to struggle when I asked it to generate actual humour.  &quot;A-Nick-ating&quot; was its idea of a pun and I still don&apos;t understand it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promotions round is done: Phew.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Friday afternoon we ran a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goosechase.com/&quot;&gt;Goose chase&lt;/a&gt; at work.  Our team started out strong and we stayed tied first right up until the final mission, where not even Tobias&apos;s epic sprint to the final spot could hold our lead against &lt;a href=&quot;https://ghost.computer/&quot;&gt;Kara&lt;/a&gt;.  We ended in third place.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thursday morning I had…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/a95f0389-50ab-4fc4-9d67-1da093a0b5cd?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Diagnosing — Week 3, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reader, this week I learned why you never put a cannula in your dominant arm.  You become hyper-aware of every movement you make.  It's really quite unpleasant. My sister stayed the weekend as part of a London-based…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/e368eb5e-c9c5-4482-bf10-1161dd27982f?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/e368eb5e-c9c5-4482-bf10-1161dd27982f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 23:42:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reader, this week I learned why you &lt;strong&gt;never&lt;/strong&gt; put a cannula in your dominant arm.  You become hyper-aware of every movement you make.  It&apos;s really quite unpleasant.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My sister stayed the weekend as part of a London-based training course she&apos;s doing, and the timing ended up being excellent given the main event this week.  We ate Korean and talked about Pokémon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Following the trail of my spooky symptoms, I went back to the ER mid-week and spent some time in hospital going through a litany of tests.  And I finally have walked out with a diagnosis &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; a treatment plan which I won&apos;t talk about much yet.  But importantly, the anxiety is waning.  And once again I can only thank the NHS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know &lt;a href=&quot;https://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/IOweYouMyLife&quot;&gt;that trope&lt;/a&gt; where Alice saves Bob&apos;s life, and Bob acts super weird about being indebted to Alice?  I used to dismiss it as being a weird little story device, but I now understand it, and it just about brings me to tears. There is a particular doctor who listened, took me seriously, popped by to check on me…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/e368eb5e-c9c5-4482-bf10-1161dd27982f?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Recovering — Week 2, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Iconic week. Real highlight was a team lunch on Monday, welcoming George to our team. I quietly made a real mess of some grilled king prawns and failed to hide the evidence. We all had affogato for dessert and talked…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/634aa88d-fbe5-411e-8121-5f561ef1b0da?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/634aa88d-fbe5-411e-8121-5f561ef1b0da</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 22:30:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Iconic week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Real highlight was a team &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linastores.co.uk/&quot;&gt;lunch&lt;/a&gt; on Monday, welcoming &lt;a href=&quot;https://georgecrawford.com/&quot;&gt;George&lt;/a&gt; to our team. I quietly made a real mess of some grilled king prawns and failed to hide the evidence. We all had affogato for dessert and talked about music notation. Welcome George!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Slightly bittersweet, this was my last week as acting tech director of FT.com: reflections on that as part of 2022 review ... &lt;em&gt;eventually&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shorter notes again this week: I&apos;ve spent a lot of it recovering. This thing hit me hard. I&apos;m glad that the NHS was there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The uncertainty of my symptoms led to something of an anxiety tailspin this week. It got &lt;em&gt;spookier&lt;/em&gt;. And while I&apos;m feeling far better now, this kind of thing is scary and can come on fast so - reminder that mental health is no joke.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And did you know anxiety affects blood pressure?  I&apos;ve seen the numbers, it&apos;s no joke.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alongside one therapy referral, I&apos;m going through a slew of long-overdue tests with my GP.  In some countries there are annual physicals: For peace of mind I sorta…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/634aa88d-fbe5-411e-8121-5f561ef1b0da?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Rotating — Week 1, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Back at work this week, kinda. With difficulties in getting around by train, I've been working remotely from assorted Birmingham coffee shops.  Last time I did this was apparently December 2019! The CircleCI breach and…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/b78950bb-7dd6-4105-8515-8aba543e0b2e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/b78950bb-7dd6-4105-8515-8aba543e0b2e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 20:30:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Back at work this week, kinda. With difficulties in getting around by train, I&apos;ve been working remotely from assorted Birmingham coffee shops.  Last time I did this was apparently December 2019!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://circleci.com/blog/january-4-2023-security-alert/&quot;&gt;CircleCI breach&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lastpass.com/2022/12/notice-of-recent-security-incident/&quot;&gt;ever-worsening LastPass breach&lt;/a&gt; are a slightly disturbing trend, eh?  Starting to think that putting secrets in the cloud was never a good idea.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In very related news, the buzz-word of the week is rotating.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short notes this week: During a run I developed some spooky symptoms which ended up with me in the ER - the conclusion is a particularly nasty migraine. Genuinely freaked out by this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Also had some coursework deadlines on Monday, but since I let them know about the migraine, UoL have been kind enough to grant me an extra week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/b78950bb-7dd6-4105-8515-8aba543e0b2e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Decompressing — 1st January 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Happy new year!  Year of the Water Rabbit (after LNY) and hope. For the past few New Years celebrations I've been doing the science and running the numbers.  Now I can conclude beyond a shadow of a doubt that the…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/4fbaddf0-e66c-4ad1-b2dd-180bd1101791?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/4fbaddf0-e66c-4ad1-b2dd-180bd1101791</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 21:16:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Happy new year!  Year of the Water Rabbit (after LNY) and hope.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For the past few New Years celebrations I&apos;ve been doing the science and running the numbers.  Now I can conclude &lt;em&gt;beyond a shadow of a doubt&lt;/em&gt; that the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0126162/&quot;&gt;Hootenanny&lt;/a&gt; is the optimal British New Years Eve experience.  Nothing else comes close.  Even if it isn&apos;t live.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the run up to 2023 and the process of introspecting and writing-up 2022, I ended up throwing out any intention or ambition to get anything done and have been decompressing all week.  Take breaks, kids, they&apos;re important.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Man, PC gaming really never dried up did it?  Doing &lt;em&gt;nothing&lt;/em&gt; also meant making a small dent into my infamous Steam backlog.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Years Eve itself ended up being a rather wholesome affair: Last minute changes (for me, barely sleeping on the 30th and not facing hours of packing, travelling, unpacking, travelling &lt;em&gt;again&lt;/em&gt;, ugh) meant a smaller family celebration and an emergency trip to procure champagne, including a first for me - group video-calling…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/4fbaddf0-e66c-4ad1-b2dd-180bd1101791?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Celebrating — 25th December 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Happy holidays folks!  (メリークリ！) The stars aligned and I got to spend Christmas in Birmingham with family.  After unpleasant surprises in 2020 and 2021, this has been a welcome hit of nostalgia and tradition.  And too…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/6f2c2faa-cc8d-4c83-b2e4-048d5d893a27?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/6f2c2faa-cc8d-4c83-b2e4-048d5d893a27</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 23:07:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Happy holidays folks!  (メリークリ！)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The stars aligned and I got to spend Christmas in Birmingham with family.  After unpleasant surprises in 2020 and 2021, this has been a welcome hit of nostalgia and tradition.  And too much food.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But reader, it wasn&apos;t looking good.  I had a killer start to the winter break.  Instead of drinking cocktails and making music, I was confined to my sofa in with a rather unpleasant bug.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whilst recovering, I diagnosed &amp;amp; fixed a &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; annoying random iOS Slack crash. Using iOS kernel logs &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://mitmproxy.org/&quot;&gt;mitmproxy&lt;/a&gt; I linked an API payload to a memory leak, so I fixed the data (for me) and now have a ticket for Slack to patch the underlying bug.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.analogue.co/pocket&quot;&gt;Analogue Pocket&lt;/a&gt; pre-order finally arrived.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metroid_Fusion&quot;&gt;Metroid Fusion&lt;/a&gt; with the original GBA display mode is so much more atmospheric and moody than on an SP or emulator (and I set an any% PB of 1:43).  But the star of the show is native SNES on openFPGA, meaning, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_Metroid&quot;&gt;Super Metroid&lt;/a&gt; on the go&lt;/strong&gt; - but like - &lt;em&gt;actually Super Metroid and not a laggy emulator&lt;/em&gt;.  I love this so…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/6f2c2faa-cc8d-4c83-b2e4-048d5d893a27?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>