<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 07:06:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Mealdealing — Week 26, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gosh it’s been hot this week. So hot it’s hard to sleep. Went to a comedy course on Monday and have ended up on a TikTok.  Dissecting jokes is good fun, the homework includes looking at different techniques - this week…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/2316421a-4edc-43cd-b983-70e1c9553bf4?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/2316421a-4edc-43cd-b983-70e1c9553bf4</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 19:45:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gosh it’s been hot this week. So hot it’s hard to sleep.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went to a comedy course on Monday and have ended up on a TikTok.  Dissecting jokes is good fun, the homework includes looking at different techniques - this week was lists.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not one but two leaving drinks this week.  Apparently my Sainsbury’s meal-deal of choice (Southern Chicken Wrap, Yoghurt &amp;amp; Coconut Water) is low-tier.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Got into a small war with UberEats over a missing latte and some chicken selects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having installed Ableton on this computer, I’ve been learning more about how synthesis works instead of working on any of my existing tracks. Recently I’ve been focussing on FM synthesis. Maybe a good goal is to write some visual explainer posts?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of my slow-burn side NLP projects has been to vectorise and classify the contents of this blog, and I spent a decent chunk of the weekend working on that.  After talking about it for two years, I finally strung together several parametized Jupiter notebooks with &lt;a href=&quot;https://papermill.readthedocs.io/&quot;&gt;Papermill&lt;/a&gt; - all orchestrated with &lt;a href=&quot;https://metaflow.org/&quot;&gt;Metaflow&lt;/a&gt; - and it works so well that it feels like magic.  Lovely MLOps stack.  Hopefully…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2316421a-4edc-43cd-b983-70e1c9553bf4?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Fargo — Week 25, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week was marked by the duality of my team’s quarterly planning day and my department’s yearly rounders outing. Had a real blast at both seeing and chatting with people who I don’t normally get the chance to. During…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/62be874e-baab-4159-913f-924fb5f701dc?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/62be874e-baab-4159-913f-924fb5f701dc</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 21:06:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week was marked by the duality of my team’s quarterly planning day and my department’s yearly rounders outing. Had a real blast at both seeing and chatting with people who I don’t normally get the chance to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;During rounders we incepted everybody to skip going to the normal pub in favour of one far more accessible and public transport friendly. Despite a brazen bag theft, it went well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dealt with an outage where, even after restoring service, labelling the exact root cause proved tricky: It was compounded and began in a different part of the organisation. How it spread was the interesting factor, and I’m really looking forward to the retrospective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sanshinkai.uk/okinawa-day/&quot;&gt;Okinawa day&lt;/a&gt; was the closest thing I’ve seen to a Japanese festival in London. Lots of elated folk singing/dancing and a solid selection of snacks from the area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt14914430/&quot;&gt;Unfrosted&lt;/a&gt; was pretty damn funny. That Seinfeld guy could be a star.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doctor Who season finale was &lt;em&gt;good&lt;/em&gt;, but, felt rushed? Lots of things happened quickly, and they &lt;a href=&quot;https://x.com/jblacksomething/status/1804526773964575025&quot;&gt;didn’t all add up&lt;/a&gt;. I’m still hooked — but I feel like I did after…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/62be874e-baab-4159-913f-924fb5f701dc?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: The Italian Job — Week 24, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Theseus’s paradox poses the question: If you take a classic dish and substitute every major ingredient, is it the same classic dish, or is it something entirely new?  Call in now with your answers. Whirlwind week.  Got a…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c174a153-55ca-4c15-a123-84c65b781ebd?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c174a153-55ca-4c15-a123-84c65b781ebd</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 22:06:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Theseus’s paradox poses the question: If you take a classic dish and substitute every major ingredient, is it the same classic dish, or is it something entirely new?  Call in now with your answers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whirlwind week.  Got a lot done towards reliability and enjoyed getting into the details of some new technical problems.  My “there’s a debate l8r!” reminder posts have also become a meme. :(&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some very positive (and kind) unexpected feedback threw me this week because of the perspective it prompted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://innervisionsalchemy.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Innervisions Alchemy&lt;/a&gt; is a new wellness space in Bermondsey and to fundraise they’re collaborating with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.community-sauna.co.uk/community-sauna-network&quot;&gt;Community Sauna Network&lt;/a&gt;. Went there on Thursday after work and had a blast. English summer in 2024 - it turns out - makes for perfect sauna weather.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My albatross is still there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apparently M &amp;amp; I are trendsetters? That’s what a popular instagram account said - and it’s on the internet so it must be true.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Saw &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/paranoidlondon&quot;&gt;Paranoid London&lt;/a&gt; on Saturday, outdoors in the pouring rain. The event ran between 12 to 9, and the other DJs who played were &lt;em&gt;alright&lt;/em&gt;, but a little ambient/house-y for the mood I was in.  My namesake (&lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/pato&quot;&gt;Pato&lt;/a&gt;) dropped a few bangers.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/stories/highlights/17981840663540013/&quot;&gt;All worth it for that acid-heavy Paranoid London goodness&lt;/a&gt;.  Wore hearing protection &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ae6b20c6-751b-4ce9-8a73-78328483d403/&quot;&gt;this time&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c174a153-55ca-4c15-a123-84c65b781ebd?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Hopping — Week 23, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[EU Election has turned out interesting, huh? New election just dropped. Spent Tuesday’s leaders debate looking at some dashboards. Understanding how a timeseries is derived is a lot more exciting than hearing soundbite…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/977a1af3-f0a2-4ee2-8591-278fbace8d8e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/977a1af3-f0a2-4ee2-8591-278fbace8d8e</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 21:55:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EU Election has turned out interesting, huh? New election just dropped.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spent Tuesday’s leaders debate looking at some dashboards. Understanding how a timeseries is derived is a lot more exciting than hearing soundbite after soundbite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A decent chunk of my spare time this week has gone into the haunted forest that is design-decisions in my blog. Like the typography.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week I’ve also been migrating my collection of music production tools from my old laptop to the laptop I bought at the start of the year. I couldn’t get my old recording setup to work, so I built a new one using &lt;a href=&quot;https://rogueamoeba.com/loopback/&quot;&gt;Loopback&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://rogueamoeba.com/audiohijack/&quot;&gt;Audio Hijack&lt;/a&gt; - and it supports broadcasting!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Testing the new setup (and having really enjoyed it last week) &lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/axwnmusic/2024-06-03-set&quot;&gt;I played some music pretty fast&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ended a night of Clapham bar-hopping in Phonox. Their DJ booth is &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; impressive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/977a1af3-f0a2-4ee2-8591-278fbace8d8e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Adjourning — Week 22, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Theme of the (short) week has been site reliability. Things I have learned include that all reliability metrics (including nines!) are actually probabilities - which makes perfect sense, because if we could predict…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/3deb1186-8da7-454c-83de-b8da74f18cc9?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/3deb1186-8da7-454c-83de-b8da74f18cc9</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:39:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Theme of the (short) week has been site reliability. Things I have learned include that all reliability metrics (including nines!) are actually probabilities - which makes perfect sense, because if we could predict service disruptions we wouldn’t have them!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bank Holiday Monday marked a long, late rodizio lunch which was delightful. I ate so much cassava and vinaigrette.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt14164730/&quot;&gt;Dexter: New Blood&lt;/a&gt; is a great continuation/retelling of Dexter’s finale, and I’m really enjoying watching it &lt;em&gt;slowly&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;StormBit, an IRC network and project that I’ve been involved with since 2010, &lt;a href=&quot;https://stormbit.net/2024/06/01/stormbit-has-shut-down.html&quot;&gt;has now shut down&lt;/a&gt;. It’s an emotional moment - saying goodbye to any part of your identity is hard - but it was the right call.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My DJ sets are now a podcast. Eventually I’ll add a section to this site with links to it on distribution channels, but you can find it on &lt;a href=&quot;https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/id1748671352&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pca.st/gt90ppa7&quot;&gt;Pocket Casts&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLSFadn3DomKkeT6UlRvQZ6nlsBAXhYa0u&quot;&gt;Google YouTube Music&lt;/a&gt; (and probably whatever you use). My rationale is that my music project &lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/axwnmusic&quot;&gt;AXWN&lt;/a&gt;, has always been about spinning music as well as making it. &lt;a href=&quot;https://feeds.feedburner.com/axwn/axons&quot;&gt;RSS feed here&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/3deb1186-8da7-454c-83de-b8da74f18cc9?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Reducing — Week 21, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[New UK General Election just dropped: It heralds a slightly busier (and  dare I say exciting?!) period at work, and my priorities have shifted towards reliability. Went sauna for the first time in the UK. Slightly hotter…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c2e7175d-a995-4dba-8574-539ef62c3fcd?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c2e7175d-a995-4dba-8574-539ef62c3fcd</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 22:35:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New UK General Election just dropped: It heralds a slightly busier (and  dare I say exciting?!) period at work, and my priorities have shifted towards reliability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went sauna for the first time in the UK. Slightly hotter than those in Germany and without any Aufguss – which I’ve realised are my favourite part — but it still slaps and for a day after my skin felt incredible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Friday, I tagged along with Joel to see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.southampton.ac.uk/~lac/Comedy/CarrCrash/&quot;&gt;Carr Crash&lt;/a&gt; in the Vault bar at Kings. Leslie and Ruby were hilarious and high energy, genuinely a pleasure to experience. And academic hecklers are an &lt;em&gt;experience&lt;/em&gt;. Got lost trying to leave after: Bush House is a maze! &lt;a href=&quot;https://tickets.edfringe.com/whats-on/ruby-carr-ebae&quot;&gt;Go watch Ruby talk about eBay at the fringe&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recently started a co-op campaign of Borderlands 3 with L. I have a real love-hate relationship with the series, because in each instalment it feels like the writing and gameplay design are trying far too hard to eclipse the original. That being said, the everything about &lt;a href=&quot;https://borderlands.fandom.com/wiki/Lectra_City&quot;&gt;Lectra City&lt;/a&gt; was hilarious and we couldn’t…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c2e7175d-a995-4dba-8574-539ef62c3fcd?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Antennae — Week 20, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[What happens when a bunch of Japanophiles, most of whom have lived or stayed in Japan for longer than a holiday, go to the best Okonomiyaki place in London? Awkwardly specific questions to staff, that’s what. No folks…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c96ebdb3-5f73-4cc8-8ea0-6bdec2a0c6cc?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c96ebdb3-5f73-4cc8-8ea0-6bdec2a0c6cc</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 22:51:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What happens when a bunch of Japanophiles, most of whom have lived or stayed in Japan for longer than a holiday, go to the best Okonomiyaki place in London? Awkwardly specific questions to staff, that’s what. No folks, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.abeno.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Abeno&lt;/a&gt; don’t do monja. They &lt;strong&gt;do&lt;/strong&gt; do great highballs though.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In a world of component libraries, what even is a design system?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Caught up with OB at the Euston Tap, and immediately we made a mistake by going for a La Chouffe. Not designed for a pint-glass.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Picked up a new &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.hermanmiller.com/home-desk-accessories/oripura-laptop-stand/2532890.html&quot;&gt;fold-flat laptop stand from Colebrook Boston Saunders&lt;/a&gt; which pairs great with the ThinkPad Bluetooth keyboard. Game-changer for being able to work in weird places. Looks good too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Saturday I threw a birthday shindig starting in Spitalfields and ending in the Blind Beggar with some of my favourite people. You know who you are, thanks for coming!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The joy of living in South West London is not visiting any other parts of South West London because the transport links are pants, so on Sunday I found &lt;a href=&quot;https://nickramsbottom.com/&quot;&gt;Nick&lt;/a&gt; in a pub in Tooting, and joined a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.strava.com/activities/11450278100&quot;&gt;capital ring walking group heading to Crystal Palace&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c96ebdb3-5f73-4cc8-8ea0-6bdec2a0c6cc?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Dizzy — Week 19, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Holiday this week, originally the plan was to go to Mälmo to the Eurovision semifinal - but that didn’t happen for a few reasons. Monday marked my birthday, which was a pretty relaxed affair. Had a nice lunch (Nanban…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/88372de1-9bd8-458a-9e32-5af232dd05e2?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/88372de1-9bd8-458a-9e32-5af232dd05e2</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:28:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Holiday this week, originally the plan was to go to Mälmo to the Eurovision semifinal - but that didn’t happen for a few reasons.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monday marked my birthday, which was a pretty relaxed affair. Had a nice lunch (Nanban!? In the UK!?) followed by some cake. I got a watch and a sketchpad, as well as far too many kind messages to reply to in any decent time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Tuesday I walked through Wimbledon, and was wired up to a 5-lead EKG for a 24-hour test. You wear it around your neck, and it continuously monitors the electrical activity in your heart. It’s odd wearing all these cables on your chest, amongst other things you hope you’re not sending scary vibes. It’s probably the closest I will ever come to wearing a wire.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The follow-up appointment happened on Saturday and I got the all-clear. Major relief, although in the future I’ll check-in just to be sure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pub quiz at the George &amp;amp; Vulture: Our team was on fire, and I was uncharacteristically in flow and had tonnes of answers which were almost…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/88372de1-9bd8-458a-9e32-5af232dd05e2?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Beating — Week 18, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[During a lull at my local polling station I cast all my votes for the London local elections (all for labour this round). Satisfying seeing the conservatives lose lots of seats as the votes came in, although I will miss…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c5810871-c4b7-4148-8835-050657185a56?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c5810871-c4b7-4148-8835-050657185a56</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 20:49:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;During a lull at my local polling station I cast all my votes for the London local elections (all for labour this round). Satisfying seeing the conservatives lose lots of seats as the votes came in, although I will miss hearing from Andy Street.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have put Rust on hold.  For now!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visited Chinatown with L, and did an almost complete inventory of the restaurants. Ended up going to the bao place that isn’t on Google Maps, followed by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.taiyakiya.co.uk/&quot;&gt;taiyakiya&lt;/a&gt;. I highly recommend both.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Popped by the Market Porter briefly to say goodbye to Carina (and share some Japan travel tips), and to say hello to some of the rest of the team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First time back in the office for a little while. I got a bowl of soup. Everybody should have easy access to soup. Very quiet - I think the aforementioned leaving drinks went well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kept up the Persian food streak by going to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ariana-order.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Ariana&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prompted by last week’s health scare (and slow NHS waiting times), I saw a cardiologist on Saturday, where someone did an ultrasound on my heart…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c5810871-c4b7-4148-8835-050657185a56?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Flooding — Week 17, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[This wasn’t the most productive of weeks. Update: the beard has left the building. Asking “How many emails did I miss?” is a bit like asking “How long is a piece of string?”. Nobody can really know. Thanks to a brand new…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/af1559dc-0305-4c32-960c-a53d0e08881e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/af1559dc-0305-4c32-960c-a53d0e08881e</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 19:18:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This wasn’t the most productive of weeks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/e8403728-ba79-4750-914f-811999b74ab3&quot;&gt;Update: the beard has left the building&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Asking “How many emails did I miss?” is a bit like asking “How long is a piece of string?”. Nobody can really know.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thanks to a brand new exciting health-scare I spent another night in the ER, where I witnessed many exciting things including the entire ER waiting room flooding. Several tests later (including my first ever x-ray!) at 6AM, I stumbled into a taxi, made a hasty hot chocolate and collapsed into bed.  Totally wrecked that day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visited the one-and-only CG in Leighton Buzzard to catch-up on puns, grumble about AI and to hike around the hills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Walking to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sinuherestaurant.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Sinuhe&lt;/a&gt; for dinner on Sunday, I realised that - indeed - Charing Cross hospital is my nearest.  I’ve been wrong the entire time I’ve lived in Putney, and maybe I would’ve been seen more quickly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oh well.  I got to share tasty Persian food.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/af1559dc-0305-4c32-960c-a53d0e08881e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>