<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:18:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Sand — Week 11, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Worked on an interesting problem over the week: How do you pragmatically iterate over a series without using loops/iterators/etc? The solution takes you back to fundamentals, and back to maths. Inductive proofs hold the…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/e8403728-ba79-4750-914f-811999b74ab3?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/e8403728-ba79-4750-914f-811999b74ab3</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 22:02:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked on an interesting problem over the week: How do you pragmatically iterate over a series without using loops/iterators/etc? The solution takes you back to fundamentals, and back to maths. Inductive proofs hold the answer. This was &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; energising.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blood tests now all done: My arm is very bruised.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Friday evening I watched &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt15239678&quot;&gt;Dune 2&lt;/a&gt; with MT and D. The final exclamation of “Lisan al Gaib!” had the whole cinema laughing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subsequently consumed the entire Dune cinematic universe (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0087182&quot;&gt;Dune 1984&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0142032&quot;&gt;Frank Herbert’s Dune&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0287839&quot;&gt;Children of Dune&lt;/a&gt;), and have now made a pact to read the books. I am &lt;em&gt;hooked&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Saturday brought a long-awaited outlet for Karaoke, and I was made to sing Rasputin: Starting to think that the beard has got to go. Highlights were watching Mike Ehrmantraut and Feyd-Rautha Harkonnen on the dancefloor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Closed the week with a nightmarish journey to Birmingham involving three train tickets and standing around on Euston’s concourse waiting for an announcement that never came.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/e8403728-ba79-4750-914f-811999b74ab3?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Pioneers — Week 10, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gladiators is really good. It’s just cheesy and fun. Mental health focus this week. Did you know people aren’t very happy in the UK? That’s why we need more things like Gladiators and fewer things like Saltburn. Major…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/ae6b20c6-751b-4ce9-8a73-78328483d403?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/ae6b20c6-751b-4ce9-8a73-78328483d403</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 22:02:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt27706924/&quot;&gt;Gladiators&lt;/a&gt; is really good. It’s just cheesy and &lt;em&gt;fun&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mental health focus this week. Did you know &lt;a href=&quot;https://mentalstateoftheworld.report/2023_read/&quot;&gt;people aren’t very happy in the UK&lt;/a&gt;? That’s why we &lt;em&gt;need&lt;/em&gt; more things like Gladiators and fewer things like Saltburn.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Major highlight was wolfing down a triple-roast rice (三寶飯) and smuggling in a 7 day supply of flucloxacillin into Fabric to watch Paranoid London. I think this makes me cool? Maybe?  (to be clear, it was a prescription to clear up a scary infection. so perhaps not cool.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paranoid London were playing their new album live, &lt;a href=&quot;https://paranoid-london.bandcamp.com/album/arseholes-liars-and-electronic-pioneers&quot;&gt;which is fantastic&lt;/a&gt;. Lots of synth equipment on stage and the vocalists joined live. My fave track was Fields of Fire.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Played through, and beat &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.metacritic.com/game/paradise-killer/&quot;&gt;Paradise Killer&lt;/a&gt; over the course of the week. Loved it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had a much-delayed appointment with a geneticist this week, which involved a full family medical history and a physical exam. Ruled out for the obvious stuff which is good, but I now have a hot date with a phlebotomist: Yay.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not for anything serious I’m also back in the neurology sphere of interest which means I can look forward to yet another &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/neurological-exam&quot;&gt;neuroexam&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ae6b20c6-751b-4ce9-8a73-78328483d403?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Wisdom — Week 9, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Happy Leap Day week! Did you know babies born on February 29th are called Leapers or Leaplings? Birmingham’s busses were fitted in the late 2000s with screens showing announcements, advertisements and a quote of the day…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/bc8cad80-18ff-44f0-9599-fa5bf485fdb8?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/bc8cad80-18ff-44f0-9599-fa5bf485fdb8</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 22:48:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Happy Leap Day week! Did you know babies born on February 29th are called Leapers or Leaplings?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Birmingham’s busses were fitted in the late 2000s with screens showing announcements, advertisements and a quote of the day. There were some real zingers on show, but only one stood out. Coming home one day I saw Miles Kington’s infamous line: “Knowledge is knowing that a tomato is a fruit; Wisdom is not putting it in a fruit salad”. In that moment I realised the difference.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Years later, with these words still echoing in my head, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodreads.com/review/list/90636253?shelf=read&quot;&gt;I still over-index on knowledge&lt;/a&gt; over wisdom. I don’t really know why. Maybe it’s impatience? Wisdom happens over time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thematically, but definitely unrelatedly, Pinto’s Beans didn’t win the quiz this time. I can’t believe none of us could identify the Grand Designs theme tune.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoyed walking up Chapel Market.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The weekend was a bit of a blur really: I walked around SE London a bit, and impulse bought books of short stories in Russian and Japanese to sharpen my…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/bc8cad80-18ff-44f0-9599-fa5bf485fdb8?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Reclining — Week 8, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Got to play an early preview of Chroma Arcana, and it is wholeheartedly a lot of fun. Very quick, and I picked up the rules with hopefully not too much explaining. Did you know the Seahorse does Karaoke? After getting a…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/580545ab-a50f-47bb-ada9-095953c0ef87?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/580545ab-a50f-47bb-ada9-095953c0ef87</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 22:10:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Got to play an early preview of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/rocnest/chroma-arcana&quot;&gt;Chroma Arcana&lt;/a&gt;, and it is wholeheartedly a lot of fun. Very quick, and I picked up the rules with hopefully not too much explaining.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did you know the Seahorse does Karaoke?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After getting a strong recommendation, I watched &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt17351924/&quot;&gt;Saltburn&lt;/a&gt; on the way home: I have many opinions, but one thing is fact: Sophie Ellis-Bextor is back in &lt;em&gt;style&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shout out to the MVP of the week: FS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ImageCDN is now on Fastify and uses origin based rate-limiting. It took me about 3 hours from upgrading Node and refactoring everything, load-testing in a new pre-production environment and then finally tuning parameters in production. Memory usage is now at an all-time low, and RPS at an all-time high.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeping the momentum going, I then bumped the Enable Github Automerge Action to run on Node 20 - with two major releases: &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/alexwilson/enable-github-automerge-action/releases/tag/1.1.0&quot;&gt;1.1.0&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/alexwilson/enable-github-automerge-action/releases/tag/2.0.0&quot;&gt;2.0.0&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped a friend out with sofa shopping at the weekend, where I discovered Cinemax offer &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.furniturevillage.co.uk/cinemax-media-2-seater-fabric-power-recliner-sofa-with-power-headrests/ZFRSP000000000054895.html&quot;&gt;a sofa version of the reclining seats in cinemas&lt;/a&gt;. I have never…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/580545ab-a50f-47bb-ada9-095953c0ef87?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Soup — Week 7, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bust out the Fexofenadine, Spring is here early and with it - seasonal allergies are back. Took one on Monday and it nearly conked me out, but by Tuesday I was feeling myself again. Bought a 6 month supply, which seems…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/0b698eb1-5c8a-465d-b8aa-154143decbb1?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/0b698eb1-5c8a-465d-b8aa-154143decbb1</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 18:11:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bust out the Fexofenadine, Spring is here early and with it - seasonal allergies are back. Took one on Monday and it nearly conked me out, but by Tuesday I was feeling myself again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bought a 6 month supply, which seems surprisingly forward thinking. It’s very annoying to need it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; soup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aren&apos;t we all just electrical impulses in brined bundles of fibres?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There are only two occasions where I&apos;ll wait in line in the rain: To get into a (good) restaurant, or, to get into a (good) club. Flea markets in multistory carparks are neither of these things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://jamesshelley.com/blog/writing-on-the-internet.html&quot;&gt;What&apos;s the fun of writing on the Internet anymore?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Closed the week at Shoryu with D. Very good.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/0b698eb1-5c8a-465d-b8aa-154143decbb1?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Singing — Week 6, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Spent all week hyping myself up for karaoke. Dorstone is a wonderful cheese.  Probably the fastest I will ever go from trying to buying. Managed ~40000 steps between the assorted markets of East London. The last time I…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/b770bf12-9bac-4b32-a0bb-1509be11adfc?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/b770bf12-9bac-4b32-a0bb-1509be11adfc</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 21:45:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spent all week hyping myself up for karaoke.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thecourtyarddairy.co.uk/blog/cheese-farm-producer-visits/what-makes-dorstone-goats-cheese-so-special/&quot;&gt;Dorstone&lt;/a&gt; is a wonderful cheese.  Probably the fastest I will ever go from trying to buying.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managed ~40000 steps between the assorted markets of East London.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The last time I ate cheese from a tube, it made me want to throw up - but at Scandi Kitchen I discovered Fjällbrynt Ädelost which is surprisingly really good.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This post brought to you by a successful mission to find Mooncakes in Chinatown. On the way there I saw a space dragon on the go, and we bumped into JB. Happy Lunar New Year folks!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Karaoke didn’t happen. :(&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/b770bf12-9bac-4b32-a0bb-1509be11adfc?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Jar, Bowl, Lantern — Week 5, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Our mark, let's call her “E”, doesn't know that this is a surprise birthday dinner.  Cake is in play.  We keep the conversation light in wait of the music.  One problem - the card is still blank!  So begins the great…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/19af7e7f-b357-4194-b1e1-d10b882825e4?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/19af7e7f-b357-4194-b1e1-d10b882825e4</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 22:51:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our mark, let&apos;s call her “E”, doesn&apos;t know that this is a surprise birthday dinner.  Cake is in play.  We keep the conversation light in wait of the music.  One problem - &lt;em&gt;the card is still blank!&lt;/em&gt;  So begins the great birthday card heist of &apos;24.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This was a Tanzwüste kinda week.  Melodic and cheerful.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wednesday evening was a real highlight.  I can only gush about how delightful it was and how delightful the crowd was, but that&apos;s not what you&apos;re here for so I&apos;ll gloss over that.  Thanks for organising, R!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Aren&apos;t we always heading to Paddington?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At the weekend I walked from Harrow to Hanwell to see parakeets and beavers, and then ran (aided by public transit) from Hanwell to Surrey Quays to drink caipirinhas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Imagine having to wear a straw hat in class, as part of your uniform.  Wild.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mHONNcZbwDY&quot;&gt;HELLO // IS IT ME YOU&apos;RE // LOOKING FOR&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;M dragged me along to a table tennis court: I walked in as an embarrassing beginner and walked out a teensy bit better.  I find it really hard to be bad at stuff like…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/19af7e7f-b357-4194-b1e1-d10b882825e4?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Stormy — Week 4, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Storms Isha and Jocelyn came to visit this week bringing high-speed gusts, a wave of train cancellations and the soothing wailing of wind passing through the rafters.  One problem - my apartment doesn't have any rafters…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/640c0929-9828-4369-862d-545fdee6d6ae?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/640c0929-9828-4369-862d-545fdee6d6ae</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 23:33:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Storms Isha and Jocelyn came to visit this week bringing high-speed gusts, a wave of train cancellations and the soothing wailing of wind passing through the rafters.  One problem - my apartment doesn&apos;t have any rafters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;That Don Clifton chap sure might have been onto something, eh?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;James recommended a new cheese: &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cabrales_cheese&quot;&gt;Cabrales&lt;/a&gt;.  It&apos;s blue, absolutely delicious, and maybe even a hint too sharp.  I ate a little before bed on Tuesday and had wonderfully bizarre dreams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One evening was spent watching cars trying to cram into a narrow passageway already packed with people.  First, Alex blocked them with some bikes.  That worked for a while.  Then I blocked them by moving a sign.  Turns out that many drivers are willing to disrupt tens of people in hope of a shortcut, but not a single two-foot-high wooden sandwich board.  Not sure how I feel about that, but it certainly doesn&apos;t motivate me to become a cyclist.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In even the dingiest of canteens, soup is always a joy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At the weekend I attempted to…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/640c0929-9828-4369-862d-545fdee6d6ae?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Meticulous — Week 3, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Each detail has been meticulously planned, every minute accounted for.  Nothing can go wrong.  It will all be OK.  But today is the big day and now it feels real: Really real.  Running a conference — seeing a room full…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/335131d2-edd3-4fc1-96da-e3aef0b5232d?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/335131d2-edd3-4fc1-96da-e3aef0b5232d</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 19:46:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each detail has been meticulously planned, every minute accounted for.  Nothing can go wrong.  It will all be OK.  But today is the big day and now it feels real: &lt;em&gt;Really&lt;/em&gt; real.  Running a conference — seeing a room full of people and the more on the livestream — you can&apos;t help but think about how any mistake will waste everyone&apos;s time.  It&apos;s heavy.  Maybe that&apos;s healthy.  But do your job and it will all be OK.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Notwithstanding me being on the organising committee, EngineRoom - FT&apos;s internal tech conference - ran relatively smoothly and to some pretty kind feedback (so far).  We had guests from our sister and parent companies, and it&apos;s delightful seeing brand new bridges being built in real time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great talks throughout with several standouts — in particular I really enjoyed learning all about &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/andygout/theatrebase-api&quot;&gt;modelling the complicated world of theatre in a graph&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I took a more operational role on the day since there were lots of tiny things going slightly awry, ranging from reconfiguring AV and trying to…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/335131d2-edd3-4fc1-96da-e3aef0b5232d?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Sprinting — Week 2, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[In Zeno's paradox of Achilles and the Tortoise, it's impossible for Achilles to catch-up with the Tortoise because the Tortoise is always ⅒ of the distance ahead of Achilles. It makes perfect sense because there'll…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/8dc5fbfe-cf65-4a16-9b2b-4e50eb07cbd9?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/8dc5fbfe-cf65-4a16-9b2b-4e50eb07cbd9</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 22:27:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In Zeno&apos;s paradox of &lt;a href=&quot;https://personal.lse.ac.uk/robert49/ebooks/philsciadventures/lecture24.html&quot;&gt;Achilles and the Tortoise&lt;/a&gt;, it&apos;s impossible for Achilles to catch-up with the Tortoise because the Tortoise is always ⅒ of the distance ahead of Achilles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It makes perfect sense because there&apos;ll always be an infinitesimally small distance between them, however, &lt;em&gt;unfortunately&lt;/em&gt; in reality the laws of physics exist and also we don&apos;t live inside a maths puzzle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Starting back at work this week, a week after everyone else, in many ways I felt like Achilles — not only because I could not catch-up with everyone else&apos;s head-start — but also because I hurt my foot and I&apos;m pretty sure that&apos;s what he was famous for.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But I have caught up now, though, at least enough to have found this silly metaphor for the second week of the year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New year, new calendar: I am trying out time-blocking (the old fashioned way, without any fancy apps) to focus on specific tasks.  Specifically taking some time and saying, &quot;OK NOW WE WILL FOCUS ON X&quot; is just intrinsically motivating.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoyed watching…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/8dc5fbfe-cf65-4a16-9b2b-4e50eb07cbd9?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>