<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 04:59:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Sunrising — 9th October 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[There's something quite magical about watching the sunrise from an airport lounge.  It brings a kind-of existential clarity to your priorities and your life.  The (usually) sleepless night before really helps in setting…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/8e4c8a4b-0f13-4665-9e22-e08ac1657b15?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/8e4c8a4b-0f13-4665-9e22-e08ac1657b15</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 05:59:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There&apos;s something quite magical about watching the sunrise from an airport lounge.  It brings a kind-of existential clarity to your priorities and your life.  The (usually) sleepless night before really helps in setting the mood to answer such difficult questions as “What am I even doing with my life?”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It was beautiful though.  Wish you could have seen it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week was largely spent in spreadsheets, changing (&lt;em&gt;occasionally&lt;/em&gt; moving) cells.  And then speaking to people about the changes.  I also spent some time doing some targeted deep-dives into our tech-stack, to look at personalisation and caching logic.  A pull-request may have been produced, and subsequently rejected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;M﻿y new vice this week is sudoku.  I reinstalled &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.playgoodsudoku.com/&quot;&gt;Good Sudoku&lt;/a&gt; while watching the final season of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt7016936/&quot;&gt;Killing Eve&lt;/a&gt;, and then a day later caught myself doing one during a slightly more talk-y meeting.  According to screentime I have over 24 hours in-game.  &lt;em&gt;Yikes&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;R﻿eally disappointed at where Killing Eve went BTW.  Not sure…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/8e4c8a4b-0f13-4665-9e22-e08ac1657b15?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Anecdotalizing — 2nd October 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Working for a newspaper, it's impossible not to feel connected to the news.  But with Skandal! on everybody's lips this week, that connection feels more real than ever.  In many ways it's exciting being on the periphery…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/2f9fe94e-668a-4ce7-bbc7-592ab21db0f1?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/2f9fe94e-668a-4ce7-bbc7-592ab21db0f1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 11:49:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working for a newspaper, it&apos;s impossible not to feel connected to the news.  But &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt21836620/&quot;&gt;with Skandal!&lt;/a&gt; on everybody&apos;s lips this week, that connection feels more real than ever.  In many ways it&apos;s exciting being on the periphery of this kind of work, holding so many to account.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generally excited right now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The UK economy, huh?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We had two fairly major (but brief) outages on the website this week.  One was caused by a recent breaking change within NodeJS and the other by an experimental feature-flag, both which slipped within our error boundaries.  On top of the excellent cooperation between teams, what was very exciting to see is how our &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/ft-product-technology/next-chapter-on-our-journey-to-achieve-and-maintain-operational-excellence-of-ft-com-7dd9c7871347&quot;&gt;recent focus on reliability&lt;/a&gt; allowed us to learn from both.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two more pumpkin-spices in btw.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For a few years, what has stopped me from getting a &lt;a href=&quot;https://remarkable.com/&quot;&gt;Remarkable&lt;/a&gt; is the lack of backlight and lack of Kindle support.  On Thursday everything changed with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aboutamazon.com/news/devices/amazon-announcing-kindle-scribe&quot;&gt;the Kindle Scribe announcement&lt;/a&gt;.  I&apos;m genuinely excited about this device: It&apos;s the e-ink tablet which genuinely does…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2f9fe94e-668a-4ce7-bbc7-592ab21db0f1?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Pumpkin Spice — 25th September 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reader, Autumn is here, marking the much-anticipated return of pumpkin spice.  While writing I'm drinking my first (and maybe last) latte and can already feel the power of being so, so basic surging through my veins. At…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/d60799c7-a664-4f25-974c-c36f17880854?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/d60799c7-a664-4f25-974c-c36f17880854</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 14:14:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reader, Autumn is here, marking the much-anticipated return of pumpkin spice.  While writing I&apos;m drinking my first (and maybe last) latte and can already feel the power of being so, so basic surging through my veins.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At work, more and more teams have begun blogging semi-regularly.  It&apos;s very energising reading about their progress (and I &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; the occasional deep-dives).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I upgraded to the iPhone 14 Pro, going for the smaller model after I found the 11 Pro Max a shade too big.  So far I&apos;m really enjoying it.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/08/iphone-14-pro-dynamic-island/&quot;&gt;Dynamic Island&lt;/a&gt; is a joy.   Unfortunately I have one gripe: The always-on screen is &lt;strong&gt;really&lt;/strong&gt; distracting, so, I&apos;ve started laying it upside down.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recently I finished watching &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt12851524/&quot;&gt;Only Murders in the Building&lt;/a&gt;.  Overwhelmingly wholesome.  Really just a treat from end-to-end.  Imagine being &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; into true-crime podcasts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A new term starts in a few weeks.  I&apos;m not ready.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week also &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-62920969&quot;&gt;marked a mini-budget in the UK&lt;/a&gt;, doubling-down on &quot;trickle-down&quot; economics.  Mostly I&apos;ve avoided writing…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/d60799c7-a664-4f25-974c-c36f17880854?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Lying — 18th September 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[It’s hard to say how long it’s been now. We lost the South Bank of the Thames to The Queue on Wednesday. Thursday we had The Queue contained to Southwark Park.  Sleep came easy that night. But somewhere along the way we…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/0d17eff9-a290-4381-8c22-feb75babeb3e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/0d17eff9-a290-4381-8c22-feb75babeb3e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 14:15:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s hard to say how long it’s been now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We lost the South Bank of the Thames to The Queue on Wednesday.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thursday we had The Queue contained to Southwark Park.  Sleep came easy that night.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But somewhere along the way we got cocky - containment failed.  The breach rapidly expanded north.  Green Park, St James&apos;s Park &amp;amp; Hyde Park Corner have all fallen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We think some famous footballer (from the 2000s) was involved in the containment breach: Anything for a knighthood.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Queue was five miles long before we lost the ability to measure it.  Our equipment doesn&apos;t work anymore.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s like 2020 all over again: Next week, we’re closing the shops, the schools and the encouraging people not to work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The republicans warned us.  We should have listened.  It may now be too late.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/0d17eff9-a290-4381-8c22-feb75babeb3e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Accessioning — 11th September 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[A lot has happened in the UK this week - we have a new prime minister, a new king - and - the queen passed away during the week.  The new people are where the title is from btw. Wishing I were on holiday. Still running…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c950ebe9-d857-4c5f-817a-8bc33aa9ac75?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c950ebe9-d857-4c5f-817a-8bc33aa9ac75</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 13:29:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A lot has happened in the UK this week - we have a new prime minister, a new king - and - the queen passed away during the week.  The new people are where the title is from btw.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wishing I were on holiday.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Still running!  Now with new shoes which I can’t decide if they’re too small or not.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I took off Wednesday afternoon for an exam which I estimated would take between 6 and 8 hours, but I finished in ~4.  So I went to a birthday party which with hindsight was a mistake.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Thursday I left the office at 6:15PM to join some people at a nearby pub, and around 6:30PM was back in the office in an incident room as we made tweaks to messaging on the site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An interesting thing about working at a newspaper is that we sort-of knew the news was coming. What confirmed it for me - wasn&apos;t the request we pause push-notifications, nor the rumours of notes being passed around the House of Commons. It was the building staff standing by to move our flags to half-mast.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crikey.  Editing the website isn’t…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c950ebe9-d857-4c5f-817a-8bc33aa9ac75?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Toting — 4th September 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reader, this week I’ve been engaged in battle with my bathroom sink: On the verge of calling in reinforcements (a plumber) I had a mild victory involving a plunger.  Now I know how the Daleks must feel. This was a…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/90ef6cce-d31a-4cac-8f61-98e4b48209c3?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/90ef6cce-d31a-4cac-8f61-98e4b48209c3</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 20:35:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reader, this week I’ve been engaged in battle with my bathroom sink: On the verge of calling in reinforcements (a plumber) I had a mild victory involving a plunger.  Now I know how the Daleks must feel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This was a shorter week at work and it felt pretty hefty at times, but already far better than last week.  Reflecting, something I need to do a lot more of is time-blocking: Some documents just need to be written.  It’s like being in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2022/08/26/15-tech-leaders-on-why-and-how-ctos-should-find-time-to-code/&quot;&gt;critical-path of code&lt;/a&gt;, only, without the code - and usually docs can’t “just” be passed onto someone else.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Wednesday, I went to an impromptu leaving drinks for a conspicuously-anonymous friend moving to NYC the next day.  Our small group merged with another and I left having had one of the top-ten strangest conversations of all time - and with a job offer for a non-existent company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My new mission is to make highballs happen because they’re more refreshing than beer, and make me look cooler than drinking wine.  If you hear me ordering “Whiskey…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/90ef6cce-d31a-4cac-8f61-98e4b48209c3?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Stacking — 28th August 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week I won at Calendar-Tetris, which is to say that I sat in a near-solid block of gatherings from Monday through to Friday. It hasn’t been quite that packed since 2020. New objective: Never let it quite get that…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/0f78ea83-2c98-464c-b6bf-59198e415dbe?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/0f78ea83-2c98-464c-b6bf-59198e415dbe</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 22:18:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week I won at Calendar-Tetris, which is to say that I sat in a near-solid block of gatherings from Monday through to Friday. It hasn’t been quite that packed since 2020. New objective: Never let it quite get that bad again - which probably means starting to do &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.rescuetime.com/time-blocking-101/&quot;&gt;time-blocking&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Wednesday lunchtime I learned something semi-secret which totally broke my brain. And I think I gave a slightly disastrous presso afterwards - although people were awfully nice about it. Spent the evening at one of London’s rare Izakayas eating okonomiyaki: They made a decent highball.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thursday evening involved product chatter and cocktails at a speakeasy - one of the few spaces in the City which isn’t always packed. They made a decent highball.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reading about the community coming out of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L0pht&quot;&gt;early hacker-spaces&lt;/a&gt; or places like &lt;a href=&quot;https://gds.blog.gov.uk/2013/05/01/govuk-in-pictures/&quot;&gt;GDS&lt;/a&gt;, I feel a little sad (&lt;em&gt;and, perhaps a phantom pang of loneliness&lt;/em&gt;) that with more remoteness and less time in second or &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Third_place&quot;&gt;third places&lt;/a&gt;, that for a while there will be fewer of these…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/0f78ea83-2c98-464c-b6bf-59198e415dbe?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Conditioning — 21 August 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reader I have a confession: While I’ve referenced it plenty in the past, it’s only very recently that I started consciously compartmentalising. And it is a very useful tool indeed. On Saturday Sunday Monday Tuesday my…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c4e91546-1955-4145-ad09-e9af4cf9802f?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c4e91546-1955-4145-ad09-e9af4cf9802f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 21:18:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reader I have a confession: While I’ve referenced it plenty in the past, it’s only very recently that I started consciously &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/ryanblair/2012/06/26/5-steps-of-compartmentalization/&quot;&gt;compartmentalising&lt;/a&gt;. And it is a very useful tool indeed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Saturday Sunday Monday &lt;em&gt;Tuesday&lt;/em&gt; my new air conditioner arrived and &lt;em&gt;immediately&lt;/em&gt; brought my apartment below 30°C - and my bedroom below the 25°C - both for the first time in long over a week. Huzzah.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At work on Thursday afternoon we had our first Show &amp;amp; Tell across all of Product &amp;amp; Technology. It’s pretty bananas seeing how much interesting work is going on once it’s all presented in one place.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It fell on the day of a Rail strike, meaning fewer people came in person than had signed up. So after the few of us who were there commandeered the extra bottles of wine &amp;amp; chewed the fat: True influencer moment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Tube &amp;amp; Rail strikes have been inconvenient (I guess that’s the purpose of a strike) but for me amounted to walking a bit more - which is no bad thing. I am now mildly obsessed with buying an electric bike though. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vanmoof.com/en-GB/electric-bikes&quot;&gt;Look it&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c4e91546-1955-4145-ad09-e9af4cf9802f?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Atsuatsu — 14th August]]></title><description><![CDATA[Writing these from my “balcony”. It isn’t big enough for a chair so I’m leaning against a wall and pretending that passing cars can’t see me. It’s been pretty hot in the UK this week, and my newly instrumented apartment…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/42725480-8772-4491-b5cb-172b10e188c5?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/42725480-8772-4491-b5cb-172b10e188c5</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 18:30:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;p&gt;Writing these from my “balcony”. It isn’t big enough for a chair so I’m leaning against a wall and pretending that passing cars can’t see me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s been pretty hot in the UK this week, and my newly instrumented apartment peaked at 34.2°C (or 93.6°F). The root cause is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Heat_dome&quot;&gt;heat dome&lt;/a&gt; which reminds me of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0462538/&quot;&gt;Simpsons Movie&lt;/a&gt;. Not because of the dome - but because I can’t wait for it to be over.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know what really is an excellent movie though? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt11866324/&quot;&gt;Prey&lt;/a&gt;. Best Predator movie yet. And on the theme of media about predatory behaviour, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt10166622&quot;&gt;The Dropout&lt;/a&gt; is a great adaptation of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/37976541-bad-blood&quot;&gt;John Carreyrou’s original book&lt;/a&gt; - although unfortunately it left out &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodreads.com/notes/50253296-bad-blood/90636253-alex-wilson/42f8123f-9a03-4982-b65c-d3a33866b8a0&quot;&gt;my favourite scene&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hi Alex!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regrettably the heat has prevented me from getting much done - there’s reading I can’t concentrate on and coursework I haven’t even started. So I caved and bought an air conditioning unit - which helpfully arrives after the heatwave is over.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oh well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/42725480-8772-4491-b5cb-172b10e188c5?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Instrumenting — 7th August 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week at work felt quite heavy in terms of operational activities - it flew by and I had only really made progress in one discrete area. Some people from Nikkei were in town this week. As the two most established…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/48e0bf88-d974-4db6-9af7-2f07b74d0114?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/48e0bf88-d974-4db6-9af7-2f07b74d0114</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 21:48:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;p&gt;This week at work felt quite heavy in terms of operational activities - it flew by and I had only really made progress in one discrete area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some people from Nikkei were in town this week. As the two most established London teams, Customer Products &amp;amp; Internal Products combined our monthly team-wide showcases to welcome them. I’m glad we did it if only to see how different teams organise &amp;amp; run similar cultural events. And &lt;em&gt;so far&lt;/em&gt; it’s already given rise to at least one inter-departmental table-tennis feud and/or tournament.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As always, hugely impressive seeing the sheer skill of Japanese-English interpreters. Both during the snapshot, and later in an impromptu one-on-one, that is a level of multi-lingual mastery which needs to be seen to be believed. Meanwhile, nearly Wanikani level 3 - huzzah.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alicebartlett.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Alice&lt;/a&gt; started a book club at work, where &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/ft-product-technology/book-club-the-pragmatic-programmer-2886fe053ef&quot;&gt;we read a chapter of the revised Pragmatic Programmer and talk about it weekly&lt;/a&gt;. First week was fun. My favourite note from the conversation was: &lt;em&gt;“Stone frog soup - what???”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;…&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/48e0bf88-d974-4db6-9af7-2f07b74d0114?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>