<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 06:21:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Thirty Hours — Week 45, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Much of my week was spent with the US elections, making sure that reporting worked as well as it could.  Looking after the systems and tools telling the news makes it easier to detach from the news.  However it isn’t…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/37fdd22f-4b69-491e-86ba-a84ae72a0646?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/37fdd22f-4b69-491e-86ba-a84ae72a0646</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 22:18:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Much of my week was spent with the US elections, making sure that reporting worked as well as it could.  Looking after the systems and tools telling the news makes it easier to detach from the news.  However it isn’t always easy to &lt;em&gt;stay&lt;/em&gt; detached: That’s the rub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🧦 Sponsored socks worn: 3 pairs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🍖 Meat consumed: 0 grams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📧 Emails deleted: 6251 threads.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bsky.app/profile/alexwilson.bsky.social/post/3lagsxmbrd72y&quot;&gt;Bluesky is now my primary social media network&lt;/a&gt;.  If you don’t already, give me a follow!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ig.ft.com/us-elections/2024/results/president&quot;&gt;Coverage of the US election&lt;/a&gt; took up the entirety of the first few days of the week, with Tuesday and Wednesday turning into something of an all-nighter.  We were prepared for a several-day marathon, but it quickly became clear that this was much shorter (yet faster) sprint instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It all went rather smoothly.  We got some delightful feedback from some readers — and several million page-views in the first day.  That’s the upside, or, a “reason to be cheerful” as GC would put it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot can change in thirty hours: There&apos;s now a lot of commentary floating around, and with the exception of a few interesting anecdotes such as The Bronx being the biggest swing, I&apos;m mostly blocking it out. &lt;em&gt;Especially&lt;/em&gt; the hit-pieces rushing to apportion some blame.  &lt;em&gt;Mostly those, actually&lt;/em&gt;.  It isn&apos;t that I&apos;m apolitical — I am not — or even that I want this blog to be: I am just still processing, as I&apos;m sure many others are too.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/37fdd22f-4b69-491e-86ba-a84ae72a0646?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Plant-Based Nuggets — Week 44, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Spent a lot of the week helping with various aspects of US election coverage next week. Some assorted tasks and a real deep-dive into web performance and maps, the latter which I’ve not done much work with before…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/f1a69fcd-90b7-4838-af82-fa5ff93a05e8?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/f1a69fcd-90b7-4838-af82-fa5ff93a05e8</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 22:41:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spent a lot of the week helping with various aspects of US election coverage next week. Some assorted tasks and a real deep-dive into web performance and maps, the latter which I’ve not done much work with before. Managed to get a 75% performance improvement in a crucial area which I’m quite happy with.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week in numbers:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ebay listings created: 2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Red-meat consumed: 0 grams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Headphones thrown away: 1.5 pairs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Starting to like React Hooks.  Yeah, I’ve not been thrilled at them until now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LF and I went to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/p/DBt44ZLoQdB&quot;&gt;Baron’s Bites&lt;/a&gt;, which was a League of Legends pop-up/takeover of &lt;a href=&quot;https://butchies.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Butchies&lt;/a&gt;.  Was it worth the twenty-minute queue?  No.  But I got a badge, which I gave away later that same evening.  I paid £11 for their finest plant-based nuggets which started out strong and ended in regret.  The queue seemed friendly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Apple Intelligence update dropped.  Um.  It’s not great, is it?  Here’s a doozy: “Cow sighting; desperate for cow manure”.  Here’s another: “One soup through a straw, deemed…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/f1a69fcd-90b7-4838-af82-fa5ff93a05e8?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Restoring — Week 43, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Low energy start to the week: I had Monday off, and ended up taking part of Tuesday off too. I’ve been feeling a little under the weather, but I think now slowly on the mend. This week in data: Individual shoes thrown…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/e8163feb-6aa4-45cc-ace5-ceca9f635c53?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/e8163feb-6aa4-45cc-ace5-ceca9f635c53</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 22:51:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Low energy start to the week: I had Monday off, and ended up taking part of Tuesday off too. I’ve been feeling a little under the weather, but I think now slowly on the mend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Individual shoes thrown away: 5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How long it took me to realise the clocks went back: 18 hours&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Total of all payments made in cash: £17&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have glasses now, sort-of.  I can see totally fine without them - but over the years I’ve developed an astigmatism and so they’re really helping with situations with contrasting bright lights.  Still figuring out when to wear them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In very exciting work news, CCC — which I’ve here and &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/46dcc1c2-4791-4410-9065-e63318554381&quot;&gt;there&lt;/a&gt; since its kick-off last April — is now finally live, debuted this week by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/10489c19-aecc-43e4-947f-bfde497de7b9&quot;&gt;Joanna Kao’s excellent article on AI-assisted accessibility tooling, and how they aren’t what they seem&lt;/a&gt;.  It was a monumental effort getting there and the change seems subtle, but is profound: Previously an article with inline functionality like that would not work on the main website or app.  The same is true of most news organisations and so I&apos;m very excited to see where this capability goes!&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/e8163feb-6aa4-45cc-ace5-ceca9f635c53?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Relith — Week 42, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Saw the king’s official transport going through the City of London again.  There’s nothing too interesting for me to say about it but it felt noteworthy at the time.  Some tourists might’ve been impressed, but living…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/a422db6d-a616-4960-adc7-e2282328e28d?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/a422db6d-a616-4960-adc7-e2282328e28d</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Saw the king’s official transport going through the City of London again.  There’s nothing too interesting for me to say about it but it felt noteworthy at the time.  Some tourists might’ve been impressed, but living here I’ve lost that magic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week in numbers:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🕸️ Domains purchased: 2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📞 Phone-calls: 22&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🍲 Soup consumed: 2.2L&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had a few conversations this week which I &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; enjoyed.  I mixed a few different tools/techniques which let me keep them short and structured: Think coaching blended with the 5-whys, fuelled by active note-taking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On my backburner is the general problem of, “How to orchestrate/instrument R?”  The closest I’ve come is the &lt;a href=&quot;https://cran.r-project.org/web/packages/openmetrics/index.html&quot;&gt;openmetrics&lt;/a&gt; library, but what I really want is to see where a pipeline might be failing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you’re ever wondering if you should sort your data client-side or server-side, the answer is: both!  A comparison sort (A&amp;gt;B, or: &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;Array.sort((a,b) =&amp;gt; (b-a))&lt;/code&gt;) has linear complexity so is cheap to run client-side if data is already sorted, and it’s a good defence mechanism…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/a422db6d-a616-4960-adc7-e2282328e28d?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Bruising — Week 41, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Short week this week: In part because of last week it started on Tuesday morning, and in another part because my weekend got capped. :( This week in numbers: 🌿 Plant-based dinners: 3/6 🎚️ Missed buttdials from DJs:…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/63f289ce-7de8-4213-b340-2bd83d302a0d?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/63f289ce-7de8-4213-b340-2bd83d302a0d</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 21:21:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Short week this week: In part &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/3bfacc72-7403-4759-b921-6aad69f68c5d&quot;&gt;because of last week&lt;/a&gt; it started on Tuesday morning, and in another part because my weekend got capped. :(&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in numbers:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🌿 Plant-based dinners: 3/6&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🎚️ Missed buttdials from DJs: 2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;💉 Cannulas worn: 2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last week’s terrible eating and drinking led me this week to notch up my New Health Century. I ate &lt;em&gt;mostly&lt;/em&gt; vegetables this week. Tim Spector would be proud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I thought I had a week for the assignment I got last week, it turns out that no, I had until EOP Tuesday. I&apos;d already set-up a meeting with the most important peer to bounce ideas off, so I put together a scratch document with a lot of messy notes outlining exactly which technical problems underpinned the challenge we&apos;d been set, and transposed them into some much clearer bullet-points in the shared, working document. Got a spot edit, with very minor corrections, and some good feedback about it the following day so I&apos;m pretty chuffed with that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our CTO hosted a remote-first &quot;senior technology staff get-together&quot; this week which brought many of us together informally to chat about various topics. I actually loved the chance to connect with colleagues I hadn&apos;t properly spoken to before, or hadn&apos;t worked with/seen in ages.  Real highlight of the week - and better yet she has encouraged us to use the format if we like it.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/63f289ce-7de8-4213-b340-2bd83d302a0d?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Banging — Week 40, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Work was a bit of a blur this week. Spent some time polishing a Tech-Design-Doc which doubled as a check-list: Feedback was (consistently) to split the two.  Spent some time talking about support coverage over the US…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/3bfacc72-7403-4759-b921-6aad69f68c5d?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/3bfacc72-7403-4759-b921-6aad69f68c5d</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 22:37:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work was a bit of a blur this week. Spent some time polishing a Tech-Design-Doc which doubled as a check-list: Feedback was (consistently) to split the two.  Spent some time talking about support coverage over the US election.  Spent some time doing a rewrite of a document about ES.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week in numbers:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🚗 Miles in a car: 354&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🕺 Steps taken on a dance-floor: 64153&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🏖️ Beaches seen: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🎶 Highest BPM: 200&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monday marked MT’s last day at the FT. :(&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wednesday evening I was joined by M on a mission to buy PJs (thx Uniqlo) followed by dinner and a slow walk up to Guy Ritchie’s pub (which gave major old-man boozer vibes).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thursday I left the house (after a last-minute assignment/call), and went to Paddington station via The Cockpit.  Why?  Meeting LF to catch a train to Reading.  Why?  Road-trip from there to Skegness in the morning.  We met up with JL and grabbed a ‘spoons dinner and siren chaser.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday we drove up to Skegness, picking up a McDs brekkie and LM on the way. There was a…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/3bfacc72-7403-4759-b921-6aad69f68c5d?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Lightning — Week 39, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[My iPhone 16 Pro Max preorder arrived this week, and it’s glorious.  New iOS is great and I’m enjoying the new button + camera control, but the best thing is that I no longer have any devices that use a Lightning Cable…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/84384a91-f760-4d74-9589-a3a843df7317?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/84384a91-f760-4d74-9589-a3a843df7317</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 22:03:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My iPhone 16 Pro Max preorder arrived this week, and it’s &lt;em&gt;glorious&lt;/em&gt;.  New iOS is great and I’m enjoying the new button + camera control, but the best thing is that I no longer have any devices that use a Lightning Cable!  We are a USB-C only house.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of my main focuses has been rolling forward a bunch of low-intervention changes which, once live, will make it far easier to monitor and reduce the usage of a legacy system.  It isn’t all done, but I’ve got it written up with a TDD and a lengthy living todo document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work hosted a “safety skills seminar” this week which featured an ex-copper coming in and talking about how to identify and avoid being the victim of phone thefts, etc. Lots of examples and lots learned, but my main takeaways are to take a breath before going into a new place (eg leaving the office) and to think like an adversary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made some headway with feedback loops: Model feedback as a hand-off in kanban terms, and when planning as a generic dependency.  Set some…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/84384a91-f760-4d74-9589-a3a843df7317?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Griddling — Week 38, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[An audible sigh emerged after I re-ran a Jupyter notebook and saw a result meaning I will have to delay some work. Loud enough to turn TK’s head. I got (only) one question wrong in our tech all-hands quiz, and am feeling…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/bbd1b132-2373-4c64-bda4-6b67ea47c051?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/bbd1b132-2373-4c64-bda4-6b67ea47c051</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 19:23:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An audible sigh emerged after I re-ran a Jupyter notebook and saw a result meaning I will have to delay some work. Loud enough to turn TK’s head.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I got (only) one question wrong in our tech all-hands quiz, and am feeling slightly salty about it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quite hyped about a few new features and bits of tech that are going live soon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Over the week I had a side-quest to assemble what I’m calling “lo-fi black-tie attire”: Including a casual black jacket, a clip-on tie and grand court 2.0s. With student discounts the whole set was silly cheap.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thursday evening I went to the Business Book Awards where my mum’s book “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.co.uk/dp/191138385X&quot;&gt;From Grenades to Griddles&lt;/a&gt;” won the second place award (“highly commended”) in its category - the judges were &lt;em&gt;super&lt;/em&gt; complimentary and I&apos;m so proud.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The awards were a gala dinner pulling in interesting people from all over the world.  Dinner was a selection of Indian cuisine; naturally I binged on chaat.  It was too spicy for some but the staff were under the impression it was mild…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/bbd1b132-2373-4c64-bda4-6b67ea47c051?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Pills & Tape — Week 37, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[In my head this week had two big themes: CP day and housework. CP day fell on Wednesday: it is my team’s quarterly all-in-office day. This round I was one of the organisers, and between holidays (and illness) we didn’t…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/16761d87-7f56-44a8-aff5-fd93383aaefe?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/16761d87-7f56-44a8-aff5-fd93383aaefe</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 20:45:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In my head this week had two big themes: CP day and housework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CP day fell on Wednesday: it is my team’s quarterly all-in-office day. This round I was one of the organisers, and between holidays (and illness) we didn’t have much time to prepare. We split the day in two (as a proven format), with the first half being talks and a workshop with the theme of reviewing/discontinuing features, and the second half being a supported OKR session.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Like with other events (eg &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/335131d2-edd3-4fc1-96da-e3aef0b5232d&quot;&gt;ENGINEROOM&lt;/a&gt;) there’s preparation, and the day itself. A few things needed tweaking in the days running up (including changing our prizes, corralling speakers and encouraging people to bake). The day-of ran &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; smoothly - so smoothly in-fact that we actually lengthened some sessions without (hopefully) anyone noticing. I planned in buffer time for time-keeping in a little spreadsheet, but we never needed any of it!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remember &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2536c4b8-a8a9-48cf-a337-e1f5ed1fae1b&quot;&gt;the thing about the wallet&lt;/a&gt;? I forgot to transfer over my corporate card which meant I had to open the…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/16761d87-7f56-44a8-aff5-fd93383aaefe?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Gastropod — Week 36, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Experimentally this week I switch from a card-holder to a chunky bifold wallet. On Monday I buy lunch in the canteen, and one of the servers chases after me to give me the wallet I’ve just dropped.  Awkward!  Right, that…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/2536c4b8-a8a9-48cf-a337-e1f5ed1fae1b?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/2536c4b8-a8a9-48cf-a337-e1f5ed1fae1b</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 21:36:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experimentally this week I switch from a card-holder to a chunky bifold wallet. On Monday I buy lunch in the canteen, and one of the servers chases after me to give me the wallet I’ve just dropped.  Awkward!  Right, that’s why no to wallets. This trial continues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Between planning work that involves talking, reflecting and writing (and waiting) - this week I spent focussed time cleaning up old systems and code to simplify the planning. One involved removing a hack that Rhys, Luke and I did in 2019 which had made it into production, and another involved removing an entire line in our architecture by closing a Kinesis stream.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Later MS, MT and I meet up for dinner. We encounter an excitable man who eagerly expresses his sheer dismay at how quiet London is tonight, before asking us if we might know why - and - where he might find a crazy party. He pauses for long enough for us to send him on his way to Soho. As he walks away, I spot a toothbrush in his pocket. Dinner is fine: Katzenjammers…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2536c4b8-a8a9-48cf-a337-e1f5ed1fae1b?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>