<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 07:09:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Eye of the Beholder — Week 3, 2026]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m now a wallet phone case guy. Monday was Coming of Age day (a national holiday for those paying attention) and it was coincidentally also the Ome Daruma Market. To add pomp and circumstance to my 2026 resolution…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/6f14786e-98e6-4734-a38e-7e9420e68e3d?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/6f14786e-98e6-4734-a38e-7e9420e68e3d</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m now a wallet phone case guy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monday was Coming of Age day (a national holiday for those &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/f68de120-85c4-4431-8cb6-499f2a5ac60e&quot;&gt;paying attention&lt;/a&gt;) and it was coincidentally &lt;em&gt;also&lt;/em&gt; the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.city.ome.tokyo.jp/site/omekanko/16651.html&quot;&gt;Ome Daruma Market&lt;/a&gt;. To add pomp and circumstance to my 2026 resolution, after some cat-sitting, I ventured all the way to Ome, and in exchange for cash and a few words of broken Japanese, returned triumphant with a &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Daruma_doll&quot;&gt;Daruma&lt;/a&gt; the size of a voluptuous pineapple.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unfortunately I woke up the next day with a throat &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; sore that eating hurt.  This was not a great start to the week, and between working from home and staying (mostly) indoors most of my escapades involved housework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But: One of my chores involved contacting some law firms.  Most wrote back.  One, with an address in one of Tokyo’s “nicest” business districts, emailed me a quote with so many zeroes that my head is still spinning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Back in Japanese class for this term, and it’s certainly a difficulty notch higher.  I can rattle off the self introductions fairly unprompted now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After some wrangling, we re-did the branding for my department for an all-hands presentation.  I’m sticking &lt;em&gt;hard&lt;/em&gt; to the comms plan I…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/6f14786e-98e6-4734-a38e-7e9420e68e3d?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Of Bepsi and Frogs — Week 2, 2026]]></title><description><![CDATA[Twelfth night burst into my apartment in the dead of the night and bundled my Christmas tree into a small box. Week 2 and I’m both still digesting last year and writing goals for this year. However after a self-inflicted…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/f68de120-85c4-4431-8cb6-499f2a5ac60e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/f68de120-85c4-4431-8cb6-499f2a5ac60e</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:32:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Twelfth night burst into my apartment in the dead of the night and bundled my Christmas tree into a small box.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Week 2 and I’m both still digesting last year and writing goals for this year. However after a self-inflicted nudge, I have now set my top-priority.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For some system design, I learned a lot about how public holidays and time-off legally work in Japan. In short there are three-(ish) separate bodies of legislation which each do a different thing and name different days, but come together to give us weekends and bank holidays.  Although, interestingly, unless you’re a bank, none of these days is actually guaranteed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My birthday gift game is getting better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Over a delicious chicken lunch, I&apos;m loaned some house-keys with a fob-attached AirTag. I know that the AirTag is there, obviously, but this is a rare opportunity to see how long it really takes for an phone to notice.  How long did it take my phone?  6+ hours.  Scary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ridiculously efficient dental appointment on Friday.  In 4…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/f68de120-85c4-4431-8cb6-499f2a5ac60e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: For Whom The Bell Tolls — Week 1, 2026]]></title><description><![CDATA[How did you ring in the new year?  We walked around Kabukicho a lot before deciding it would be simpler to go to Aoyama for some sparkling sake. I swear that That Brand™ of sparkling sake tastes like apple juice. It is…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/6b9afd58-29f7-45be-ba77-7b277be544ca?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/6b9afd58-29f7-45be-ba77-7b277be544ca</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:22:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How did you ring in the new year?  We walked around Kabukicho a lot before deciding it would be simpler to go to Aoyama for some sparkling sake.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I swear that That Brand™ of sparkling sake tastes like apple juice. It is one of &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; most dangerous drinks I have ever tasted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On new years day, near a fateful shrine, I shared a cup of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yuenyeung&quot;&gt;Coffee Milk Tea&lt;/a&gt;, which I’d forgotten was that good. It&apos;s pretty easy to make at home with an aeropress don&apos;t you know?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reader, have you ever built a TV?  I&apos;m building one now as my latest side-project.  There&apos;s a lot of moving parts, and it&apos;s quite frustrating testing it end-to-end, but I think it&apos;ll be worth it for the passive language immersion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Before the break, a friend came over for a knife party, in which after sharpening my kitchen knives, we took a whetstone to my brand new pan to try and fix the seasoning.  I’m not sure if it worked, but I do know that my brand new pan now looks older than me.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonenkai turned into an all-nighter lock-in on account of…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/6b9afd58-29f7-45be-ba77-7b277be544ca?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Buchō's Rules — Week 52, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Phew, we did it, we made it to another Christmas in Japan. Well done reader, I know it was hard, and I’m proud of you. This week was split between Nagoya and Tokyo. What did we learn this week? 🤔 Firstly: Don’t share a…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/9632ec8b-008a-461d-a96b-771015240f84?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/9632ec8b-008a-461d-a96b-771015240f84</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 13:18:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;p&gt;Phew, we did it, we made it to another Christmas in Japan. Well done reader, I know it was hard, and I’m proud of you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week was split between Nagoya and Tokyo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What did we learn this week? 🤔&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Firstly: Don’t share a tatami room with someone who is sick. I had a sniffly nose for the duration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Secondly: KFC is kinda bland, and even if you’re able to pick the fabled &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.timeout.com/tokyo/things-to-do/whats-the-deal-with-kfc-and-christmas-in-japan&quot;&gt;“Party Barrel”&lt;/a&gt; up last minute, it really isn’t worth your while.  I was right to dodge it &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c363c1fb-8348-4502-8a65-3ed904f858e4/&quot;&gt;last year&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thirdly: Karaoke snack bars are &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; place to be, and you absolutely must make friends with the hostess.  Meanwhile karaoke open bars are more of a gamble, and making friends here is optional.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fourthly: Quite a lot about how to architect a workflow engine, and how approval flows work in Japanese companies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finally: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bucyocoffee.com/&quot;&gt;Bucyo Coffee&lt;/a&gt; do the best &lt;a href=&quot;https://ja.wikipedia.org/wiki/%E3%83%A2%E3%83%BC%E3%83%8B%E3%83%B3%E3%82%B0%E3%82%B5%E3%83%BC%E3%83%93%E3%82%B9&quot;&gt;モーニング&lt;/a&gt; in Nagoya, and you’d better play by the Bucyo’s rules.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What else went on? 🤔&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Invented a cocktail that RM would approve of, but it would horrify AG. Sorry lxds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; good 1:1s this week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My objectives/expectations for next year now include me learning to sing Candy Tune’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9HKbo1FstOE&quot;&gt;Fight&lt;/a&gt;.  When I agreed to this, it didn&apos;t seem to have many words.  Is this what regret feels like?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I really enjoyed working from the Nagoya branch office for a few days, since it&apos;s pretty small. I haven&apos;t worked in such an intimate environment since the early days of the Specialist in Sofia, and I forgot how nice an experience it it is when the &lt;em&gt;entire office&lt;/em&gt; heads out to lunch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There&apos;s pretty good hot chocolate there too, or so I&apos;m told.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Christmas day, I worked from home, and as background noise put on &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nine_Lessons_and_Carols&quot;&gt;nine lessons &amp;amp; carols&lt;/a&gt; from a variety of British minsters and cathedrals. It helped a bit with setting a festive atmosphere. If you’re noticing that this is a mere bullet-point in my notes, that’s &lt;em&gt;kiiiiind-of&lt;/em&gt; what celebrating Christmas in Japan is like?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/9632ec8b-008a-461d-a96b-771015240f84?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Busy Era — Week 51, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week marks the beginning of a busy era.  I was first introduced to this concept this year, and since have become intimately familiar with it, although this is my first time in my own one.  They are born in a moment…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/4a8d9445-0103-4a8d-a6be-f2db18dbb678?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/4a8d9445-0103-4a8d-a6be-f2db18dbb678</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 13:42:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week marks the beginning of a busy era.  I was first introduced to this concept this year, and since have become &lt;em&gt;intimately&lt;/em&gt; familiar with it, although this is my first time in my own one.  They are born in a moment of realisation that you are in too deep.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Where did my time go this week?  Some “back-of-napkin” maths for RAG (it’s expensive!), some talking &amp;amp; goal-setting (seeking approvals!) and some efforts to understand how big this new project I was asked to support is (scarily large!).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In my notes there’s something in here about a collaboration cafe, but to be honest I don’t really remember what it was themed after.  The company was the main reason I went, and I got to recount some stories that didn&apos;t paint me in a positive light but made my friends smile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We returned to the Bombay Sizzlers for dishes which were no longer on the menu, and settled for curry instead.  I had the Goan Fish Curry, which is at least as good as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ashasbirmingham.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Asha’s&lt;/a&gt; and brings me back: The last time I had it was in…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/4a8d9445-0103-4a8d-a6be-f2db18dbb678?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: 24 bottles — Week 50, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[We start the week right with maybe the best burger yet in Tokyo.  It was more pastrami than burger, more mustard than greens, and apparently this is perfect.  To be honest, I’m still thinking about it. A couple of big…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/376a5add-1c58-4559-91b6-0ee080fb7a09?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/376a5add-1c58-4559-91b6-0ee080fb7a09</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 13:34:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We start the week right with &lt;em&gt;maybe&lt;/em&gt; the best burger yet in Tokyo.  It was more pastrami than burger, more mustard than greens, and apparently this is perfect.  To be honest, I’m still thinking about it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A couple of big earthquakes happen this week.  We feel them.  I watch the news into the wee hours tracking the resulting tsunami until it hits land.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Presented about some light strategy &amp;amp; charter work to a “standing ovation”.  That felt good.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My piece &lt;a href=&quot;https://global.moneyforward-dev.jp/2025/12/04/migrating-to-the-next-js-app-router-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-server-actions/&quot;&gt;about a project I was involved in this year is out&lt;/a&gt;. I learned a few things including, “if you’re writing about adopting a technology, and a CVE about that technology is released that same day, expect delays”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On a Shinjuku mission to see some flowers, saw &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Maurice_Utrillo&quot;&gt;Mautrice Utrillo&lt;/a&gt;’s life and works at the Sampo museum. He went through a lot, held some strange views, and he also &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; enjoyed the cabaret. Saw Van Gogh’s sunflowers on the way out which gave off a very calming energy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Closed the week in reflection and prayer at a temple.  Walked out…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/376a5add-1c58-4559-91b6-0ee080fb7a09?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Migrating to the Next.js App Router (or: how I learned to stop worrying and love Server Actions)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi, I’m Alex Wilson and I’m a Staff Engineer in the Business Platform Development Division of Money Forward.  Welcome to day 5 of our 2025 advent calendar. In 2025, we overhauled one of our customer-facing products to…]]></description><link>https://global.moneyforward-dev.jp/2025/12/04/migrating-to-the-next-js-app-router-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-server-actions/?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://global.moneyforward-dev.jp/2025/12/04/migrating-to-the-next-js-app-router-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-server-actions/</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:30:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;p&gt;Hi, I’m &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech&quot;&gt;Alex Wilson&lt;/a&gt; and I’m a Staff Engineer in the Business Platform Development Division of Money Forward.  Welcome to day 5 of our &lt;a href=&quot;https://adventar.org/calendars/11946&quot;&gt;2025 advent calendar&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2025, we overhauled one of our customer-facing products to make it faster, more secure and more reliable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We achieved this by consolidating business logic to run on the server, server-rendering with React Server Components, and unlocking both of these things by migrating to the Next.js App Router.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this post I want to talk about how we did this, and about the challenges we faced along the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Chapter 1. The Challenge&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We build many web applications with Next.js, which is a framework for building full-stack React applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Next.js and its routers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before Next.js version 13, its primary architecture was called the Pages Router, which would detect React Components in a &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;src/pages&lt;/code&gt; directory, allow them to do some data-fetching and then compile these into the actual pages/views shown to users.  For most applications, this means that the…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://global.moneyforward-dev.jp/2025/12/04/migrating-to-the-next-js-app-router-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-server-actions/?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Not Assembling — Week 49, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[It’s December, I now have a Christmas tree and it’s freezing. Consequences of a week about furniture?  This week I spent a lot of time at home waiting for deliveries, assembling furniture and preparing recycling…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/ecf648ef-8334-4d3d-b59f-14b8f66abac9?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/ecf648ef-8334-4d3d-b59f-14b8f66abac9</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 14:39:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s December, I now have a Christmas tree and it’s freezing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consequences of a week about furniture?  This week I spent a lot of time at home waiting for deliveries, assembling furniture and preparing recycling materials from all the packaging.  More of it was that last one than I’m proud to admit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New monitor &amp;amp; desk means I can now work from home.  Actually, this time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week I founded a new team which will be accountable for technical architecture.  On top of wrap-up activities for my previous area, I did requirement-gathering with my new stakeholders and I began developing a 3-pillar strategy.  Next step is writing a charter and drafting objectives - exciting stuff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Naturally I’m re-reading “&lt;a href=&quot;https://gilest.org/books/ach.html&quot;&gt;The Agile Comms Handbook&lt;/a&gt;” one of the most useful business books of all time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went to the taco placed that must not be named.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Friday there was a major Cloudflare incident. You’ve probably heard about it.  This blog was unaffected, I’m not sure why.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wrote a 3000-word blog post this week…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ecf648ef-8334-4d3d-b59f-14b8f66abac9?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Shaka Brah — Week 48, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Well reader, how do you follow Nagoya?  The answer, apparently, is by buying more furniture. I now use Kagi.  Unlike many other products I use, it Just Works™ and honestly I love it.  It has restored my faith in the web…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/650e9d98-b00a-4d1f-a8be-df156ea025b2?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/650e9d98-b00a-4d1f-a8be-df156ea025b2</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 13:11:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well reader, how do you follow Nagoya?  The answer, apparently, is by buying more furniture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I now use &lt;a href=&quot;https://kagi.com/&quot;&gt;Kagi&lt;/a&gt;.  Unlike many other products I use, it Just Works™ and honestly &lt;em&gt;I love it&lt;/em&gt;.  It has restored my faith in the web, and I find myself using web search again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A year ago I was sitting in an empty apartment, wondering what I’d got myself into.  Today I haven&apos;t yet decided where I’m at, but I do know that this will be a banger yearnotes post.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Major release this week, which was heaps of fun and in-part put my Japanese to the test because it is &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; customer facing.  I think that part went well.  The todo list I assembled is now complete.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Almost immediately after the release I found myself thinking about the weeks leading into the start of this project, and a tactical error I made.  I don&apos;t have many regrets but I do wish I could go back and change things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We visited the Taco factory and gave them a run for their money.  Much garlic shrimp was consumed that night.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What began as a…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/650e9d98-b00a-4d1f-a8be-df156ea025b2?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Packing — Week 47, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week marks a year since I left the FT, and my 51st week in Tokyo. Where is my head at a year after stepping away from journalism?  I still feel an incredible passion for the news and I miss it (and, of course, my…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/8fa394fb-c8f0-494e-8bc9-020d1ad0b63f?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/8fa394fb-c8f0-494e-8bc9-020d1ad0b63f</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week marks &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/198b3ab3-2b8d-4da8-8881-1262d3eb2366&quot;&gt;a year since I left the FT&lt;/a&gt;, and my 51st week in Tokyo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Where is my head at a year after stepping away from journalism?  I still feel an incredible passion for the news and I miss it (and, of course, my beloved former coworkers) &lt;em&gt;every day&lt;/em&gt; but I am also enjoying some distance from the cutting edge of current affairs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’ve now got braces, sort-of, step-one of many, and getting ahead of future issues.  They are &lt;em&gt;slightly&lt;/em&gt; limiting.  Pronouncing “Th” and “F” have become an adventure.  I’m sure you’d find it funny.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did a second batch of Pizza dough, this time with the same flour I previously used, and it went OK.  Still many variables to perfect.  Hydration was off, but the final bake was very good.  Future batches will be much smaller.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BTW there is good Pizza in Tokyo. And sangria, and limoncello. Oh no.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How better to celebrate almost a year in Japan than to finally visit the Japanese equivalent of my hometown of Birmingham?  You may know it as Nagoya.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What took me to Nagoya…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/8fa394fb-c8f0-494e-8bc9-020d1ad0b63f?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>