<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 06:11:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Archaeologising — 12th June 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[During the week I was lucky enough to go to both LeadDev & LeadingEng conferences.  Huge thank-you to Euan & Anna respectively for the tickets - I otherwise wouldn't have gone, which would have been a huge mistake…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/96a83745-76dc-47dc-8294-eae333aec62d?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/96a83745-76dc-47dc-8294-eae333aec62d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 16:20:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;During the week I was lucky enough to go to both &lt;a href=&quot;https://leaddev.com/&quot;&gt;LeadDev&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://leaddev.com/leadingeng-london&quot;&gt;LeadingEng&lt;/a&gt; conferences.  Huge thank-you to &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/efinlay24&quot;&gt;Euan&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annashipman.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Anna&lt;/a&gt; respectively for the tickets - I otherwise wouldn&apos;t have gone, which would have been a &lt;em&gt;huge&lt;/em&gt; mistake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://leaddev.com/&quot;&gt;LeadDev&lt;/a&gt;’s name is definitely unintuitive: I’d recommend it to &lt;strong&gt;all&lt;/strong&gt; mid &amp;amp; senior level engineers as a flavour of what sorts of things tech-leads &amp;amp; engineering-managers are doing, as well as a guide on how to progress to either.  It’s also pointer to the wealth of excellent resources that now exist.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I last went to &lt;a href=&quot;https://leaddev.com/&quot;&gt;LeadDev&lt;/a&gt; in 2016 and at the time, as a recently-minted tech-lead, I found the content super-stretchy &amp;amp; valuable.  Several years later, some of the talks feel less relevant but I cannot understate how excellent &amp;amp; helpful it still was.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://leaddev.com/leadingeng-london&quot;&gt;LeadingEng&lt;/a&gt; on Friday was exactly the progression it promised to be.  Sitting at a table of directors…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/96a83745-76dc-47dc-8294-eae333aec62d?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full article...&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Jubilating — 4th June 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Slowly getting back to normal this week, just in time to remember that over the past few years I’ve been developing hay-fever. No running (yet) this week.  It’s the Platinum Jubilee so it was a short 3-day week. I spent…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/dcc7d761-6e75-4cf3-9068-71989b3ec7cb?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/dcc7d761-6e75-4cf3-9068-71989b3ec7cb</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 12:40:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Slowly getting back to normal this week, just in time to remember that over the past few years I’ve been developing hay-fever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No running (yet) this week.  It’s the Platinum Jubilee so it was a short 3-day week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I spent some time reviewing fracture planes with a view to applying them to (hopefully) enable some several teams to work together in harmony.  Many things about this work are quite exciting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Wednesday I went to a lunch with Fastly which was nice, not only because Fastly are a lovely collection of humans, but, because we learned about how other companies approach some of the same challenges that we’re facing.&lt;/li&gt;…&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/dcc7d761-6e75-4cf3-9068-71989b3ec7cb?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full article...&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Convalescing — 28th May]]></title><description><![CDATA[Week two of Covid: Last Saturday was the peak of my symptoms, and one long week later, I'm feeling somewhere between 93-96%. Every day Oura has reported a slightly healthier temperature, respiratory-rate & heart-rate…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/9c7263f6-3aea-4217-9b14-952468c41b53?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/9c7263f6-3aea-4217-9b14-952468c41b53</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:22:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Week two of Covid: Last Saturday was the peak of my symptoms, and one long week later, I&apos;m feeling somewhere between 93-96%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Every day &lt;a href=&quot;https://ouraring.com/&quot;&gt;Oura&lt;/a&gt; has reported a slightly healthier temperature, respiratory-rate &amp;amp; heart-rate-variability. The long-tail shows how gradual the recovery has been.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The major symptoms were a dry-cough (which became a wet cough the next day), a five-day-long headache, fatigue (which hasn&apos;t gone entirely yet).  Oh, and sneezing, &lt;a href=&quot;https://covid.joinzoe.com/post/covid-sneezing&quot;&gt;which is how I know the vaccine is still doing something&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At some point I stopped being able to smell anything, which is a story involving food that I&apos;d really rather not go into.&lt;/li&gt;…&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/9c7263f6-3aea-4217-9b14-952468c41b53?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full article...&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Succumbing — 21st May]]></title><description><![CDATA[Writing from my sofa in PJs: This week started out okay, and then I came down with Covid-19.  So now my life is rewatching Breaking Bad. Guess I won't see you at J's drinks after-all!]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/02ceb85c-8e28-4c60-a530-8c0d3b3c9af2?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/02ceb85c-8e28-4c60-a530-8c0d3b3c9af2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 16:13:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Writing from my sofa in PJs: This week started out okay, and then I came down with Covid-19.  So now my life is rewatching &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0903747/&quot;&gt;Breaking Bad&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guess I won&apos;t &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/a5d000d1-b899-4ebd-b102-c33d86e8001a&quot;&gt;see you at J&apos;s drinks&lt;/a&gt; after-all!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/02ceb85c-8e28-4c60-a530-8c0d3b3c9af2?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full article...&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Recruiting — 15th May]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m still running. Somehow I’m trapped inside a rare virtuous cycle and reader - I am here for it. This week I drew out two circuits: One short, through Putney Park Avenue, and the other, long, through Putney & Wimbledon…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/a68da397-8a07-4cff-924e-4598db873970?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/a68da397-8a07-4cff-924e-4598db873970</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 22:21:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I’m still running. Somehow I’m trapped inside a rare virtuous cycle and reader - I am &lt;em&gt;here&lt;/em&gt; for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week I drew out two circuits: One short, through Putney Park Avenue, and the other, long, through Putney &amp;amp; Wimbledon Commons.  I skipped going to any Eurovision parties to give them a try.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What I’m most proud of is making sure there’s a good way of running at home, with other plans. This is a huge step which will make it a lot harder to procrastinate.  This is a good thing!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After this second week of running, my legs still hurt. For some reason I started doing press-ups &amp;amp; planks again. Now the rest of me hurts too.&lt;/li&gt;…&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/a68da397-8a07-4cff-924e-4598db873970?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full article...&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Reminiscing — 8th May 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[With Friday marking my birthday & several days off work, I went to Birmingham for the first time since last summer. And walked, ate & drank a lot. And took some photos. Really nice seeing family in person after delaying…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/a5d000d1-b899-4ebd-b102-c33d86e8001a?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/a5d000d1-b899-4ebd-b102-c33d86e8001a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 22:26:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With Friday marking my birthday &amp;amp; several days off work, I went to Birmingham for the first time since last summer. And walked, ate &amp;amp; drank a lot. And &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/alexphotosthings/&quot;&gt;took some photos&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Really nice seeing family in person &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/50d21458-ac67-4c16-ad05-a7111ff5001b&quot;&gt;after delaying in December&lt;/a&gt;, and finally exchanging Christmas gifts: My sister got me &lt;a href=&quot;https://digitalgametechnology.com/products/chess-clocks/dgt3000-fide-approved&quot;&gt;a chess timer&lt;/a&gt; which I’m thrilled about.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With all the walking recently, I found my old running shoes &amp;amp; went on a few short runs: My legs hurt, but, in a good way. What hurts in a bad way is my ego: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.strava.com/activities/7100960598&quot;&gt;I’m really down on my times from 2018&lt;/a&gt;, when I last did this. Hmm.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With media saturation, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/may/02/roe-v-wade-abortion-supreme-court-draft-opinion&quot;&gt;Roe vs. Wade&lt;/a&gt; in the US…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/a5d000d1-b899-4ebd-b102-c33d86e8001a?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full article...&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Perambulating — 1st May 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tried two slightly novel things this week: Not following a schedule for going to the office, and, insisting on cooking at home. On Thursday morning I thought "Yolo" and went into the office, and, surprisingly had a…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/30dd5f21-f924-437f-9e73-fb42d39c2b96?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/30dd5f21-f924-437f-9e73-fb42d39c2b96</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 21:17:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Tried two slightly novel things this week: Not following a schedule for going to the office, and, insisting on cooking at home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Thursday morning I thought &quot;Yolo&quot; and went into the office, and, surprisingly had a pretty decent — slightly productive — day.  For me, a denier of Thursdays, this is a big deal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skipped cooking on Wednesday because, I accidentally took the last train. Whoops!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maybe it&apos;s less pressure? Maybe it&apos;s novelty? Maybe it&apos;s a mixture of a healthier attitude: I did admin, formed a chonky proposal &amp;amp; wrote some code.  And felt great!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last week my website build was failing…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/30dd5f21-f924-437f-9e73-fb42d39c2b96?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full article...&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Dallying — 17th April 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[I didn’t do anything for lent this year. But the four day long weekend is worth celebrating in its own right. Why don’t we have more of these? On Wednesday I went to a sake-tasting by Takara brewery, where after a brief…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/d3a83160-9c13-4c90-a63b-bc69bcce3331?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/d3a83160-9c13-4c90-a63b-bc69bcce3331</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 22:34:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I didn’t do anything for lent this year. But the four day long weekend is worth celebrating in its own right. Why don’t we have more of these?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Wednesday I went to a sake-tasting by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.takarashuzo.co.jp/english/&quot;&gt;Takara brewery&lt;/a&gt;, where after a brief lecture on the production &amp;amp; grading of sake, we got to try four pretty different varieties. I’d never had sparkling sake before and, considering how cheap it is, it’s delicious. Move on over champagne.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Also on Wednesday, &lt;a href=&quot;https://jakechampion.name/&quot;&gt;Jake&lt;/a&gt; left the FT (and I gave him the best leaving gift I’ll probably ever give). I’ll miss you Jake, really.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chatham_House_Rule&quot;&gt;Some interesting conversations came up during Jake’s leaving drinks&lt;/a&gt;, but one that stuck with me was actually about weeknotes. Our most “liked” notes are ones sprinkled with tragedy and negativity. What gives, people? You’re sending some really…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/d3a83160-9c13-4c90-a63b-bc69bcce3331?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full article...&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Remaining — 10th April 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[This weekend I was supposed to be in Lisbon (for Sónar & Pastéis de Nata) — unfortunately fate had other plans. Perhaps I’m biased but right now it definitely seems like everybody is travelling to Lisbon to vacation or…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c9a36370-33a7-48fe-84ee-e96ad0799d4e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c9a36370-33a7-48fe-84ee-e96ad0799d4e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 20:30:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This weekend I was supposed to be in Lisbon (for &lt;a href=&quot;https://sonarlisboa.pt/&quot;&gt;Sónar&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; Pastéis de Nata) — unfortunately fate had other plans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perhaps I’m biased but right now it definitely seems like everybody is travelling to Lisbon to vacation or &lt;a href=&quot;http://rebase.co/portugal&quot;&gt;work&lt;/a&gt;. Portuguese travel restrictions are relatively lax, but not that much more than other European countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whatever it is, I’m definitely a little jealous, so hopefully there’ll be another reason to go soon!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thinking about travel more generally (and remembering that I haven’t taken a totally-switched-off holiday since December 2019), I’m toying more and more with the idea of taking a month off a little later in the year for some immersive &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2078a9cb-4dd8-407f-aba3-45a3f9265193&quot;&gt;language-learning&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;…&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c9a36370-33a7-48fe-84ee-e96ad0799d4e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full article...&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Counting — 2nd April 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[With a few coursework deadlines this week, last week I skipped both journalling & writing weeknotes.  Two weeks flew by! 😬 On Monday I took the day off work, barely met said deadlines and successfully didn’t cry. Now…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/2078a9cb-4dd8-407f-aba3-45a3f9265193?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/2078a9cb-4dd8-407f-aba3-45a3f9265193</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 22:28:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;With a few coursework deadlines this week, last week I skipped both journalling &amp;amp; writing weeknotes.  Two weeks flew by! 😬&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Monday I took the day off work, barely met said deadlines and successfully didn’t cry. Now the term is finally over, to make time for travel &amp;amp; for other hobbies/learning, I’ve dialled back my class-load next term.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://stargate.fandom.com/wiki/Kree&quot;&gt;Kree!&lt;/a&gt; Between the cracks I began watching &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0118480&quot;&gt;Stargate SG-1&lt;/a&gt;. It’s been over a decade since I saw this show. It hasn’t aged well, but the nostalgia is wonderfully distracting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With the weather improving, I’ve been going on long walks around Putney/Roehampton/Wimbledon. Between the dreary winter lockdown &amp;amp; finals season I’ve been quite sedentary (gaining a few pounds) so long walks through greenery &amp;amp; woods in the sun are a &lt;em&gt;major&lt;/em&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2078a9cb-4dd8-407f-aba3-45a3f9265193?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full article...&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>