<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:37:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Suffocating — Week 33, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[A while ago I said that my tag-cloud would’ve highlighted “Lunch“, this week it would’ve highlighted “Coffee”.  Several memorable coffee catch-ups (without incident, this time).  My current side-quest involves one of the…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/a767410e-0706-4a55-bb67-091b6a31f7fb?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/a767410e-0706-4a55-bb67-091b6a31f7fb</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 14:55:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A while ago I said that my tag-cloud would’ve highlighted “Lunch“, this week it would’ve highlighted “Coffee”.  Several memorable coffee catch-ups (without incident, this time).  My current side-quest involves one of the less walked (and, documented?) roads of being a senior IC: networking.  More about this another time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nothing too exciting to report.  Got involved in some discussions, and tried to create focus-time to ship something.  Made some progress.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tragedy struck at Sonicmania after the epiphany that I was dancing to Drum ’n Bass but I hadn’t brought my brand new &lt;a href=&quot;https://kneecap.backstreetmerch.com/products/logo-bucket-hat&quot;&gt;Kneecap bucket hat&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But, it was was &lt;strong&gt;brilliant&lt;/strong&gt;.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.summersonic.com/sonicmania/&quot;&gt;Sonicmania&lt;/a&gt; is the all-nighter pre-party for &lt;a href=&quot;https://summersonic.com/&quot;&gt;Summer Sonic&lt;/a&gt;.  It was mostly electronic acts, and it let me finally tick &lt;a href=&quot;https://theprodigy.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;The Prodigy off my bucket list (somehow I missed them completely when I lived in London).  I &lt;em&gt;loved&lt;/em&gt; their set.  Many memorable moments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I saw... &lt;em&gt;sharp inhale of breath&lt;/em&gt; ... &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Perfume_(Japanese_band)&quot;&gt;PERFUME&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2hollis&quot;&gt;2HOLLIS&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kyary_Pamyu_Pamyu&quot;&gt;Kyary Pamyu Pamyu&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/floatingpoints&quot;&gt;Floating Points&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/prodigythe&quot;&gt;The Prodigy&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/gesaffelstein&quot;&gt;Gesaffelstein&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/shioriybradshaw&quot;&gt;Shiory Bradshaw&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/minna-no-kimochi&quot;&gt;Minna-no-Kimochi&lt;/a&gt;.  All were great performances with high production value, and great energy in the room.  I had major FOMO for the acts I &lt;em&gt;couldn’t&lt;/em&gt; see.  [&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/stories/highlights/18073701635098980/&quot;&gt;highlight reel&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/a767410e-0706-4a55-bb67-091b6a31f7fb?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Blues — Week 32, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[I really enjoyed this week, but, I didn’t have a good week.  Looking back, in many ways it reminds me of that week when we went to the Wolf. This week I shipped some code, wrote some documents and chatted with some other…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/41ef9228-75ba-4a91-8a20-78149d2e5f74?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/41ef9228-75ba-4a91-8a20-78149d2e5f74</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 12:37:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I really enjoyed this week, but, I didn’t have a good week.  Looking back, in many ways it reminds me of that week when we went to the Wolf.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week I shipped some code, wrote some documents and chatted with some other teams about their problems.  Spoke a bit with some colleagues about a monkey’s paw I’ve been offered and came to a conclusion.  (This is the post I put on &quot;&quot;&quot;The Gram&quot;&quot;&quot; the other week)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had an unfortunate incident involving a Starbucks Venti latte.   The less said, the better, but it happened in an &lt;em&gt;incredibly&lt;/em&gt; public place and now I keep chatting to people who “heard about [it]”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attempted to check out fireworks this weekend, and here’s how that went: Saturday - cancelled due to heavy rain.  Sunday - cancelled due to a fire.  Sign from the universe?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seems like everyone is sick this week.  Hope it’s nothing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.asagaya.or.jp/tanabata/tanabata.html&quot;&gt;Asagaya Tanabata festival&lt;/a&gt; at the weekend which was hella crowded but was lined with good food.  That’s where the paper-mache statues were.  [&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.asagaya.or.jp/tanabata/100selection.html&quot;&gt;It goes back ages&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/41ef9228-75ba-4a91-8a20-78149d2e5f74?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Allocations — Week 31, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[A week of doing things I'd meant to do for literally years. After battling with some Kubernetes configuration, I ran a (very!) large data migration job late this week.  From a purist perspective - in GitOps - even one…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/60ea6f5a-918b-4e71-8b3b-b32fbaea649e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/60ea6f5a-918b-4e71-8b3b-b32fbaea649e</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 14:24:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A week of doing things I&apos;d meant to do for literally years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After battling with some Kubernetes configuration, I ran a (very!) large data migration job late this week.  From a purist perspective - in GitOps - even one-off tasks need to go into Git.  And these operations are supposed to be immutable so you can’t just &lt;a href=&quot;https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/12/introducing-suspended-jobs/&quot;&gt;suspend&lt;/a&gt; them and come back later.  I’m sure I’ve misunderstood something?  There has to be a better way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learned some very interesting and exciting familial lore, which led me into discovering that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tartanregister.gov.uk/&quot;&gt;there is a tartan registry&lt;/a&gt;, and to realising that the GDS lot still haven&apos;t got to it.  Starting to understand the complaining about the Londoners.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The word &quot;Allocations&quot; has been sitting rather ominously at the top of these notes, which I have been completely unable to decipher.  And so it has become the title of this week’s notes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accidentally talked myself into a lunch invite, and am very glad I did because the conversation was great, but the discovery of a brand new lunch place offering an &lt;em&gt;above-average&lt;/em&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/60ea6f5a-918b-4e71-8b3b-b32fbaea649e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Pressure — Week 30, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[For me, it was the water pressure.  After a week of dribbling taps & spluttering shower-heads in England, the contrasting flow when I got home was the starkest and most visceral reminder that I wasn’t in England anymore…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/e1e629e1-9f78-4de1-b077-7df9deb3e91f?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/e1e629e1-9f78-4de1-b077-7df9deb3e91f</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:55:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For me, it was the water pressure.  After a week of dribbling taps &amp;amp; spluttering shower-heads in England, the contrasting flow when I got home was the starkest and most visceral reminder that I wasn’t in England anymore.  I guess I was too tired to notice all the others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monday was a &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; long day. I went for a run to get breakfast, did some work, and then headed to Paddington where I met Z and JW for a quick lemonade in the sun.  It started raining.  Heathrow was the fastest it’s ever been, I was at my gate in under 20 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The direct plane journey back is no picnic: I napped but 14 hours is far too long and I regret not having a layover.  Managed 5 films, of which by far the most interesting was &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt12299608&quot;&gt;Mickey 17 (2025)&lt;/a&gt; which I’m giving a 3.5/5.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt1745960/&quot;&gt;Top Gun Maverick (2024)&lt;/a&gt; also gets 3.5/5 but in a different way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have created a new question-bank for job interviews, building on my last one.  Each question is split by competency and level (although I need to better script follow-ups) and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annashipman.co.uk/jfdi/interviewing-fairly.html&quot;&gt;scored with a rubric based on the 0-3 scale I learned from Anna&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/e1e629e1-9f78-4de1-b077-7df9deb3e91f?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Diners Club — Week 29, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week’s story is best told through its dinners. Monday we find ourselves at The Indian Brewery.  We order two naans and a side of fish.  This is pit-stop on the way to cocktails after a few hours in the sun. Tuesday…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/a118ee8a-9154-4390-b43d-9c44720df964?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/a118ee8a-9154-4390-b43d-9c44720df964</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 22:31:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week’s story is best told through its dinners.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monday we find ourselves at The Indian Brewery.  We order two naans and a side of fish.  This is pit-stop on the way to cocktails after a few hours in the sun.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuesday ends at Birmingham’s most notorious institution: Maccies on the Ramp.  We have a tradition, born in darker days, which always finds us either here or Temple Row.  We meet near Ikon and take the long way round discussing startups and runners.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wednesday’s dinner is a humble Meal Deal: It’s a cost-effective way of powering our mini-celebration of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.co.uk/newsround/48991574&quot;&gt;St Swithin’s day&lt;/a&gt;. There’s two excellent coffees - I haven’t had espresso drinks in a hot minute so these keep me up into the wee hours.  The night ends with me extolling the virtues of powdered jasmine tea - which is perfectly proportioned to blend with a pint of iced water.  Then I go for a (very) long walk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thursday is a killer serving of Falafel &amp;amp; Halloumi with a side of Ayran.  It caps AN’s leaving drinks - which are…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/a118ee8a-9154-4390-b43d-9c44720df964?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Expletive-Worthy — Week 28, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week feels like a count-down, but, even as I close the week I’m unsure what it was counting down to. Did some writing about strategy and gave a small presso about the Golden Signals.  The Golden Signals are a great…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/23755f8c-602a-47b2-a31e-265b6f0fc150?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/23755f8c-602a-47b2-a31e-265b6f0fc150</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 22:56:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week feels like a count-down, but, even as I close the week I’m unsure what it was counting down &lt;em&gt;to&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did some writing about strategy and gave a small presso about the &lt;a href=&quot;https://sre.google/sre-book/monitoring-distributed-systems/&quot;&gt;Golden Signals&lt;/a&gt;.  The Golden Signals are a great example of &lt;a href=&quot;https://strategyu.co/wtf-is-mece-mutually-exclusive-collectively-exhaustive/&quot;&gt;Mutually-Exclusive, Collectively-Exhaustive&lt;/a&gt; framework thinking in the wild: As metrics they don’t overlap but they still let you clearly pinpoint if something is working, how well, etc.  This is the point I want to eventually land: At a high level they&apos;re enough.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Wednesday I woke up absolutely ready to fight the world. I channelled that energy into writing a 900 line pull request, and in doing so I reminded myself that I’m not bad at this whole software development thing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Thursday I yeet a message which I immediately regret.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After weeks of pitching drinks in the sun the day has finally arrived.  And after weeks of beautiful weather, it’s the heaviest sudden rainfall Tokyo has seen in quite some time.  We pivot to indoors and take turns trying to take…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/23755f8c-602a-47b2-a31e-265b6f0fc150?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Desk Edit — Week 27, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fuelled by the introspection and retrospection of the last two weeks, I felt an enjoyable clarity all week. Unfortunately, at the same time, the weather did its darndest to punish me. This week in data: Running: 15…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/ed088553-8ca5-4c2a-8a71-e9f3d3f26f53?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/ed088553-8ca5-4c2a-8a71-e9f3d3f26f53</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 14:19:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fuelled by the introspection and retrospection of the last two weeks, I felt an enjoyable clarity all week. Unfortunately, at the same time, the weather did its darndest to punish me.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week in data:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Running: 158 minutes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Italian food eaten: 2 pizzas, 1 pasta&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bike parking: Free for First 2 Hourse&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capability mapping is going well.  It’ll require a few passes to get right so I’m publishing early &amp;amp; often: Inaccuracies open a feedback loop for both improving the mapping, and, for finding areas for future improvements.  I&apos;m starting to understand how governance can work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Papers Club reviewed &lt;a href=&quot;https://modelcontextprotocol.io/introduction&quot;&gt;MCP&lt;/a&gt; this week.  What I like is that there aren’t any new fundamental ideas: You aggregate APIs.  What &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; new: A new class of security vulnerability.  There’s lots of room for interesting development there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had a first-pass at setting both my objectives and my expectations for the rest of the year.  It means doing a lot of (realistic) thinking about further developing as an IC, which is exciting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reconnected with some old coworkers in &lt;a href=&quot;https://tabelog.com/tokyo/A1310/A131002/13214764/&quot;&gt;the best English-style pub I’ve been to yet&lt;/a&gt; - which was an absolute blast - with a &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ed088553-8ca5-4c2a-8a71-e9f3d3f26f53?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Unified Supermarket Theory — Week 26, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This has been a Fusion heavy week: I have been virtually reliving the Sonnendeck, Tanzwüste & Turnbühne whilst gazing at all the stories from Glasto. Started something exciting: Capability Mapping.  There are a lot of…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/82bd3ca5-74b6-4f2b-a680-31690375eb77?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/82bd3ca5-74b6-4f2b-a680-31690375eb77</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:42:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This has been a Fusion heavy week: I have been virtually reliving the Sonnendeck, Tanzwüste &amp;amp; Turnbühne whilst gazing at all the stories from Glasto.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Started something exciting: Capability Mapping.  There are a lot of APIs in my new jurisdiction, and to deliver the best possible platform experience, we first need a map of what they do and what they don’t.  I’m the Ordinance Survey in this situation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated by this I am experiencing severe Biz-Ops withdrawal: I want to model everything - in work and in life - in graphs.  No.  I &lt;em&gt;need&lt;/em&gt; to model everything - in work and in life - in graphs.  Just one more node.  That’s all I need.  I can stop any time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;According to my notes, “Got some stuff into production”, so, that?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Over the week and weekend, I went through a series of McKinsey courses on topics ranging from resilience, communication and problem-solving*.  Some of the content was basic, but for every topic there was at least one practical tool, framework or technique.  There were lots…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/82bd3ca5-74b6-4f2b-a680-31690375eb77?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Actualising — Week 25, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reader, this week - in an entirely positive way - was rather a lot. It was cyclical. It had highs and lows. And I unlocked some unactualised-but-latent personal growth. This week in data: Distance walked: 112,780 steps…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/9653be3b-20fd-467c-a493-840cea6370e4?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/9653be3b-20fd-467c-a493-840cea6370e4</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 12:12:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reader, this week - in an entirely positive way - was rather a lot. It was cyclical. It had highs and lows. And I unlocked some unactualised-but-latent personal growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week in data:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Distance walked: 112,780 steps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conversations: 14 phone-calls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jitter: 10ms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The internet saga has concluded: For reasons unclear to anyone, I’m on a VDSL line which runs parallel to the gigabit ethernet already in my building. It doesn’t matter much since the central switch is still capped.  But it’s enough: I can now finally take video-calls at home.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The week begins with two high stakes conversations. For both, I believed that I was not equipped, so I assembled a brain trust.  And reader, the brain trust &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; came through.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Both conversations are call-backs to previous conversations from my past, and despite being &lt;em&gt;completely&lt;/em&gt; thematically unrelated, I have tactlessly avoided both for the longest time.  But this week I saw the avoidant link, and decided to change that.  Equipped with advice, second…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/9653be3b-20fd-467c-a493-840cea6370e4?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: From Legacy To Luxury — Week 24, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[What to say.  Stats are looking good this week.  Packed quite a lot in.  Tapped into some positive energy.  Wrote 0 Golang.   Wrote lots of words. This week in data: Papers Read: 1 Palace Run: -9 seconds Chess Ranking…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/7507d44d-a3de-405e-9152-ddb3151a0097?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/7507d44d-a3de-405e-9152-ddb3151a0097</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 14:24:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What to say.  Stats are looking good this week.  Packed quite a lot in.  Tapped into some positive energy.  Wrote 0 Golang.   Wrote lots of words.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week in data:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Papers Read: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Palace Run: -9 seconds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chess Ranking: +3 ELO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;今ちょっと暑いね？　うちのエアコンは頑張ってるよ！&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lots of recruitment activities this week, including I think the greater number of interviews done in a week in a hot minute.  (the 2019 record is &lt;em&gt;probably&lt;/em&gt; impossible to beat though)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The JS community said it couldn’t be done, but in a tiny technical win, I figured out how to feature-flag something gnarly this week. (&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/97c9a70f-3d45-4d96-94dd-3071f6af2dcd&quot;&gt;Maybe still technical?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marking &lt;em&gt;roughly&lt;/em&gt; a year since it started, Papers Club finished our longest paper yet, completing our deep-dive into Mixture of Experts architecture.  In our year we’ve welcomed guests, new members and new structure and I’ve learned lots.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Move over &lt;a href=&quot;https://jisho.org/word/%E5%BE%AE%E5%A6%99&quot;&gt;微妙&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://jisho.org/word/%E6%88%90%E7%A8%8B&quot;&gt;成る程&lt;/a&gt;, my new favourite word is &lt;a href=&quot;https://jisho.org/word/%E7%A2%BA%E3%81%8B%E3%81%AB&quot;&gt;確かに&lt;/a&gt; and it’s ENDLESSLY applicable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have resumed running &lt;em&gt;outside&lt;/em&gt; of the gym, and so &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.strava.com/activities/14792322238/overview&quot;&gt;attempted Palace Run again&lt;/a&gt;.  Last time…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/7507d44d-a3de-405e-9152-ddb3151a0097?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>