<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 06:18:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Cubing — Week 47, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Since pausing writing on holiday I hadn't made any time to write, but we're so back. There are now four weeks left until the year is done.  Think about that for a moment. Achievements this week included setting a new…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/7430bc12-9179-41e4-a831-0db583168718?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/7430bc12-9179-41e4-a831-0db583168718</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 22:17:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Since pausing writing on holiday I hadn&apos;t made any time to write, but we&apos;re so back.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There are now four weeks left until the year is done.  Think about that for a moment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Achievements this week included setting a new Rubik&apos;s cube PB of 0.75 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With the end-of-the-year review cycle coming, much of my time this week has been spent on management tasks which I&apos;m enjoying quite a bit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt9362722&quot;&gt;Across the Spider-Verse&lt;/a&gt; was a beautiful film to watch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had a rather nice dinner with some visitors at a Sichuan restaurant, where I was introduced to the combo of Mapo Tofu and Chicken Fried Rice.  It shouldn&apos;t work, but it really, really does.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt20245360&quot;&gt;New Doctor Who&lt;/a&gt; is so much better than I thought it would be.  Other than (probably deliberately) provoking some discourse, it feels like exactly what I grew up with.  Not to be taken too seriously, of course.  Lots of fun.  Thanks for coming back RTD!  Now let&apos;s just forget all of season 13.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I keep getting invites to external events, and I&apos;m only recently…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/7430bc12-9179-41e4-a831-0db583168718?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Lagging — Week 41, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Finally on holiday!  Writing this from the tiny desk in my tiny hotel room. I worked Monday, Tuesday & Wednesday which were quite intense but then went by very quickly.  Monday and Wednesday I crammed in a lot of and…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/98b62001-a95d-4275-b594-2ea66c4f2f4a?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/98b62001-a95d-4275-b594-2ea66c4f2f4a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 13:02:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finally on holiday!  Writing this from the tiny desk in my tiny hotel room.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I worked Monday, Tuesday &amp;amp; Wednesday which were quite intense but then went by very quickly.  Monday and Wednesday I crammed in a lot of and writing to ensure all the things would keep going.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuesday was my team&apos;s (group tech leadership) first away day since I joined.  We met at a vendor office in Shoreditch to retrospect over the year and examine topics including our technology strategy in more depth than we usually can.  We don&apos;t spend much time together as a team, so on top of the day itself I enjoyed having a natter.  We closed with 2 Truths &amp;amp; 1 Lie and I managed to fool the room which, you know, I&apos;m not sure what that says about me but there we go.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A perfect storm of the right conditions set me up to enjoy the worst case of jet-lag I&apos;ve ever had: I barely slept Tuesday and Wednesday night (nerves, and, an early start).  Early Finnair flight was lovely and the airport lounge in Helsinki was even lovelier…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/98b62001-a95d-4275-b594-2ea66c4f2f4a?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Cramming — Week 40, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Four weeknotes in one.  They were written, but my publishing pipeline was stuck.  I've fixed it now! Week 40 - is this week! Week 39 Week 38 Week 37 Major theme of this week has been cramming before my holiday: Which has…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/40b556c0-f12c-4d48-a676-89908eb8218b?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/40b556c0-f12c-4d48-a676-89908eb8218b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 22:58:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Four weeknotes in one.  They were written, but my publishing pipeline was stuck.  I&apos;ve fixed it now!
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Week 40 - is this week!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/71d36738-255e-49d8-af43-4ade14535c64&quot;&gt;Week 39&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/b0acee94-5aa7-4589-9098-be86832825fe&quot;&gt;Week 38&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/46dcc1c2-4791-4410-9065-e63318554381&quot;&gt;Week 37&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Major theme of this week has been cramming before my holiday: Which has meant cranking through the chores I need to finish, trying to set many things in motion at work, reaching out to people to catch-up and a surprising amount of last-minute shopping.  I now own another pair of trainers, but between discounts and clever accounting on my part these were &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/reel/Cv0o-nQtFth&quot;&gt;basically free&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spent oodles and oodles of time digging through JavaScript module behaviour.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After feeling very rotten over the weekend and Monday, I spent the entire week working from home.  In part, just in case I was contagious, and in part because I don&apos;t want to catch anything before flying next week.  I don&apos;t think I could be remote full-time: Video-calls are much more draining &lt;em&gt;even&lt;/em&gt; with a really nice set-up — but my main issue is a lack of self-discipline around stopping the…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/40b556c0-f12c-4d48-a676-89908eb8218b?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Tapwater — Week 39, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[OKRs and micro-frontends this week, mostly. Met with all my teams to review their OKRs, and then later met with all the teams that IG Integration relies upon to discuss what they're able to do in Q4 - and how it jives…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/71d36738-255e-49d8-af43-4ade14535c64?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/71d36738-255e-49d8-af43-4ade14535c64</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 21:29:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OKRs and micro-frontends this week, mostly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Met with all my teams to review their OKRs, and then later met with all the teams that IG Integration relies upon to discuss what they&apos;re able to do in Q4 - and how it jives with their OKRs.  Starting to feel like I might know what I&apos;m doing?  Very scary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spent a very long time debugging how our micro-frontend module-loader performs in different browser environments, including a few pairing sessions.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the end I rewrote our loading mechanism to be entirely event-based and to better align it to the browser lifecycle.  So now, as soon as JS can run, we:
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;begin fetching modules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;we allow them to bootstrap as soon as page information is available (but before the DOM exists)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;lastly we queue all of them up until the DOM is ready for components to begin interacting with it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This was a probably the most in-depth frontend activity I&apos;ve done in a while, and it was nice to know that my skills are still sharp, it wasn&apos;t as thrilling as I used to find this stuff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/71d36738-255e-49d8-af43-4ade14535c64?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Exhausting — Week 38, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[One of my teams, Storytelling, ran a nice away-day - where everyone made it into London.  I wasn't at the main event itself, but I was there for both dinners and a lunch (hopefully not only invited so I would pay…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/b0acee94-5aa7-4589-9098-be86832825fe?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/b0acee94-5aa7-4589-9098-be86832825fe</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 19:11:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of my teams, Storytelling, ran a nice away-day - where everyone made it into London.  I wasn&apos;t at the main event itself, but I was there for both dinners and a lunch (hopefully not only invited so I would pay...).  But I had a &lt;em&gt;great&lt;/em&gt; time talking to people I don&apos;t normally get a chance to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Tuesday I had my last occupational health session at work, where I got a simple question, &quot;Are you feeling like yourself again?&quot; - and for the first time all year, the answer was a resounding yes.  I&apos;ve been in a bit of a rut, and have felt anxious and stuck, but that&apos;s all over now — and I have the all-clear to start working out and travelling again, so I should probably take advantage of it.  Writing this particular point entirely for myself.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not sure why but I found this week particularly tiring.  I had a moment at the end of it, with George, where we just sat there in silence.  &quot;I&apos;m exhausted&quot;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Also met up for dinner with Hajime, who was in town for a big data conference.  Dinner was…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/b0acee94-5aa7-4589-9098-be86832825fe?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to opt-in (or opt-out) of Slack's new UI]]></title><description><![CDATA[S﻿lack's new UI hits pretty different.﻿ Since it's rolling out slowly, being in multiple organisations is quite jarring as it impacts organisation-switching the most. Luckily, it's still possible to opt-in, or opt-out…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/d02aea7e-ff53-402f-b729-2ccd8ad0bf12?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/d02aea7e-ff53-402f-b729-2ccd8ad0bf12</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 16:38:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;p&gt;S﻿lack&apos;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://slack.com/intl/en-gb/blog/productivity/a-redesigned-slack-built-for-focus&quot;&gt;new UI&lt;/a&gt; hits pretty different.﻿ Since it&apos;s rolling out &lt;em&gt;slowly&lt;/em&gt;, being in multiple organisations is quite jarring as it impacts organisation-switching the most.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Luckily, it&apos;s still possible to opt-in, or opt-out, on a per-organisation basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Enable Developer mode&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I﻿f you haven&apos;t already, enable developer mode by setting the &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;SLACK_DEVELOPER_MENU&lt;/code&gt; environment variable to &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;true&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;O﻿n macOS or Linux, this could mean adding &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;SLACK_DEVELOPER_MENU=true&lt;/code&gt; in your profile, and then restarting Slack.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And for macOS &lt;em&gt;specifically&lt;/em&gt;, running &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;launchctl setenv SLACK_DEVELOPER_MENU true&lt;/code&gt; in a terminal will work until you log-out of your Mac, or switch it off.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In Windows environments, if you&apos;re uncomfortable with &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.oracle.com/en/database/oracle/machine-learning/oml4r/1.5.1/oread/creating-and-modifying-environment-variables-on-windows.html&quot;&gt;setting environment variables&lt;/a&gt;, then &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Slack/comments/955dro/how_do_i_open_the_chromium_developer_tools_in_the/&quot;&gt;something like this will work&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;N﻿ext, open the inspector. It &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; now appear under &quot;View&quot; -&amp;gt; &quot;Developer&quot; -&amp;gt; &quot;Toggle DevTools&quot;.  Or if you&apos;re used to a Google-Chrome-like browser, do whatever you normally do to open the inspector (Cmd+Shift+I on a Mac).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;T﻿o enable the new UI&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Open the inspector, and execute this code in the console:
&lt;em&gt;(Or, have a read…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/d02aea7e-ff53-402f-b729-2ccd8ad0bf12?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Comparing  — Week 37, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[We're into the final planning cycle of the year, which is a particularly interesting one because it's also the planning cycle that feeds into next years' budgets.  So, busy days ahead. After a scare, I ended up doing a…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/46dcc1c2-4791-4410-9065-e63318554381?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/46dcc1c2-4791-4410-9065-e63318554381</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 22:27:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We&apos;re into the final planning cycle of the year, which is a particularly interesting one because it&apos;s also the planning cycle that feeds into next years&apos; budgets.  So, busy days ahead.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After a scare, I ended up doing a piece of data analysis which involved both of our content APIs, and producing a differential of the data in each.  I used Jupyter and Pandas, the actual disunion was a one-liner: &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;only_in_api1_df = api1_df.loc[~api1_df[&apos;uuid&apos;].isin(api2_df[&apos;id&apos;])]&lt;/code&gt;, and the hardest part (and yes, I&apos;m including fetching the data in the first place) was reading files off of Google Drive!  PyDrive, which is what Google recommend, is abandonware!  Anyway, crisis averted: the report confirmed our suspicion that there was no difference.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I got invited to a leaving drinks which morphed into editorial drinks, which was intense but very interesting - and I walked back having met a lot of people I&apos;d only ever heard of or emailed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After some advice from &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/thoughtsoflj&quot;&gt;a sage&lt;/a&gt; I made it my mission this week to name some projects.  So first, the work to introduce a native graphics…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/46dcc1c2-4791-4410-9065-e63318554381?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Scorching — Week 36, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Highlights this week include watching the outcomes of a design-sprint, validating the core technical idea in my new project and watching someone implement image transformation with matrices by hand. This is my hundredth…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/5c0d4a64-54c6-4425-9e2d-a5e57f6b4526?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/5c0d4a64-54c6-4425-9e2d-a5e57f6b4526</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 21:58:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highlights this week include watching the outcomes of a design-sprint, validating the core technical idea in my new project and watching someone implement image transformation with matrices by hand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is my hundredth weeknote, and I&apos;m nearly the point where these outnumber my other posts 10:1.  I&apos;ll probably change how the RSS feed works or something to celebrate!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;September&apos;s scorching weather is brutal.  Much like has happened with the Central line, an entire summer&apos;s worth of heat has built-up in my building, meaning that when I get home I&apos;m greeted by warm water from my cold taps and that my portable air conditioner has met its match.  Avg. 29C, Max 34C, Min 26C.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So: I&apos;m pretty deep in the rabbit-hole of JavaScript bundling formats right now, but it&apos;s OK - it&apos;s for a good cause: micro-frontends.  One challenge that we will face is interoperability between ES modules and our current chosen polyfill format: SystemJS.  I enjoy these rabbit-holes, but much less than I used to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/5c0d4a64-54c6-4425-9e2d-a5e57f6b4526?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Scrubbing — Week 35, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week was a short one.  I spent Monday morning sitting in a cafe finishing the Agile Comms Handbook, my honest takeaway is that it's great.  At the start there's a core premise of how to structure comms, then the…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/6fa8589e-5891-47e7-a9f0-207b56149da0?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/6fa8589e-5891-47e7-a9f0-207b56149da0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 21:36:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week was a short one.  I spent Monday morning sitting in a cafe finishing the &lt;a href=&quot;https://agilecommshandbook.com/&quot;&gt;Agile Comms Handbook&lt;/a&gt;, my honest takeaway is that it&apos;s great.  At the start there&apos;s a core premise of how to structure comms, then the remainder is a mixture of guidance and practical steps to make it work.  All the talk of tea made me regret the coffee I paired it with.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We&apos;re done with our first round of planning sessions to enable micro-frontends, or extensions!  There are several components that bring it together, and we&apos;ve scoped just enough of all of them to enable an end-to-end basic demo relatively soon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sagemaker is behaving now.  &lt;em&gt;Sort-of&lt;/em&gt;.  We succeeded to do some training on satellite photographs, but it&apos;s still missing some of our hyperparameters so we can&apos;t tune much.  They should be in a file, or in an environment variable, but they&apos;re appearing in neither.  So there&apos;s a light sprinkling of hardcoding happening until we sort that out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Also starting to get my head around the elections next…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/6fa8589e-5891-47e7-a9f0-207b56149da0?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Balancing — Week 34, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week marked the first few planning sessions to enable micro-frontends, or extensions.  I've been using the story mapping format to walk through end-to-end journeys and draw up epics and tickets.  We got quite far…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/6f27fe5f-243f-4b65-8e14-c8236ec36914?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/6f27fe5f-243f-4b65-8e14-c8236ec36914</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 22:10:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week marked the first few planning sessions to enable micro-frontends, or extensions.  I&apos;ve been using the story mapping format to walk through end-to-end journeys and draw up epics and tickets.  We got quite far, and we&apos;re on the cusp of starting to drive a few standards.  I love wearing this hat in projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Also published a blog post about that work and generally the reception has been really nice.  I worry that I went too in-depth with the technical details, and now reading the &lt;a href=&quot;https://agilecommshandbook.com/&quot;&gt;Agile Comms Handbook&lt;/a&gt; I&apos;m considering how to better brand this work - both to describe the short-term (which is intentionally small!) and the promise of the long-term.  The balance is off.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sagemaker is such a headache.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Summer is a funny time of year: They say that things slow down, but &lt;em&gt;I think&lt;/em&gt; that they speed up.  Those going away on holiday want to see things happen while they&apos;re away.  Those coming back from holiday want to see things happen now that they&apos;re back.  One of these years I&apos;ll become one of these smart, smart people - take &lt;em&gt;holidays&lt;/em&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/6f27fe5f-243f-4b65-8e14-c8236ec36914?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>