<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 22:43:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Recovering — Week 2, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Iconic week. Real highlight was a team lunch on Monday, welcoming George to our team. I quietly made a real mess of some grilled king prawns and failed to hide the evidence. We all had affogato for dessert and talked…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/634aa88d-fbe5-411e-8121-5f561ef1b0da?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/634aa88d-fbe5-411e-8121-5f561ef1b0da</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 22:30:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Iconic week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Real highlight was a team &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linastores.co.uk/&quot;&gt;lunch&lt;/a&gt; on Monday, welcoming &lt;a href=&quot;https://georgecrawford.com/&quot;&gt;George&lt;/a&gt; to our team. I quietly made a real mess of some grilled king prawns and failed to hide the evidence. We all had affogato for dessert and talked about music notation. Welcome George!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Slightly bittersweet, this was my last week as acting tech director of FT.com: reflections on that as part of 2022 review ... &lt;em&gt;eventually&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shorter notes again this week: I&apos;ve spent a lot of it recovering. This thing hit me hard. I&apos;m glad that the NHS was there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The uncertainty of my symptoms led to something of an anxiety tailspin this week. It got &lt;em&gt;spookier&lt;/em&gt;. And while I&apos;m feeling far better now, this kind of thing is scary and can come on fast so - reminder that mental health is no joke.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And did you know anxiety affects blood pressure?  I&apos;ve seen the numbers, it&apos;s no joke.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alongside one therapy referral, I&apos;m going through a slew of long-overdue tests with my GP.  In some countries there are annual physicals: For peace of mind I sorta…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/634aa88d-fbe5-411e-8121-5f561ef1b0da?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Rotating — Week 1, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Back at work this week, kinda. With difficulties in getting around by train, I've been working remotely from assorted Birmingham coffee shops.  Last time I did this was apparently December 2019! The CircleCI breach and…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/b78950bb-7dd6-4105-8515-8aba543e0b2e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/b78950bb-7dd6-4105-8515-8aba543e0b2e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 20:30:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Back at work this week, kinda. With difficulties in getting around by train, I&apos;ve been working remotely from assorted Birmingham coffee shops.  Last time I did this was apparently December 2019!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://circleci.com/blog/january-4-2023-security-alert/&quot;&gt;CircleCI breach&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lastpass.com/2022/12/notice-of-recent-security-incident/&quot;&gt;ever-worsening LastPass breach&lt;/a&gt; are a slightly disturbing trend, eh?  Starting to think that putting secrets in the cloud was never a good idea.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In very related news, the buzz-word of the week is rotating.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short notes this week: During a run I developed some spooky symptoms which ended up with me in the ER - the conclusion is a particularly nasty migraine. Genuinely freaked out by this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Also had some coursework deadlines on Monday, but since I let them know about the migraine, UoL have been kind enough to grant me an extra week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/b78950bb-7dd6-4105-8515-8aba543e0b2e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Decompressing — 1st January 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Happy new year!  Year of the Water Rabbit (after LNY) and hope. For the past few New Years celebrations I've been doing the science and running the numbers.  Now I can conclude beyond a shadow of a doubt that the…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/4fbaddf0-e66c-4ad1-b2dd-180bd1101791?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/4fbaddf0-e66c-4ad1-b2dd-180bd1101791</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 21:16:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Happy new year!  Year of the Water Rabbit (after LNY) and hope.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For the past few New Years celebrations I&apos;ve been doing the science and running the numbers.  Now I can conclude &lt;em&gt;beyond a shadow of a doubt&lt;/em&gt; that the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0126162/&quot;&gt;Hootenanny&lt;/a&gt; is the optimal British New Years Eve experience.  Nothing else comes close.  Even if it isn&apos;t live.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the run up to 2023 and the process of introspecting and writing-up 2022, I ended up throwing out any intention or ambition to get anything done and have been decompressing all week.  Take breaks, kids, they&apos;re important.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Man, PC gaming really never dried up did it?  Doing &lt;em&gt;nothing&lt;/em&gt; also meant making a small dent into my infamous Steam backlog.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Years Eve itself ended up being a rather wholesome affair: Last minute changes (for me, barely sleeping on the 30th and not facing hours of packing, travelling, unpacking, travelling &lt;em&gt;again&lt;/em&gt;, ugh) meant a smaller family celebration and an emergency trip to procure champagne, including a first for me - group video-calling…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/4fbaddf0-e66c-4ad1-b2dd-180bd1101791?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Celebrating — 25th December 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Happy holidays folks!  (メリークリ！) The stars aligned and I got to spend Christmas in Birmingham with family.  After unpleasant surprises in 2020 and 2021, this has been a welcome hit of nostalgia and tradition.  And too…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/6f2c2faa-cc8d-4c83-b2e4-048d5d893a27?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/6f2c2faa-cc8d-4c83-b2e4-048d5d893a27</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 23:07:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Happy holidays folks!  (メリークリ！)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The stars aligned and I got to spend Christmas in Birmingham with family.  After unpleasant surprises in 2020 and 2021, this has been a welcome hit of nostalgia and tradition.  And too much food.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But reader, it wasn&apos;t looking good.  I had a killer start to the winter break.  Instead of drinking cocktails and making music, I was confined to my sofa in with a rather unpleasant bug.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whilst recovering, I diagnosed &amp;amp; fixed a &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; annoying random iOS Slack crash. Using iOS kernel logs &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://mitmproxy.org/&quot;&gt;mitmproxy&lt;/a&gt; I linked an API payload to a memory leak, so I fixed the data (for me) and now have a ticket for Slack to patch the underlying bug.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.analogue.co/pocket&quot;&gt;Analogue Pocket&lt;/a&gt; pre-order finally arrived.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metroid_Fusion&quot;&gt;Metroid Fusion&lt;/a&gt; with the original GBA display mode is so much more atmospheric and moody than on an SP or emulator (and I set an any% PB of 1:43).  But the star of the show is native SNES on openFPGA, meaning, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_Metroid&quot;&gt;Super Metroid&lt;/a&gt; on the go&lt;/strong&gt; - but like - &lt;em&gt;actually Super Metroid and not a laggy emulator&lt;/em&gt;.  I love this so…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/6f2c2faa-cc8d-4c83-b2e4-048d5d893a27?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Drifting — 18th December 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Unceremoniously closing my laptop on Friday evening also closed my last day of work for the year.  So begins the longest holiday in a while, and a firm resolution to take many more holidays next year. With Twitter…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/5bcff697-194c-48a1-a439-9fdc789f6cf1?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/5bcff697-194c-48a1-a439-9fdc789f6cf1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 17:13:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unceremoniously closing my laptop on Friday evening also closed my last day of work for the year.  So begins the longest holiday in a while, and a firm resolution to take many more holidays next year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With Twitter becoming increasingly censored &amp;amp; unstable, I&apos;m redoing my site metadata to be less Twitter specific.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://metatags.io&quot;&gt;Metatags.io&lt;/a&gt; has been helpful resource for testing and previewing, and while I&apos;m not using it, &lt;a href=&quot;https://og-image.xyz&quot;&gt;og-image.xyz&lt;/a&gt; seems handy for generating images in a pinch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Despite all odds, over the year I made a decent dent in my objectives including getting all of my team specific objectives over the line.  I haven&apos;t done so well with my non-work objectives, so the next two weeks offer a chance to focus on one or two! 😬&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In an upsetting-yet-damning inditement of &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/20bf537b-e7c7-45f5-be35-35f3e1b2b586&quot;&gt;what I wrote about language-learning last year&lt;/a&gt;, this week I got the results of a formal Japanese language assessment.  I scored 70%, but, the comment read that my knowledge is &quot;patchy&quot; because I&apos;ve &quot;used multiple textbooks&quot;.  Yep.  Really wish people would stop telling me to &quot;&lt;em&gt;just self-study&lt;/em&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/5bcff697-194c-48a1-a439-9fdc789f6cf1?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Wrapping — 11th December 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Good lord it's cold. In the FT.com tech strategy wrap-up (which Anna has written up) I spoke little bit about next year's work in extending and improving our visual & data journalism capabilities.  Lately I've focussed…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/43123be2-fd7f-459e-93a4-47149dfc8752?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/43123be2-fd7f-459e-93a4-47149dfc8752</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 14:18:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good lord it&apos;s cold.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the FT.com tech strategy wrap-up (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annashipman.co.uk/jfdi/tech-strategy-process.html&quot;&gt;which Anna has written up&lt;/a&gt;) I spoke little bit about next year&apos;s work in extending and improving our visual &amp;amp; data journalism capabilities.  Lately I&apos;ve focussed on packaging, selling and delivering news in different products - so I&apos;m genuinely excited that my teams are now also working on its expressiveness!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuesday saw the annual company wide Christmas party - the first one in-person since the pandemic.  Our subterranean venue had a sunken dance floor with windows at the sides and so between the moving atmospheric lighting and the lengthy queues to get-in, it felt like an exclusive bizarro rave.  I left once it got too loud to talk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&apos;ve been using the Kindle Scribe a bit at work to take notes, and have discovered another nice use-case: Having a selection of books already downloaded means I can reference them really easily.  The note-taking is nice.  I do wish that it synched up to something I could use on a laptop.  Feeling…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/43123be2-fd7f-459e-93a4-47149dfc8752?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Brewing — 4th December 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[December is here.  After the last two being two lockdown-driven letdowns, finding the holiday spirit is a bit more difficult, but I’m optimistic.  The main obstacle is unpredictable trains, with strikes and other…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/ccc31a35-8676-4ee2-8e87-e75e0e2b28ef?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/ccc31a35-8676-4ee2-8e87-e75e0e2b28ef</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 16:28:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;December is here.  After the last two being two lockdown-driven letdowns, finding the holiday spirit is a bit more difficult, but I’m optimistic.  The main obstacle is unpredictable trains, with strikes and other cancellations due later this month, but still hoping to see family this year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overnight groceries are great: All the fun of spontaneous purchases with the savings of bulk buys. The only downside is having to wake up at 7AM on a Sunday.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spent most of this week preparing for end-of-year reviews, looking at options in recruiting and reacting to a few operational concerns.  It’s the final stretch of the year now so everything that comes in is earmarked urgent - including a surprise risk-mitigation project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highlight this week was my team all getting together in-person for the first time since summer.  It was for a workshop - but - the workshop started super late so while we waited, we had a proper natter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.co.uk/kindle-scribe/dp/B09BSQ365J&quot;&gt;Kindle Scribe&lt;/a&gt; arrived a day early. First impressions: It’s a great e-reader, and the writing experience is &lt;em&gt;great&lt;/em&gt;.  Marking-up PDFs works like a charm.  However its organisation options are no better than a regular Kindle, holding it back from being a notepad replacement. Perhaps most disappointingly, taking notes in…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ccc31a35-8676-4ee2-8e87-e75e0e2b28ef?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Keytaring — 27th November]]></title><description><![CDATA[One of our more obscure systems had a relatively complex outage this week, and I'm left wondering why one might use stored procedures in modern application design.  They're difficult to version and test, and with…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/e3aec8aa-d442-49a9-8f15-63e1e0356ef9?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/e3aec8aa-d442-49a9-8f15-63e1e0356ef9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 12:22:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of our more obscure systems had a relatively complex outage this week, and I&apos;m left wondering why one might use &lt;a href=&quot;https://database.guide/what-is-a-stored-procedure/&quot;&gt;stored procedures&lt;/a&gt; in modern application design.  They&apos;re difficult to version and test, and with relational databases you&apos;re already getting complex aggregations happening inside the query and data-mapping layers!  Major kudos to the engineers who figured this out and repaired the database schema.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I repped the FT at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siliconmilkroundabout.com&quot;&gt;Silicon Milkroundabout&lt;/a&gt; again - really starting to enjoy these. There&apos;s something quite nice about chatting to technologists about what they&apos;re doing, what we&apos;re doing and where they might find a fit at the FT. Exhausting though.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rakugo artist &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rakugo.lol&quot;&gt;Katsura Sunshine&lt;/a&gt; performed at our office this week. I hadn&apos;t had much exposure to &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rakugo&quot;&gt;Rakugo&lt;/a&gt; but always imagined it to be quite dry so nearly gave it a miss. Very glad that I didn&apos;t, because it was incredibly fun - and might even be a highlight of the year. Katsura Sunshine did an intro and told several stories, including &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nJ8Tq5EotaE&quot;&gt;Jugemu (relatively short)&lt;/a&gt; and I think I&apos;m now hooked. It turns out there are several English-speaking performers now - so definitely something to check-out…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/e3aec8aa-d442-49a9-8f15-63e1e0356ef9?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Slumbering — 20th November 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[As we approach December, the days are getting shorter and wetter.  This was a particularly short week as I've started taking time off until the end of the year.  It's crept up quickly - all the plans of doing travel this…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/a4253518-d0d9-475b-81f4-89a576e4baad?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/a4253518-d0d9-475b-81f4-89a576e4baad</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 11:55:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As we approach December, the days are getting shorter and wetter.  This was a particularly short week as I&apos;ve started taking time off until the end of the year.  It&apos;s crept up quickly - all the plans of doing travel this year have been quashed by the reality of pricing.  So instead I&apos;m trying to write a bit more, make music and go for slightly longer runs.  Chasing those endorphins, &lt;em&gt;literally&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When you join a team with (avg.) 7+ years of systems and history, &lt;a href=&quot;https://git-scm.com/docs/git-bisect&quot;&gt;Git Bisect&lt;/a&gt; takes on a whole new use in discovering historic design decisions.  This week I used it to learn about cache-strategy implementation.  Seriously powerful, but I wish there were friendlier ways of using it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday marked Engine Room, the FT&apos;s internal conference.  Many of the talks were really fantastic and it&apos;s probably unfair to call any out because they were all rather good - but particular standouts included &lt;a href=&quot;http://hack.nikkei.com&quot;&gt;guest speakers from Nikkei&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ghost.computer&quot;&gt;Kara&lt;/a&gt; playing &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E_UrhB1G4gA&quot;&gt;a modular set&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://leemoody.co.uk&quot;&gt;Lee&lt;/a&gt; baking the best babka you&apos;ve had in years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the pouring Kensington rain, on Wednesday we went to dinner at &lt;a href=&quot;https://samadaliraqirestaurant.com&quot;&gt;Samad Al Iraqi&lt;/a&gt;.  The portions were huge and the Lamb Quzi was divine, but the real star of the show was the meal we didn&apos;t eat: Masgouf.  Fresh fish sliced, smoked and cooked over an open fire for two hours.  It smelled incredible.  The flames were hypnotic.  We watched two men order it and slowly drink tea as they waited, only…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/a4253518-d0d9-475b-81f4-89a576e4baad?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Testing — 13th November 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm still doing ZOE tests.  Monday was the roughest day, involving eating 5 specially crafted muffins.  What's wrong with muffins?  They were fine, but I felt very strange the entire day.  There was a blood-test too.  It…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/32353f5b-c6a6-4983-85ad-4ebce675693e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/32353f5b-c6a6-4983-85ad-4ebce675693e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 20:57:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&apos;m still doing &lt;a href=&quot;https://joinzoe.com/&quot;&gt;ZOE&lt;/a&gt; tests.  Monday was the roughest day, involving eating 5 specially crafted &lt;a href=&quot;https://joinzoe.com/post/muffin-metabolism-predict&quot;&gt;muffins&lt;/a&gt;.  What&apos;s wrong with muffins?  They were fine, but I felt &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; strange the entire day.  There was a blood-test too.  It didn&apos;t help.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The rest of the week I&apos;ve been doing their blood-sugar challenges, meaning eating specific foods at specific times and watching the impact on a glucose monitor.  Today that was a breakfast of plain white rice with almond butter.  Was it a weird food combination? Yes.  Was it delicious?  &lt;em&gt;Oh my god&lt;/em&gt; yes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I messed up and accidentally deleted my Substack account &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/4a1f26b1-6ac4-4300-9867-1265b5946bdb&quot;&gt;and wrote about it here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wednesday meant Pisco-sours: What an excellent cocktail.  Dinner at &lt;a href=&quot;http://mirafloreslondon.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Miraflores&lt;/a&gt;, anybody?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Friday I went to Brighton for ffconf, both for the first time.  Brighton is great (the fish &amp;amp; chips are actually better) and I now totally get why people keep moving there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ffconf was a real vibe: The talks were all bangers and I took away lots of ideas &amp;amp; frameworks for building a better, more-ethical &amp;amp; &lt;em&gt;more-fun&lt;/em&gt; web.  I spent the entire time catching up with FT colleagues old-and-new (we were probably the biggest group there) and slightly regret not meeting anyone new.  But…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/32353f5b-c6a6-4983-85ad-4ebce675693e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>