<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 20:16:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Spinning — Week 25, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[On Monday I woke in Sofia and went to bed on Tuesday in London.  Still reeling from that change.  Said several hurried "Goodbyes" after lunch, and then after getting a row to myself on the plane, said several-more…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/76280b08-2b55-40c1-ba70-f74c29ec13d1?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/76280b08-2b55-40c1-ba70-f74c29ec13d1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 19:57:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Monday I woke in Sofia and went to bed on Tuesday in London.  Still reeling from that change.  Said several hurried &quot;Goodbyes&quot; after lunch, and then after getting a row to myself on the plane, said several-more hurried &quot;Hellos&quot; in London before dragging some people to see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/jurikohno/&quot;&gt;Juri&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/city-academy-voices-choir-back-in-business-tickets-611005342427&quot;&gt;sing&lt;/a&gt;.  Great concert and friendly band.  Should have skipped the chuhi.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OK now that I&apos;ve padded out the word-count for previews, I shall attempt to bury the lede: I experienced a close loss this weekend and it&apos;s still sinking in.  What&apos;s most painful is not having said goodbye.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of my teams had a team-day this week.  I missed the retrospective because it was in the morning, but got to join in with the session around reviewing the mission and trying to write some team behavioural principles.  We wrapped with &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/umbobabo&quot;&gt;Umberto&lt;/a&gt; hosting a game of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Would_I_Lie_to_You%3F_(game_show)&quot;&gt;Would I Lie To You&lt;/a&gt;, where I successfully(?) managed to convince everybody that I was &lt;em&gt;lying&lt;/em&gt; about bringing a backup sandwich to long drinks and parties.  What did &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; achieve…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/76280b08-2b55-40c1-ba70-f74c29ec13d1?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Pouring — Week 24, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Monday started early with a hectic call with Egencia and finished with me repeating history in 2019 by going straight from lunch at Côte St Pauls to Sofia, via Heathrow.  The Lizzy line made it significantly less…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/2738e9a1-e757-4e68-8ab8-46a7ad450799?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/2738e9a1-e757-4e68-8ab8-46a7ad450799</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 18:00:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monday started early with a hectic call with Egencia and finished with me repeating history in 2019 by going straight from lunch at Côte St Pauls to Sofia, via Heathrow.  The Lizzy line made it significantly less stressful.  But the flight was 2 hours late so all that stress came right back when we landed at 1AM and I couldn&apos;t find a cab.  That bit didn&apos;t happen last time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What brings me to Sofia this week is to work in-person (again) on the product coexistence problem.  We&apos;ve spent a long time examining architecture for the general case of deploying features across teams, and for a product pilot that we&apos;re kicking off next quarter.  The approach we&apos;re taking and evaluating will involve writing contracts, allowing systems to include components from other systems, and so far it seems like a sensible, pragmatic cut-back approach to micro-frontends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Also lots of progress with the exercise to enrich interactive content on FT.com.  We had a small workshop to pitch an OKR, and my group…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2738e9a1-e757-4e68-8ab8-46a7ad450799?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Routing — Week 23, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[It's air-con season again baby. I've been context-switching like crazy between several things on my plate, while trying to make room for some focussed technical strategy work. Went to Nick's house for a BBQ.  Lost at…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/24f7e0cc-1cfb-4d90-b3ad-edb07da883c4?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/24f7e0cc-1cfb-4d90-b3ad-edb07da883c4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 18:00:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&apos;s air-con season again baby.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&apos;ve been context-switching like crazy between several things on my plate, while trying to make room for some focussed technical strategy work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went to &lt;a href=&quot;https://nickramsbottom.com/&quot;&gt;Nick&apos;s&lt;/a&gt; house for a BBQ.  Lost at many board-games that I&apos;ve never played before.  Lovely BBQ though.  Saw a fox trying to climb the wall.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doing the maths late one evening I figured out that I could save a lot of money by buying coffee and alcoholic beverages in-bulk.  So anyway, on Wednesday evening a crate of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pocari_Sweat&quot;&gt;Pocari Sweat&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Boss_Coffee&quot;&gt;Suntory Boss Coffee&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Strong_Zero&quot;&gt;Suntory Strong Zero&lt;/a&gt; arrived.  For a relaxing time, make it Suntory time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stayed late in the office on Friday, and ended up watching &lt;a href=&quot;https://uxrconf23.joinlearners.com/&quot;&gt;UXRCon&lt;/a&gt; with several researchers.  Pretty interesting stuff, I really enjoyed the different perspectives on examining personal and systemic biases in research.  I also really enjoyed most of the sponsor talks where they framed a sales-pitch for a product as a talk, and actually conveyed some pretty good stuff.  Don&apos;t get that at…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/24f7e0cc-1cfb-4d90-b3ad-edb07da883c4?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Standing — Week 22, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[I last left you in a field.  It was a nice field.  I've been thinking about that field a lot. Got into the office quite early one morning for a conversation with the ABC about the technical work I'm doing to improve how…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/9da78967-f8c4-49eb-9597-15757d50c4d7?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/9da78967-f8c4-49eb-9597-15757d50c4d7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 18:00:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I last left you in a field.  It was a nice field.  I&apos;ve been thinking about that field a lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Got into the office quite early one morning for a conversation with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.abc.net.au/&quot;&gt;ABC&lt;/a&gt; about the technical work I&apos;m doing to improve how we build interactives, and learned &lt;em&gt;lots&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of my teams did a design sprint this week, and on Thursday afternoon I was invited to the &quot;jury&quot; to feed back on their ideas - some of which seemed like novel iterations of things we already had, and some of which were just fantastic ideas that really might push how journalists tell stories.  Felt pretty hyped afterwards!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kicked off some technical-strategy work, and spent a lot of time refining documents for senior stakeholders.  I&apos;ve decided my new favourite font for these documents is Work Sans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finally went to one of the Bulgarian restaurants in London - it was &lt;em&gt;fantastic&lt;/em&gt;.  Missed Шкембе чорба a lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Someone bullied &lt;em&gt;politely encouraged&lt;/em&gt; me into doing a bit of work to fix the mailing list on this blog, which I have now done…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/9da78967-f8c4-49eb-9597-15757d50c4d7?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Camping — Week 21, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[The trouble with doing a long hike on Sunday and then immediately walking to work from Waterloo the following day is that you get massive cramp. Writing this to the sound of “Cotten-Eyed Joe” in a field in the middle of…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/d971117e-ff1f-45cc-a976-23d1437da3be?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/d971117e-ff1f-45cc-a976-23d1437da3be</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 22:44:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The trouble with doing a long hike on Sunday and then immediately walking to work from Waterloo the following day is that you get massive cramp.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing this to the sound of “Cotten-Eyed Joe” in a field in the middle of Hertfordshire.  How did we get here?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Career progression in engineering is heavily on my mind this week.  Both the general case, and my own (I think they call this career planning) - and I’ve started writing down some thoughts. It’s hard to write something that includes both a diagnosis of difficulties and some suggestions without it reading a bit like a manifesto but I’m trying.  And also to not make it just about me.  And here we are.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Furthering a reputation I’d rather I not have, I discovered that a cache of discount cards for the sea-creature pub and started distributing them.  Sorry Euan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gee, the first season of this Succession show is pretty good.  Yes I know I&apos;m several years late.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There&apos;s a lot more to write but I don&apos;t want to miss my inconsequential self…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/d971117e-ff1f-45cc-a976-23d1437da3be?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Interesting — Week 20, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Started porting a subset of a very old PHP+React project to NodeJS this week which was surprisingly fun.  There's lots of wacky things you can do like parsing Twig templates as TwigJS or Nunjucks, and turning framework…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/b3b0eb11-6806-4291-9843-603ca1f51980?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/b3b0eb11-6806-4291-9843-603ca1f51980</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 11:34:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Started porting a subset of a very old PHP+React project to NodeJS this week which was surprisingly fun.  There&apos;s lots of wacky things you can do like parsing &lt;a href=&quot;https://twig.symfony.com/&quot;&gt;Twig&lt;/a&gt; templates as &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/twigjs/twig.js/&quot;&gt;TwigJS&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://mozilla.github.io/nunjucks/&quot;&gt;Nunjucks&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/nodeca/js-yaml&quot;&gt;turning framework Yaml config into JSON&lt;/a&gt;.  Miraculously the &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;package.json&lt;/code&gt; file still worked and I remembered how much I loved Class Components.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had a &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; uplifting 1:1 with our new CTO, and a bittersweet leaving lunch for our old CTO.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spent some time going over &lt;em&gt;every&lt;/em&gt; bit of current or future interdepartmental work and sorting them into three feasibility buckets.  Immensely satisfying.  There is now a practical list of things to look at to get the whole lot moving.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Wednesday I outed myself as a reader of a popular tech blog by going to &lt;a href=&quot;https://russelldavies.typepad.com/planning/interesting.html&quot;&gt;Interesting&lt;/a&gt;.  It was pretty good!  I learned a lot about shopping lists and misophonia, and a little bit about blood sugar and &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Section_28&quot;&gt;section 28&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mash, Diesel, Sausages, Shortbread&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went to Taro for lunch on Saturday and spent the rest of the day playing &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nintendo.co.uk/Games/Nintendo-Switch-games/The-Legend-of-Zelda-Tears-of-the-Kingdom-1576884.html&quot;&gt;Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom&lt;/a&gt;.  It&apos;s pretty good.  I preferred the mystique and lore of the first game, but I&apos;m having &lt;em&gt;so much fun&lt;/em&gt; building…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/b3b0eb11-6806-4291-9843-603ca1f51980?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Pudding — Week 19, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Short week, but I packed in tonnes, too much to write about really: We kicked off the thing I mentioned last week (although I haven't done my homework yet), and some other things got shipped.  Picked up a left-field…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/b42894a1-eec7-4459-a4b5-70e13408d9d8?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/b42894a1-eec7-4459-a4b5-70e13408d9d8</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 21:59:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short week, but I packed in &lt;em&gt;tonnes&lt;/em&gt;, too much to write about really: We kicked off the thing I mentioned last week (although I haven&apos;t done my homework yet), and some other things got shipped.  Picked up a left-field assignment that had me running around the building to speak to different departments, skimming research papers and writing a Jupyter notebook - all with a slightly stressful deadline that I barely hit - genuinely energising in a good way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had a follow-up occupational health appointment and pleasantly realised that while I&apos;m not where I was health-wise at the close of last year, I&apos;m much closer than I was.  Alas, my wait on the NHS continues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sometimes visibly doing &lt;em&gt;anything&lt;/em&gt; is more important than invisibly doing &lt;em&gt;the right thing&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;(And sometimes a comment in Alex&apos;s week-notes is a comment in Alex&apos;s week-notes!  Nothing to decode here, at least not this time)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Also learned why stroke order is important in kana.  Turns out that シ &amp;amp; ツ and ン &amp;amp; ソ are imminently readable once you…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/b42894a1-eec7-4459-a4b5-70e13408d9d8?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Fishing — Week 18, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bank holiday week this week, marked by a Monday road-trip to Winchester Service Station to watch the cherry blossom.   Since they were on the way, we also visited Stonehenge to get yelled at by security & Oxford to get…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/0e7d15c3-e714-41c1-96a4-f046cc782601?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/0e7d15c3-e714-41c1-96a4-f046cc782601</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 21:44:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bank holiday week this week, marked by a Monday road-trip to Winchester Service Station to watch the cherry blossom.   Since they were on the way, we also visited Stonehenge to get yelled at by security &amp;amp; Oxford to get yelled at by some cyclists.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visiting Oxford was really nice. Spending so much time there as a teen, I did a spot tour of the very centre, ending up at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greeneking-pubs.co.uk/pubs/oxfordshire/turf-tavern/&quot;&gt;Turf Tavern&lt;/a&gt; where I got to overhear the funniest debate about fishes and metaphysics.  What fish would you be?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spent a lot of time at work this week with the interactive publishing stack.  On top of recruiting for a small group to work on advancing it (kicking off soon™), I began documenting and building a dashboard for one of the most misunderstood bits of kit. The dashboard has already unpleasantly surprised me.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Splunk tip of the week: Build a dashboard by starting with data-sources, and chained searches &lt;em&gt;first&lt;/em&gt; before ever trying to do anything with the user interface.  It&apos;s faster and less confusing.  And remember…&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;| fields nameOfField1, nameOfField2&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/0e7d15c3-e714-41c1-96a4-f046cc782601?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: SkyTweeting — Week 17, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Upward trajectory this week: Started out feeling fairly unenthused and ended in a much better place.  There's power to figuring out what's bothering you, west-winging it and then trying to work through it.  Highly…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/ca79da85-4fca-4434-9e6c-9f975b0a9121?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/ca79da85-4fca-4434-9e6c-9f975b0a9121</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 22:35:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upward trajectory this week: Started out feeling fairly unenthused and ended in a much better place.  There&apos;s power to figuring out what&apos;s bothering you, west-winging it and then trying to work through it.  Highly recommended.  Bias for action is coming back, slowly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week started with a live-coding exercise with one of our journalists.  Quite often technologists will shadow or do various business processes (famously, Nandos encouraging people into kitchens) - so flipping it on its head is a bit novel and I hope we pulled it off?  Maybe we can do more?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We also had several major outages impacting the homepage this week.  Mostly out-of-hours and all slightly different.  All exhausting.  I got to write a bit of code to help mitigate the last one.  This long weekend is well-deserved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/efinlay24/&quot;&gt;Euan&lt;/a&gt;&apos;s last day was Friday.  Over forty people stopped by for his Thursday send-off - which speaks volumes - it&apos;s probably the most fun I&apos;ve had in a pub all year.  Friday was a very quiet day.  I&apos;ll miss…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ca79da85-4fca-4434-9e6c-9f975b0a9121?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Alarming — Week 16, 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Had a blast writing up how one of our systems (Magnet, for the interested) works.  Went in knowing a lot about how two parts of it worked.  I wrote out an outline around what its main request/response lifecycle worked…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/29cfad30-e864-4142-aad8-e66540df88c6?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/29cfad30-e864-4142-aad8-e66540df88c6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 21:42:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had a blast writing up how one of our systems (Magnet, for the interested) works.  Went in knowing a lot about how two parts of it worked.  I wrote out an outline around what its main request/response lifecycle worked like and started a deep-dive to fill it out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;While eating a lunch of katsu curry outside &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thened.com/&quot;&gt;The Ned&lt;/a&gt; on Monday, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.willhoward.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Will&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; I became unwitting participants of a China protest.  People walked past waving placards and handing out flyers with QR codes.  The chicken was pretty good, although the portion was huge and I struggled to finish.  Solid 8/10.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Men literally only want to talk about two things (Religion &amp;amp; History) and it&apos;s disgusting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuesday evening I left the office to meet the people at the boozy golfing social, and met the other people at the other boozy golfing social instead.  Then ran from the Seahorse to Nandos: You can do it in ~7 minutes on a good day, I did it in 8.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My group made an afternoon of teams running through their OKRs.  Genuinely heartwarming seeing so many…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/29cfad30-e864-4142-aad8-e66540df88c6?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>