<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:27:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Clicking — Week 03, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Busy week evenings-wise, but I really needed the social battery recharge it gave me - it’ll really help me lock-in on this whole language-learning thing, as well as my yearly theme. Bank holiday Monday I stayed in doing…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/de892dbd-fbf7-4e3e-956c-11ddfd6df546?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/de892dbd-fbf7-4e3e-956c-11ddfd6df546</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 13:14:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Busy week evenings-wise, but I really needed the social battery recharge it gave me - it’ll really help me lock-in on this whole language-learning thing, as well as my yearly theme.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bank holiday Monday I stayed in doing a few chores including a lot of laundry (first load of the year if you can believe it).  Some of the NA team were visiting town so I traded some texts and we met up for a little catch-up and an Okonomiyaki dinner in a Hiroshima themed restaurant.  Reminisced about a few things.  I’d been meaning to do this in the UK for yonks.  Probably my favourite moment of the week - which for this week was a feat.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I bought a radio-controlled clock.  It also has a feature where it beeps and flashes bright red every few minutes when it thinks that I’m likely to catch a cold.  It took me 30 minutes to figure out the pattern, and to figure out how to turn it off.  No, that’s it, no other anecdotes here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuesday evening, TPC was in town with S so we tore up the izakayas (and their…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/de892dbd-fbf7-4e3e-956c-11ddfd6df546?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Hauling — Week 2, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cleanly breaking weeks with travel seems to work great for me: It creates a neat time-bounded window, or a context if you will. But long-distance travel — which can span days — are a lot fuzzier.  These journeys can form…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/ea01a831-6b81-424a-b97f-369da32eccf5?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/ea01a831-6b81-424a-b97f-369da32eccf5</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 12:36:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cleanly breaking weeks with travel seems to work great for me: It creates a neat time-bounded window, or a context if you will. But long-distance travel — which can span &lt;em&gt;days&lt;/em&gt; — are a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt; fuzzier.  These journeys can form their own chapters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leon wraps consumed: 0&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hours slept: Not enough. :(&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my case, a chapter involving some extremely pointy elbows  and my rib-cage on the the first long leg of my journey back: Being allocated a middle-seat is the opposite of winning the lottery.  And it involved some &lt;em&gt;extremely&lt;/em&gt; tasty soup (at the pop-up Tin Kee) in Hong-Kong airport which almost made up for everything else...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Long-haul flights get the travel out of the way, but, after you’ve done one or two (ever) they aren’t exactly exciting. You learn rules, tricks, optimisations to make the lost time  easier to manage.  You begin to trade these with your fellow travellers: This route has better food, this seat is easier to sleep in, this airline is much cheaper, this airport is to be avoided at all costs.  Long-haul travel becomes a part of the identity - and not one I enjoy embracing.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ea01a831-6b81-424a-b97f-369da32eccf5?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Shipping — Week 1, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Back in London this week to do, as I put in an email, the “grown-up parts of moving out”.  Also to celebrate the new year. Or at least, that was the plan.  You know what they say about the best laid plans?  Well lots of…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/acbeea07-f027-4ba8-a9cf-6b4b6f0f3b10?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/acbeea07-f027-4ba8-a9cf-6b4b6f0f3b10</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 10:58:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back in London this week to do, as I put in an email, the “grown-up parts of moving out”.  Also to celebrate the new year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or at least, that &lt;em&gt;was&lt;/em&gt; the plan.  You know what they say about the best laid plans?  Well lots of things did &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; go to plan this week, but we still executed on all the important bits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Firstly, and most importantly, I neglected to review the in-flight entertainment over from Hong Kong.  I watched &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt11057302/&quot;&gt;Madame Web (2024)&lt;/a&gt;.  It was everything I hoped it would be, everything they said it would be, and so much less.  Lots of things happened for no coherent reason.  Solid cast though.  2/5.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🗑️ Visits to a bin: 16 round-trips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;💉 Blood tests: 1 draw&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🍻 Spoons visits: 4 meals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Secondly, Happy New Year!  I hope you enjoyed all the AI-generated HNYs.  I know I did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No, that other jigsaw wasn’t me, I honestly don’t know who put it there.  Please keep me posted: I’m ever-so-curious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After getting into my old flat, I went to say hi to CR.  Before I left, covered in sweat and airplane grime, I changed shirts — donning my “let’s get relfed” shirt — a moment of foreshadowing I would come to regret.  A coffee turned into a chat turned into a crawl, and before I knew it, we had made it into deepest Bermondsey and to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.poulet.biz/&quot;&gt;Poulet&lt;/a&gt; with some friendly Americans talking about tax.  At some point I got home having fulfilled the shirt’s prophecy.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/acbeea07-f027-4ba8-a9cf-6b4b6f0f3b10?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Spiriting — Week 52, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Oh gosh OK there’s quite a lot to get through. One of my most received message all week was, “Did you do KFC for Christmas?”.  Let’s cut straight to the chase so you can close this tab and get back to doomscrolling: the…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c363c1fb-8348-4502-8a65-3ed904f858e4?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c363c1fb-8348-4502-8a65-3ed904f858e4</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 23:58:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh gosh OK there’s quite a lot to get through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my most received message all week was, “Did you do KFC for Christmas?”.  Let’s cut straight to the chase so you can close this tab and get back to doomscrolling: the answer is &lt;strong&gt;no&lt;/strong&gt;.  I considered getting the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.timeout.com/tokyo/things-to-do/whats-the-deal-with-kfc-and-christmas-in-japan&quot;&gt;“Party Barrel”&lt;/a&gt; but — for the price it seemed like &lt;em&gt;horrible&lt;/em&gt; value (as well as a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt; of food) so I let it sell out.  Instead I picked up some Family Mart &amp;amp; Lawson fried chicken on the day, since they were still discounted but could come in &lt;em&gt;much&lt;/em&gt; smaller servings and I had that instead.  It was OK, and the roast chicken was borderline good (and not on KFC’s menu) but the fried chicken is - just that - fried chicken.  Picture in the little collage at the bottom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🎵 Number of times WHAM!&apos;d: 13 Last Christmasses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🎄 Christmas trees observed: 12 trees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🎅 Occurrences of the word &quot;Christmas&quot; in this article: 10&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For lack of any carols I pulled up the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/m00268s1&quot;&gt;Salvation Army’s yearly shindig on the BBC Sounds app&lt;/a&gt;.  I tried to listen to King’s College Chapel service about some number of carols and lessons — but it’s locked-up, gated and paywalled in so many ways outside of the UK that calling it a &lt;em&gt;religious&lt;/em&gt; ceremony seems &lt;em&gt;slightly&lt;/em&gt; inaccurate?  First year without hearing “Once in Royal David&apos;s City”. :^(&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c363c1fb-8348-4502-8a65-3ed904f858e4?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Triangulating — Week 51, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Spent a bit of this week debugging an infrastructure problem in an unfamiliar stack, and I’m really enjoying this period of discovery. Finding the problem was super affirming. Did a little intro in the engineering all…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/06fd4e46-dd48-4650-90aa-ec4ecde32479?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/06fd4e46-dd48-4650-90aa-ec4ecde32479</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 13:48:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spent a bit of this week debugging an infrastructure problem in an unfamiliar stack, and I’m really enjoying this period of discovery. Finding the problem was super affirming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did a little intro in the engineering all-hands. It’s hard to distill yourself into a slide but I think I got away with it.  (it had pictures and I got distracted mid-sentence by the chat trying to identify one!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Closed the week with the really big yearly all-hands. My head is still spinning!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Met up with JK &amp;amp; FT for dinner in a wine bar in Shimbashi to reminisce, and learned more about how all these visas work in the process. Also walked away slightly more optimistic about learning the language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The 21st was the winter solstice, and marking the occasion I went to the incredibly packed Hōjōji in Waseda to pick up a &lt;a href=&quot;https://katnsatoshiinjapan.blogspot.com/2020/12/ichiyo-raifuku.html&quot;&gt;Ichiyo Raifuku&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It needs attaching to the wall, facing the right direction at exactly midnight.  Unfortunately I didn’t have a surface facing the right direction, so instead it is now sitting on a…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/06fd4e46-dd48-4650-90aa-ec4ecde32479?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Verifying — Week 50, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Over the course of this week I made a few small break-throughs culminating in the realisation that: If after one week I suspected that cleaning, sorting and separating garbage was about to become a big part of my life…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/b61e1e29-750d-4cb2-87e3-37411b6c716b?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/b61e1e29-750d-4cb2-87e3-37411b6c716b</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 13:01:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the course of this week I made a few small break-throughs culminating in the realisation that: If after &lt;em&gt;one&lt;/em&gt; week I suspected that cleaning, sorting and separating garbage was about to become a big part of my life - Now after &lt;em&gt;three&lt;/em&gt; I know the remainder will become all about points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🤑 PayPay points earned: 1215pts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🍋 Vitamin C consumed: 3690mg&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🏬 Second-hand stores searched: 7&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before I left  I asked around a bit, “If I’m bringing a &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Omiyage&quot;&gt;souvenir/gift from our culture&lt;/a&gt; what should it be?”  The answers were many, but a consensus formed split somewhere between M&amp;amp;S Shortbread (you know, the blue tin? yes &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; blue tin. You know.) and tea.  Shortbread seemed more practical.  Anyway I brought it in this week and it went down a treat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally booked into some language lessons, starting in January...  I&apos;m excited!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One big change this week is that after a lot (and I mean a lot) of wrangling, my Apple account is now a Japanese one.  Meaning that at the cost of losing access to a few apps, I now have access to some incredibly useful ones: Such as PayPay.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/b61e1e29-750d-4cb2-87e3-37411b6c716b?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Orienting — Week 49, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week felt considerably more normal than last week. Maybe the routine got me somewhere. Maybe it’s just the jet lag having worn off. Maybe it’s the nature of the life-admin changing. Maybe it’s something else…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/8c466999-be7c-4fb0-9f32-6bd5ff22899a?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/8c466999-be7c-4fb0-9f32-6bd5ff22899a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 14:32:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week felt considerably more normal than last week. Maybe the routine got me somewhere. Maybe it’s just the jet lag having worn off. Maybe it’s the nature of the life-admin changing. Maybe it’s something else entirely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📼 Training videos watched: 5 hours&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🌯 Team lunches: 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🍵 Oi Ocha consumed: 3.5 litres&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Felt my first earthquake in yonks &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.data.jma.go.jp/multi/quake/quake_detail.html?eventID=20241204191551&amp;amp;lang=jp&quot;&gt;on Tuesday evening&lt;/a&gt;. It’s been a while (maybe 5 years?) so I’d forgotten how it feels. Intensity 1 so nobody else was even remotely fussed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was my first week at work, and I’m feeling the same sense of awe and wonder one does exploring any new world. I’m pretty excited!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Part of onboarding, or, I guess, being in a large company is needing an evergreen way of introducing yourself - and so one of my tasks involved writing a page about myself for an internal documentation hub.  (It also includes a link to the about me page on this blog, which, is somewhat out of date - sorry!)  It’s kind-of great, and reading others I realised that there’s lots to strike up conversations about.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/8c466999-be7c-4fb0-9f32-6bd5ff22899a?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Not Unpacking — Week 48, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[This was one of these weird weeks where I didn’t have much on - because it was my time off between two jobs. It was a bit like a staycation?  But in a new place?  Lots of life-admin. Where did I leave you?  Ah yes…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/5db865f1-cefa-4378-a4c3-d315da8cb8cc?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/5db865f1-cefa-4378-a4c3-d315da8cb8cc</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 10:59:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was one of these weird weeks where I didn’t have much on - because it was my time off between two jobs. It was a bit like a staycation?  But in a new place?  Lots of life-admin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where did I leave you?  Ah yes, watching Garfield on the plane.  Tray table went up, we landed, we taxied and we disembarked. Now for the moment I was dreading: I went to the immigration counter for residents and was presented with my very own residence card.  Phew - that was easy.  And then both it and my passport were taken from me and I was asked to take a seat and wait.  Uh-oh.  After what felt like an eternity (a few minutes) both were handed back and I was allowed through: I’d given the wrong post-code.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Collected my bags, and met an agent who handed me my SIM card, keys, and a few other bits I’d need, before escorting me to a taxi.  On the way I plug in my new SIM card on the way, message a few people to let them know I’ve landed.  Before I knew it, we’ve arrived and I’m standing alone on a brand new street with two suitcases, a backpack and some documents to keep me company.  And I now understand the confusion at border control: There&apos;s no building by the name I&apos;ve been given.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/5db865f1-cefa-4378-a4c3-d315da8cb8cc?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Not Packing — Week 47, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[This was my last week at the FT, something I kept very close to my chest.  It surprised a few people.  Truth be told it didn’t really sink in for me until this week.  I spent the entire week trying to remain composed…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/198b3ab3-2b8d-4da8-8881-1262d3eb2366?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/198b3ab3-2b8d-4da8-8881-1262d3eb2366</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 13:13:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was my last week at the FT, something I kept &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; close to my chest.  It surprised a few people.  Truth be told it didn’t really sink in for me until this week.  I spent the entire week trying to remain composed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why leave?  The exit survey poses that question expectantly.  It’s simple: I’m relocating and circumstances [editor’s note: &lt;em&gt;including&lt;/em&gt; but not only my age] made now the right time.  Where to?  Tokyo.  I’ve wanted to do it since 2017, so, you know.  That’s why.  This has been in the works for a  hot minute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🥪 Pret eaten: 7 sandwiches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🚶 People who said they plan to visit Japan next year: 12&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🎬 Movies watched: 6 films&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Between packing and leaving a job.  I began the week with a todo list as long as my arm...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many people reached out to chat.  Some wished me luck.  Some said kind things. All of them — some of whom might be reading this — in reaching out made leaving just that little bit harder.  Thank-you?  But, really.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most common question I got was “Do you speak any japanese?” to which I answered “少し話せます”, or, a little. The second most common question was “Are you packed yet?” to which I answered “No, but that’s not the problem - it’s getting rid of my furniture and all the other things I’m not packing!”...&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/198b3ab3-2b8d-4da8-8881-1262d3eb2366?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Red Arrow — Week 46, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello from sunny Birmingham.  The weather has been alternating between rain and grey all weekend. This week in data: Magazines issues thrown into a recycling bin: 37 Heartfelt emails sent: 9 Spent some time steeling…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c6208cb1-57cb-4cc0-986e-19a6856c391a?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c6208cb1-57cb-4cc0-986e-19a6856c391a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 22:37:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hello from sunny Birmingham.  The weather has been alternating between rain and grey all weekend.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week in data:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Magazines issues thrown into a recycling bin: 37&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Heartfelt emails sent: 9&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spent some time steeling myself for a few conversations that I thought would be difficult.  No, reader, they all went swimmingly well.  I’m genuinely pleasantly surprised.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I got here in a van: Despite having multiple train lines from Birmingham to London, it’s somehow still quicker to drive from my flat in London to my parents home in Birmingham. Or at least, it should have been: It took &lt;em&gt;nearly 30 minutes&lt;/em&gt; to drive down Putney High Street alone.  Sheesh.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bluesky is really popping off huh.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;L helped me with some more chores. Later we played some music, &lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/axwnmusic/2024-11-17-set&quot;&gt;first semi-seriously&lt;/a&gt; and later after giving up &lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/axwnmusic/genresweep-afterparty-2&quot;&gt;just committed some crimes&lt;/a&gt; with my apparently now &lt;em&gt;broken&lt;/em&gt; mixer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Despite the (painful, at least to me) mistakes that was still a pretty technically advanced set and I&apos;m pretty proud of how far I&apos;ve come since picking DJing back up in 2020. It&apos;s such a fun hobby. And it&apos;s a very different, really intimate — and almost &lt;em&gt;therapeutic&lt;/em&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c6208cb1-57cb-4cc0-986e-19a6856c391a?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>