<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 06:35:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Yvaga — Week 33, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[My love-hate relationship with Google Colab continues: I’m back to loving it, brought on by its secrets management which makes it easy to repeat sensitive analysis. A new trick which made my week is writing a dataframe…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/07374c72-69b6-4353-8d3a-0ead50324933?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/07374c72-69b6-4353-8d3a-0ead50324933</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 20:32:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My love-hate relationship with &lt;a href=&quot;https://colab.research.google.com&quot;&gt;Google Colab&lt;/a&gt; continues: I’m back to loving it, brought on by &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/GoogleColab/status/1719798406195867814&quot;&gt;its secrets management&lt;/a&gt; which makes it easy to repeat sensitive analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A new trick which made my week is writing a dataframe to Google Sheets for wrangling/sharing: &lt;a href=&quot;https://gspread-dataframe.readthedocs.io/&quot;&gt;gspread-dataframe&lt;/a&gt;’s &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;set_with_dataframe&lt;/code&gt; makes it so easy I can’t believe I hadn’t used it before!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/music/article/2024/jun/06/charli-xcx-brat-review-insecurity-obliterating-anthems-by-pops-most-human-superstar&quot;&gt;It’s a brat summer&lt;/a&gt;, late I know. I &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; 365’s acid line.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highlight of the week was NL’s birthday which started at The George, featured some wholesome conversations and ended at &lt;a href=&quot;https://mallowlondon.com/&quot;&gt;Mallow&lt;/a&gt;, who do a pretty mean burger.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thursday saw both the formation of the Coxinha Crew, and me getting a detailed Zodiac reading so close-to-home (yet seemingly devoid of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Barnum_effect&quot;&gt;Barnum statements&lt;/a&gt;) that I’m &lt;em&gt;still&lt;/em&gt; reeling all the way over here on Sunday.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ate some mid pizza and then watched &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt18412256&quot;&gt;Alien: Romulus (2024)&lt;/a&gt; with TM &amp;amp; LF: Loved the vibe, it felt a lot like the first film. ScreenX added nothing. “That Scene” was A Lot. Computers went bleep. Synthetics were thought-provoking. “Non…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/07374c72-69b6-4353-8d3a-0ead50324933?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Mending — Week 32, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Not much happened this past fortnight. I came down with Covid, and reader, it hit me hard. Like not leaving the apartment hard. 25/25 on Joe two weeks in a row tho. Wrote some pretty cool Splunk queries: Did you know…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/40fcf41f-757b-4312-8229-2bcddc303db9?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/40fcf41f-757b-4312-8229-2bcddc303db9</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 22:53:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not much happened this past fortnight. I came down with Covid, and reader, it hit me &lt;em&gt;hard&lt;/em&gt;. Like not leaving the apartment hard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;25/25 on Joe two weeks in a row tho.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wrote some pretty cool Splunk queries: Did you know that after adding categories to your events (&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;eval category=case(like(), &quot;Category 1&quot;, like(), &quot;Category 2&quot;, 1=1, &quot;Default&quot;)&lt;/code&gt;) you can then use an &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;xyseries&lt;/code&gt; to transform them into a columnar structure?  A few &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;transpose&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;table&lt;/code&gt;s later and now you’re cooking. &lt;em&gt;(without a spreadsheet!)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With not much I could actually do, I picked &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.igdb.com/games/the-legend-of-zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom&quot;&gt;Tears of the Kingdom&lt;/a&gt; back up after &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2815bfca-621e-4c87-b237-4e19a87e5a47&quot;&gt;unlocking all the Lightroots last year&lt;/a&gt; and beat all 120 shrines, all 32 sky shrines and a bunch of side-quests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuing the streak, I booted up &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.igdb.com/games/the-legend-of-zelda-breath-of-the-wild&quot;&gt;Breath of the Wild&lt;/a&gt; for the first time since 2017 and completed all 120 shrines there too and some of the EX shrines.  At some point the game design started to feel so tedious that my inner completionist took over and now here we are.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To keep my distance from the screens, I finally split the Switch&apos;s joycons. It&apos;s a really liberating play-style and I now really wish &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/40fcf41f-757b-4312-8229-2bcddc303db9?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Jubilation — Week 30, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Highlight of the week was our first-ever away-day for tech-leads and principals in my team. After a great ice-breaker we ran through many group activities including charting all the technical interactions needed to serve…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/d5d8284c-ca98-4242-bfb0-2ba590465b87?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/d5d8284c-ca98-4242-bfb0-2ba590465b87</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 21:51:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highlight of the week was our first-ever away-day for tech-leads and principals in my team. After a great ice-breaker we ran through many group activities including charting all the technical interactions needed to serve articles to users, which I loved but which pulled on enough of my esoteric knowledge that it was surprisingly draining: We covered an entire wall. Conversations over the day were all a genuine joy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For a proposal I’m working on, I’ve been combing through many systems and codebases to identify how they interact with a notorious area of our architecture.  I’ve learned a fair bit about the methodology: I tried to automate classification several ways but found the results &lt;em&gt;consistently&lt;/em&gt; variable and unreliable.  In the end generating dependency trees starting with our software catalogue, charting in a spreadsheet and then reading parts of source-code by hand has been far more effective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s always DNS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No improvements to the site this week, instead I focussed on the CMS: I write a lot on my phone and for the longest time have been unable to write on this website without a computer.  This week I &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/alexwilson/frontend/pull/2730&quot;&gt;moved my CMS to the Decap distribution&lt;/a&gt; and added in &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/alexwilson/frontend/issues/2731&quot;&gt;styles to make it mobile friendly&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/d5d8284c-ca98-4242-bfb0-2ba590465b87?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Calculating — Week 29, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[A week of noteworthy lunches. Even my Sainsbury’s meal-deal on Wednesday cooccurred with fun chat.  Spent a lot of time in VCV Rack in the evenings working on dangerous new hobby. My team had our first all-in-person…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/275ba2af-ae17-4cfe-bc40-4543f41510cc?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/275ba2af-ae17-4cfe-bc40-4543f41510cc</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 22:39:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A week of noteworthy lunches. Even my Sainsbury’s meal-deal on Wednesday cooccurred with fun chat.  Spent a lot of time in VCV Rack in the evenings working on dangerous new hobby.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My team had our first all-in-person retro in a little while and after our normal retro app refused to work, got to use real post-it notes on a whiteboard.  So analogue - I loved every second.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What brought on the in-person retro?  We welcomed a new member to our team this week, and I’m incredibly excited to work with him: We’re working across the same areas and there’s so much interesting work coming up!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;You see, it all comes back to google sheets?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had a 2-hour debrief on my &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facet5global.com/&quot;&gt;Facet5 profile&lt;/a&gt;, and while I suspect I answered some questions strangely and potentially distorted my scores, the general gist felt bang-on.  I’m a “&lt;a href=&quot;https://family.facet5gps.com/promoter/&quot;&gt;Promoter&lt;/a&gt;”.  Lots of interesting things that I can now work on, because I see my blindspots more clearly than after exercises &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/cdf6575f-d01f-43bb-8a26-eb1530ca9952/&quot;&gt;like the Johari window&lt;/a&gt;.  I’m hyped.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week’s major update to the blog was &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/alexwilson/frontend/pull/2715&quot;&gt;an overhaul of the typography, implementing a fluid scale&lt;/a&gt;, meaning text is now bigger and more legible for…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/275ba2af-ae17-4cfe-bc40-4543f41510cc?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Post-Technical — Week 28, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[The aftermath of the election has been smooth at work. While we haven’t run a retrospective yet, we successfully sped back up to our normal pace of changes without any major issues. Already we’re in the throes of a…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/97c9a70f-3d45-4d96-94dd-3071f6af2dcd?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/97c9a70f-3d45-4d96-94dd-3071f6af2dcd</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 22:35:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The aftermath of &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c9a8468a-61ad-4e0d-bb2a-ec2ddc5d897f&quot;&gt;the election&lt;/a&gt; has been smooth at work. While we haven’t run a retrospective yet, we successfully sped back up to our normal pace of changes without any major issues. Already we’re in the throes of a heated US Election so the focus on reliability continues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At work my primary focus this week has been identifying and classifying consumers of a core [but not well understood] capability. I’ve been combing through our infrastructure accounts, our secrets storage and even our internal software catalog - and got told off for hitting it with too many API calls! So far I’ve identified at least 40 unique consumers, and have begun asking people about how they work: This might be big.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This phase of (experimentally) wearing white might need to come to an end: Mysterious stains have appeared on a shirt that I can’t work out or get out.  Any and all tips are welcome!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recently my dear colleague Lee has been going through the same incredibly scary health condition that hit me last year. We’ve spoken about it: I wanted to say what I wish anyone had told me at the time. I’m seriously impressed at his bravery, honesty and articulation in in writing about it. Please follow his journey: &lt;a href=&quot;https://leemoody.co.uk/blog/weeknotes/91/&quot;&gt;Dissected note&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://leemoody.co.uk/blog/weeknotes/92/&quot;&gt;Horizontal note&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/97c9a70f-3d45-4d96-94dd-3071f6af2dcd?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Electing — Week 27, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[UK Election this week.  My week is evenly split into three: Pre-Election, Election Night and Recovery. Pre-election my focus at work was end-to-end testing a few scenarios that were theoretically fine, but had not been…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c9a8468a-61ad-4e0d-bb2a-ec2ddc5d897f?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c9a8468a-61ad-4e0d-bb2a-ec2ddc5d897f</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 11:21:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UK Election this week.  My week is evenly split into three: Pre-Election, Election Night and Recovery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pre-election my focus at work was end-to-end testing a few scenarios that were &lt;em&gt;theoretically&lt;/em&gt; fine, but had not been tested. I’m super glad we did this because we identified a few bottlenecks that would have been tricky to diagnose in a worst-case scenario.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had the first of several executive-coaching sessions this week to discuss things including how to improve my adaptability: First step is doing a personality assessment which will help me identify my innate behaviours versus my learned behaviours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The night of the election was fantastic: I was doing the 10PM-4AM shift, so shifted my sleep schedule slightly in the days before. On Thursday I woke up at midday, went to my polling station and went to a sauna session in Bermondsey before arriving at the office around 4:30PM via Rosslyn.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our systems ran stable (if a little hot) so things were mostly quiet on the night - So I focussed on…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c9a8468a-61ad-4e0d-bb2a-ec2ddc5d897f?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Mealdealing — Week 26, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gosh it’s been hot this week. So hot it’s hard to sleep. Went to a comedy course on Monday and have ended up on a TikTok.  Dissecting jokes is good fun, the homework includes looking at different techniques - this week…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/2316421a-4edc-43cd-b983-70e1c9553bf4?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/2316421a-4edc-43cd-b983-70e1c9553bf4</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 19:45:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gosh it’s been hot this week. So hot it’s hard to sleep.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went to a comedy course on Monday and have ended up on a TikTok.  Dissecting jokes is good fun, the homework includes looking at different techniques - this week was lists.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not one but two leaving drinks this week.  Apparently my Sainsbury’s meal-deal of choice (Southern Chicken Wrap, Yoghurt &amp;amp; Coconut Water) is low-tier.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Got into a small war with UberEats over a missing latte and some chicken selects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having installed Ableton on this computer, I’ve been learning more about how synthesis works instead of working on any of my existing tracks. Recently I’ve been focussing on FM synthesis. Maybe a good goal is to write some visual explainer posts?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of my slow-burn side NLP projects has been to vectorise and classify the contents of this blog, and I spent a decent chunk of the weekend working on that.  After talking about it for two years, I finally strung together several parametized Jupiter notebooks with &lt;a href=&quot;https://papermill.readthedocs.io/&quot;&gt;Papermill&lt;/a&gt; - all orchestrated with &lt;a href=&quot;https://metaflow.org/&quot;&gt;Metaflow&lt;/a&gt; - and it works so well that it feels like magic.  Lovely MLOps stack.  Hopefully…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/2316421a-4edc-43cd-b983-70e1c9553bf4?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Fargo — Week 25, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week was marked by the duality of my team’s quarterly planning day and my department’s yearly rounders outing. Had a real blast at both seeing and chatting with people who I don’t normally get the chance to. During…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/62be874e-baab-4159-913f-924fb5f701dc?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/62be874e-baab-4159-913f-924fb5f701dc</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 21:06:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week was marked by the duality of my team’s quarterly planning day and my department’s yearly rounders outing. Had a real blast at both seeing and chatting with people who I don’t normally get the chance to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;During rounders we incepted everybody to skip going to the normal pub in favour of one far more accessible and public transport friendly. Despite a brazen bag theft, it went well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dealt with an outage where, even after restoring service, labelling the exact root cause proved tricky: It was compounded and began in a different part of the organisation. How it spread was the interesting factor, and I’m really looking forward to the retrospective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sanshinkai.uk/okinawa-day/&quot;&gt;Okinawa day&lt;/a&gt; was the closest thing I’ve seen to a Japanese festival in London. Lots of elated folk singing/dancing and a solid selection of snacks from the area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt14914430/&quot;&gt;Unfrosted&lt;/a&gt; was pretty damn funny. That Seinfeld guy could be a star.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doctor Who season finale was &lt;em&gt;good&lt;/em&gt;, but, felt rushed? Lots of things happened quickly, and they &lt;a href=&quot;https://x.com/jblacksomething/status/1804526773964575025&quot;&gt;didn’t all add up&lt;/a&gt;. I’m still hooked — but I feel like I did after…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/62be874e-baab-4159-913f-924fb5f701dc?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: The Italian Job — Week 24, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Theseus’s paradox poses the question: If you take a classic dish and substitute every major ingredient, is it the same classic dish, or is it something entirely new?  Call in now with your answers. Whirlwind week.  Got a…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c174a153-55ca-4c15-a123-84c65b781ebd?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c174a153-55ca-4c15-a123-84c65b781ebd</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 22:06:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Theseus’s paradox poses the question: If you take a classic dish and substitute every major ingredient, is it the same classic dish, or is it something entirely new?  Call in now with your answers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whirlwind week.  Got a lot done towards reliability and enjoyed getting into the details of some new technical problems.  My “there’s a debate l8r!” reminder posts have also become a meme. :(&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some very positive (and kind) unexpected feedback threw me this week because of the perspective it prompted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://innervisionsalchemy.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Innervisions Alchemy&lt;/a&gt; is a new wellness space in Bermondsey and to fundraise they’re collaborating with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.community-sauna.co.uk/community-sauna-network&quot;&gt;Community Sauna Network&lt;/a&gt;. Went there on Thursday after work and had a blast. English summer in 2024 - it turns out - makes for perfect sauna weather.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My albatross is still there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apparently M &amp;amp; I are trendsetters? That’s what a popular instagram account said - and it’s on the internet so it must be true.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Saw &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/paranoidlondon&quot;&gt;Paranoid London&lt;/a&gt; on Saturday, outdoors in the pouring rain. The event ran between 12 to 9, and the other DJs who played were &lt;em&gt;alright&lt;/em&gt;, but a little ambient/house-y for the mood I was in.  My namesake (&lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/pato&quot;&gt;Pato&lt;/a&gt;) dropped a few bangers.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/stories/highlights/17981840663540013/&quot;&gt;All worth it for that acid-heavy Paranoid London goodness&lt;/a&gt;.  Wore hearing protection &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ae6b20c6-751b-4ce9-8a73-78328483d403/&quot;&gt;this time&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c174a153-55ca-4c15-a123-84c65b781ebd?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Hopping — Week 23, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[EU Election has turned out interesting, huh? New election just dropped. Spent Tuesday’s leaders debate looking at some dashboards. Understanding how a timeseries is derived is a lot more exciting than hearing soundbite…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/977a1af3-f0a2-4ee2-8591-278fbace8d8e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/977a1af3-f0a2-4ee2-8591-278fbace8d8e</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 21:55:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EU Election has turned out interesting, huh? New election just dropped.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spent Tuesday’s leaders debate looking at some dashboards. Understanding how a timeseries is derived is a lot more exciting than hearing soundbite after soundbite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A decent chunk of my spare time this week has gone into the haunted forest that is design-decisions in my blog. Like the typography.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week I’ve also been migrating my collection of music production tools from my old laptop to the laptop I bought at the start of the year. I couldn’t get my old recording setup to work, so I built a new one using &lt;a href=&quot;https://rogueamoeba.com/loopback/&quot;&gt;Loopback&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://rogueamoeba.com/audiohijack/&quot;&gt;Audio Hijack&lt;/a&gt; - and it supports broadcasting!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Testing the new setup (and having really enjoyed it last week) &lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/axwnmusic/2024-06-03-set&quot;&gt;I played some music pretty fast&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ended a night of Clapham bar-hopping in Phonox. Their DJ booth is &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; impressive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/977a1af3-f0a2-4ee2-8591-278fbace8d8e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>