<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 06:47:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Anthropocene — Week 23, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[A few puzzle-pieces slotted into place this week.  People have noticed my use of the word なるほど.  Closed a meeting at work with 頑張っていきましょう！ to some smiles. This week in data: Voxpops dodged: 3 reporters Creepy-crawlies…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/72497298-d029-4249-8ab0-a43712fb02e7?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/72497298-d029-4249-8ab0-a43712fb02e7</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 14:17:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A few puzzle-pieces slotted into place this week.  People have noticed my use of the word なるほど.  Closed a meeting at work with &lt;em&gt;頑張っていきましょう！&lt;/em&gt; to some smiles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week in data:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Voxpops dodged: 3 reporters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creepy-crawlies spotted: 7 large bugs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regrets: 1 big mistake&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We’re still working on the “How does Alex get home internet?” saga. This isn’t so high priority, because, you know, unlimited 5G. But it’s become clear this is more of a saga than an check-list item.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MT bullied me into sending a message.  A good friend.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After putting public speaking off for ages (other than a &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/06fd4e46-dd48-4650-90aa-ec4ecde32479&quot;&gt;brief self-introduction&lt;/a&gt;, and right before that, &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/198b3ab3-2b8d-4da8-8881-1262d3eb2366&quot;&gt;my leaving speech&lt;/a&gt;), I gave a progress update at an all-hands.  It went well, and it felt easy even, and I left it feeling unfazed.  Whatever has made me overthink public speaking recently, I seem to be getting over it?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Workload has climbed, &lt;em&gt;ever-so-slightly&lt;/em&gt;, this week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can I talk about how &lt;em&gt;good&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mori.art.museum/en/exhibitions/machine_love/&quot;&gt;Machine Love&lt;/a&gt; was?  It was an exhibition at the Mori Art Museum on perhaps my favourite topic: In a cybernetic wold, what does it mean to be human?  I loved it all.  Three particular standouts were &lt;a href=&quot;http://ayoungkim.com/wp/3col/delivery-dancers-sphere-2022&quot;&gt;Delivery Dancer’s Sphere&lt;/a&gt; by Kim Ayoung (unfortunately not available online), &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.calculatingempires.com/&quot;&gt;Calculating Empires&lt;/a&gt; by Kate Crawford &amp;amp; Vladan Joler, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://luyang.asia/2023/05/20/doku-the-self/&quot;&gt;DOKU The Self&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/72497298-d029-4249-8ab0-a43712fb02e7?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Stinky — Week 22, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[If the past few weeks had a tag-cloud, the word “lunch” would be somewhere near the top. Made a small breakthrough with a complicated but annoying framework problem, which banked me some serious JFDI energy. Encountered…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/6c125f69-a2a0-49b7-a3ff-4bea263e9b9d?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/6c125f69-a2a0-49b7-a3ff-4bea263e9b9d</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 14:23:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the past few weeks had a tag-cloud, the word “lunch” would be somewhere near the top.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made a small breakthrough with a complicated but annoying framework problem, which banked me some serious JFDI energy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Encountered the best machine mistranslation, maybe, of all time which had me laughing for hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What’s the news? At the weekend met TPC for some &lt;em&gt;excellent&lt;/em&gt; chicken (and TBH even better pork) at a place with a mahoosive queue, followed by a spot visit to a very special HUB. There I was given a scratch card, which won a me game of rock-paper-scissors against the house, and a chance to win the &quot;A+&quot; prize.  My scissors trumped our bartender’s paper.  What did I win? A cute whiskey tumbler: Quite chuffed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With Pioneer DJ’s rebrand to AlphaTheta, they’ve brought new design language and products which look phenomenal.  The OmnisDuo is &lt;em&gt;so close&lt;/em&gt; to the entry-level XDJ I’ve spent years wishing for, that every way it falls short feels disappointing.  Resigned to getting a FLX4 at this point.&lt;/li&gt;…&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/6c125f69-a2a0-49b7-a3ff-4bea263e9b9d?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Billing — Week 21, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello, it is me, the floating head of Jor-El. Monumental week: My new bed & sofa arrived.  There’s nothing like a month on a futon (on a laminate wooden floor) to help you appreciate the wonders of a firm mattress.  And…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/7a79c2ef-55a7-47ba-b52d-57ff98f0288b?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/7a79c2ef-55a7-47ba-b52d-57ff98f0288b</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hello, it is me, the floating head of Jor-El.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monumental week: My new bed &amp;amp; sofa arrived.  There’s nothing like a month on a futon (on a laminate wooden floor) to help you appreciate the wonders of a firm mattress.  And having a sofa is game-changing: Now I can drink coffee.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Got a nice shout-out in the departmental all-hands (thank-you!). Also an announcement about the formation of a new central team, which I’m joining part-time and am pretty chuffed about.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s H1 performance review season.  Which, for me, is a great time to reflect on this whole being-an-IC-again thing.  Mirroring my time as an EM, separating the two roles is difficult: I find it far too easy to call on my EM tool-kit in some situations.  But no regrets so far: We trust in the great IC-EM pendulum.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thursday and Friday evenings were spent hanging out until the wee hours.  Thursday I split a cab, and Friday I walked home: my new address is already paying off big time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very glad to see a few people I hadn’t seen in…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/7a79c2ef-55a7-47ba-b52d-57ff98f0288b?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Easy Numbers — Week 20, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Kicking off being proper-grown-up-like by going to the gym and to the dentist this week. Every day I track a few things, including my mood and a few sentiment scores, but I didn’t need these numbers to tell me that wasn…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/a1aaa867-ada5-4668-bdc2-d136e8ba7523?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/a1aaa867-ada5-4668-bdc2-d136e8ba7523</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 14:17:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kicking off being proper-grown-up-like by going to the gym &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; to the dentist this week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Every day I track a few things, including my mood and a few sentiment scores, but I didn’t need these numbers to tell me that wasn’t a great week.  Endorphins from the gym and a few nice meals kept me going.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Papers Club was &lt;em&gt;exceptional&lt;/em&gt; this week.  Not only were we joined by a new member, but I think we hit a record number of “Aha” moments.  The paper we&apos;re reading has some fairly complicated but crucial maths.  The difference was applying the advice of my high-school maths teacher PJ to the equations in the paper, “When in doubt, try it out, with easy numbers”.  So, e.g., a vector of size 2, and a layer of size 3, that sort of thing.  Timeless advice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Joked about a dinner feeling like a product management meetup a few weeks ago, and, well, it happened again over Duck on Friday.  Perhaps the universe is trying to tell me something.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I now have a map with good coffee places that I personally vouch for.  It’s still incomplete while I backload places like London.  But you might enjoy?  &lt;a href=&quot;https://maps.app.goo.gl/QkkzxM89yudGxAKWA&quot;&gt;Map here&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/a1aaa867-ada5-4668-bdc2-d136e8ba7523?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Gold-ish — Week 19, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week was one I that have been dreading for a decade. Firstly and most importantly, yes, the rumours are true.  I did buy a microwave with a flat-folding door.  It doubles as an oven and came with the cutest little…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/4db1831b-af79-421b-ac38-15c2325faac3?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/4db1831b-af79-421b-ac38-15c2325faac3</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 12:19:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week was one I that have been dreading for a decade.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Firstly and most importantly, yes, &lt;strong&gt;the rumours are true&lt;/strong&gt;.  I &lt;em&gt;did&lt;/em&gt; buy a microwave with a flat-folding door.  It doubles as an oven and came with the cutest little baking tray, perfect for the sourdough baking obsession which the stats say is likely heading my way in the next few years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My ambitious-yet-still-approval-seeking younger self set high expectations for where I would be, who I would be and what I would have done by the time this week came around.  And more recently, since the close brush at the start of ’23, there have been times when I thought that I might not see this week.  But here we are.  We did it.  This week I turned 30.  And, consequentially, I no longer qualify for a UK rail card.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the end I&apos;m not really sure what all the fuss was about.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Golden_Week_(Japan)&quot;&gt;Golden Week&lt;/a&gt;, or &quot;GW&quot;, is four bank holidays which normally create an entire week of downtime.  This year two of them were at weekend.  Back home, when a bank holiday occurs on a Saturday &lt;em&gt;or&lt;/em&gt; Sunday, the next available weekday becomes a substitute holiday.  So consecutive days become consecutive holidays.  Japan has a similar rule, but only for Sundays.  Meaning that this year’s Golden Week was really more of a “Gold-ish-Monday…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/4db1831b-af79-421b-ac38-15c2325faac3?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Robotic Cat — Week 18, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Another month, another ward office trip. This time it’s Chiyoda, and instead of having translated forms, they have actual interpreters. The hardest part is writing out kanji. Done and done in record time. This week we go…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/543304fc-c025-4239-9a1f-32351fe06a0c?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/543304fc-c025-4239-9a1f-32351fe06a0c</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 12:46:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Another month, another ward office trip. This time it’s Chiyoda, and instead of having translated forms, they have actual interpreters. The hardest part is writing out kanji. Done and done in record time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week we go to war.  In my new bathroom, there is a smell which I can’t identify, locate or label.  It’s not an unpleasant smell, but, it’s definitely not a pleasant one either.  It smells a lot like soap, but, &lt;em&gt;sweet&lt;/em&gt;?  Research and conversations suggest that it’s the product of a “bio-film”, which is a brand new type of home maintenance problem that I’d rather not have learned about.  I steadily arm myself with every category of cleaning product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wrapping Monday I run (literally) from work in the pouring rain to see US, one of my favourite all-time people who is in town for one night and one night only.  Over reasonably-priced yakiniku we talk bikes and the expo in a room which — by medium of sharpie — very loudly shares my politics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Okonomiyaki in Sumida-city is lots of fun, but…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/543304fc-c025-4239-9a1f-32351fe06a0c?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Candle — Week 17, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[When leaving the UK, I got a lot of advice. One bit stood out above the rest. “Find somewhere to live which reminds you that you’re in Japan”.  This week I moved into that place.  It’s within spitting distance of a…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/5432df00-8120-44ea-8b7d-b4de3ff5174c?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/5432df00-8120-44ea-8b7d-b4de3ff5174c</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 11:58:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When leaving the UK, I got a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt; of advice. One bit stood out above the rest. “Find somewhere to live which reminds you that you’re in Japan”.  This week I moved into that place.  It’s within spitting distance of a centroid and from my window I can &lt;em&gt;just about&lt;/em&gt; see the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/NTT_Docomo_Yoyogi_Building&quot;&gt;NTT Docomo Yoyogi building&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There was some work stuff too this week, but I’ll spare you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The actual move was very, very easy.  Faster than last time.    The hard part was actually cleaning my last apartment (by my count, making it the third time this year!).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&apos;ll miss living in Azabu though.  It made me nostalgic for my flat in Sofia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only trouble with moving in for the first time, during peak moving season, is that I own no furniture.  Zip.  Nothing.  Nada.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So anyway, I’m temporarily sleeping on AB’s old futon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bought some essentials: Blinds, towels, kettle and a hair dryer which looks &amp;amp; sounds like a Dyson Supersonic but definitely isn’t.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some reprieve at a Sushiro dinner (which was considerably more reasonably priced…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/5432df00-8120-44ea-8b7d-b4de3ff5174c?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Eggs — Week 16, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This was a cyclical week. Went to Microsoft HQ for hands-on training with Azure AI services. There I built a tool for getting answers from a large collection of technical documentation.  It comprised a processing…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/67faf168-26d5-4f38-8aa1-df86622e0f06?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/67faf168-26d5-4f38-8aa1-df86622e0f06</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:18:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This was a cyclical week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went to Microsoft HQ for hands-on training with Azure AI services. There I built a tool for getting answers from a large collection of technical documentation.  It comprised a processing pipeline and an agent, and because I have trust issues, I extended it to issue citations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This actually blew my mind.  A few years and a few teams ago, I worked on a similar problem so I’m familiar with the NLP problem space: Long months of experimentation were reduced to a few keystrokes and clicks over an afternoon.  The commodification of tooling right now is impressive, and I walked out shocked.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shipped the largest codebase change I’ve made recently affecting 364 files, which required a few weeks of lead-in and planning.  OMG I&apos;m so relieved it’s over.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went for dinner with some folks working data where we talked news and I tried my very very best to sell the UK and London as places to &lt;em&gt;at least&lt;/em&gt; visit.  Unfortunately &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Birmingham_bin_strike&quot;&gt;recent headlines about Birmingham&lt;/a&gt; made it impossible to sell going there.  C’mon people, how else are we getting people to visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.purecraftbars.com/&quot;&gt;PureCraft&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/67faf168-26d5-4f38-8aa1-df86622e0f06?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Flowering — Week 13, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cherry blossom season is upon us, and it’s gorgeous.  The parks are chokka.  Unfortunately the same cannot be said of the weather: It has been cold, and dark, and damp, and miserable all week. Between the weather and…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/d12df8f8-cc9d-4463-a51b-fc44dad1e16e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/d12df8f8-cc9d-4463-a51b-fc44dad1e16e</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 12:51:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cherry blossom season is upon us, and it’s gorgeous.  The parks are chokka.  Unfortunately the same cannot be said of the weather: It has been cold, and dark, and damp, and miserable all week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Between the weather and immediately jumping back into work, even though it was a few days, I was suffering a proper holiday hangover this week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Many years ago I read &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/44919&quot;&gt;“Working Effectively with Legacy Code”&lt;/a&gt;, and it excited me to work with gnarly codebases.  Well, let’s just say I burned a lot of that excitement this week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After missing 3 lessons in a row, Japanese class was &lt;em&gt;incredibly&lt;/em&gt; rough.  We made it, in the end, but wow there were moments where I doubted myself.  Who’d have guessed that learning a language is hard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very thought provoking catch-up on Wednesday evening. 😅&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had a university final during the week.  It caught me by surprise, but luckily it was in an area I know well.  Finished with hours to spare.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Omiyage of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sweetheart_cake&quot;&gt;sweetheart cake&lt;/a&gt; (老婆餅) was very well received.  I had a spare which I stuck…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/d12df8f8-cc9d-4463-a51b-fc44dad1e16e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Sharp Sandspit — Week 12, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[If last week marked my first serious travel since the big move, this week marked my proper first holiday - and with it, more travel.  Thursday was a bank holiday and together with Friday made for an extended “long…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/b2f53898-7914-40dc-b0a9-40f75e49b09a?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/b2f53898-7914-40dc-b0a9-40f75e49b09a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 12:43:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If last week marked my first serious travel since the big move, this week marked my proper first holiday - and with it, more travel.  Thursday was a bank holiday and together with Friday made for an extended “long weekend”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maximum height: 332.6m&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kowloon Dairy products consumed: 7&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After work on Tuesday evening I went to the top of Landmark 81 - the tallest building in Vietnam, the 2nd tallest in SEA and the 17th tallest in the world. It is also, by at least 100 meters, the highest I have ever been.  Reaching the top, they strapped me to a pole and let me walk right up to the edge, where I took a few precarious photos and a selfie, right before scurrying right back down to ground level.  Gorgeous view though, well worth the nerves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wrestled with some NodeJS meta-programming which I really didn&apos;t enjoy. Sometimes I think we had it good with n-gage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And on Wednesday, REDACTED.  All I’m saying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Thursday I packed up, picked up some laundry, had some emergency banh mi, and swatted away the biggest cockroach you ever did see, before collapsing into an airplane seat.  Onboard I watched &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt8368368&quot;&gt;The Apprentice (2024)&lt;/a&gt;, which I really rate, it’s a very good movie.  Solid 3/5.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/b2f53898-7914-40dc-b0a9-40f75e49b09a?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>