<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 04:35:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Settling — Week 7, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This was a pretty good week.  I had a moment where I thought back to a question someone asked me, and I realised, that I couldn’t fault a single day this week.  Considering the number of big changes that have happened in…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/dbadbdda-2f45-4088-ab21-82f809d87b50?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/dbadbdda-2f45-4088-ab21-82f809d87b50</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 13:05:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a pretty good week.  I had a moment where I thought back to a question someone asked me, and I realised, that I couldn’t fault a single day this week.  Considering the number of big changes that have happened in the past 12 weeks alone, that&apos;s pretty huge.  This felt good in a calm way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🚶 Distance walked: 115,895 steps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🧉 Jasmine tea drunk: 3 litres&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To solve an incredibly annoying migration problem in a repeatable way, I wrote some code which parses the ES AST to extract its exports.  And, it, worked?  Normally I don’t do something so low-level and cursed until &lt;em&gt;at least&lt;/em&gt; summer?  So I’m pretty chuffed with that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Had two stand-out work lunches, only one of which was probably unhealthy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Got accepted for the apartment I applied for, which is &lt;em&gt;wonderful&lt;/em&gt; news, but the move-in date is a little ways off.  So during the week I signed another short-term lease, this one for a flat in Minami-Azabu.  It’s not the most convenient for going to other parts of Tokyo, but it’s an extremely nice area I’ve always enjoyed passing through, and being just on the cusp of walkable to work, I’ll probably never again have the opportunity to stay there.  I’m mega excited to explore a new neighbourhood.  Move-in next weekend.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/dbadbdda-2f45-4088-ab21-82f809d87b50?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Emdashing — Week 6, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Class update: Katakana are happening and they’re happening fast.  I’m staying (mostly) on top of vocab, at least. Learning katakana is making grocery shopping significantly easier, mind.  I finally found oatmeal, and in…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/b91a5f27-b922-428d-9cb2-58daa9d17911?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/b91a5f27-b922-428d-9cb2-58daa9d17911</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 13:18:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Class update: Katakana are happening and they’re happening fast.  I’m staying (mostly) on top of vocab, at least.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learning katakana &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; making grocery shopping significantly easier, mind.  I finally found oatmeal, and in case the picture wasn’t enough, I know enough letters to now know that it says “OATMEAL”.  So that’s neat.  Lessons are already paying for themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🍣 Sushi consumed: 21 pieces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🥣 Oatmeal consumed: 270g&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of my periodic LinkedIn doomscrolling (to reach &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/games&quot;&gt;their daily puzzle games&lt;/a&gt; I must open the feed) I read an incredibly bad take that using emdashes is a tell-tale sign of the use of artificial intelligence in writing, because obviously nobody uses emdashes.  I remember being taught to use them in school, but, unfortunately, I do not remember &lt;em&gt;how&lt;/em&gt;.  Nonetheless I continue to use them.  I hope the inaccuracies are proof enough that, at least for now, my posts are still hand-cranked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Part of joining a new job is learning how the goal-setting and evaluation systems work, and I’ve just about crossed that threshold this week by setting my half-yearly objectives.  I’m quite happy with the approach, and the output.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/b91a5f27-b922-428d-9cb2-58daa9d17911?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Soundproofing — Week 5, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Happy new lunar year! This week in data: 🍣 Time taken to eat Ehomaki: 682.33 seconds ☁️ Average humidity: 27% Had a few delightful catch-ups with people outside my team this week, so I’m feeling like I’m starting to…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/5f0ded1d-4f02-4ddd-8899-c37cd199346e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/5f0ded1d-4f02-4ddd-8899-c37cd199346e</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 14:19:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy new lunar year!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🍣 Time taken to eat Ehomaki: 682.33 seconds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;☁️ Average humidity: 27%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Had a few delightful catch-ups with people outside my team this week, so I’m feeling like I’m starting to settle in better — but there’s still a lot of things for me to learn, as well as some cultural differences to navigate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t normally do this sort of thing, but I’ve been using Endel (a soundscape app, e.g. for concentration, for activity, for sleep, etc.) - and I’m finding it incredibly good.  I&apos;ve used similar apps in the past - this generates music (not AI, dw), instead of playing back pre-recorded tracks, so it feels relatively fresh and non-repetitive.  My default soundscape has become &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FHRi_4rBcEM&quot;&gt;Richie Hawtin’s collaboration&lt;/a&gt; which I genuinely love.  This isn’t a referral-driven recommendation, but I do have &lt;a href=&quot;https://code.endel.io/?code=16hsnko&quot;&gt;a referral code/voucher which nets you a 14-day trial&lt;/a&gt; (regularly 7-days).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The weather is currently incredibly cold and also incredibly dry which is not doing good things to my skin.  To combat it, I went out and bought a humidifier and paired it with my IR hub - so now I have the ability to remotely heat and humidify my flat.  It seems to be helping?&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/5f0ded1d-4f02-4ddd-8899-c37cd199346e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Bangarang — Week 4, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week brought the fabled health-check, of Instagram/TikTok/YouTube creator fame.  I hate to shatter the illusion† but it turns out to be a series of tests and measures to assess overall health, much like in many…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/38a52047-9cac-45a3-886e-3e832421ee01?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/38a52047-9cac-45a3-886e-3e832421ee01</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 12:23:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week brought the fabled health-check, of Instagram/TikTok/YouTube creator fame.  I hate to shatter the illusion† but it turns out to be a series of tests and measures to assess overall health, much like in many other countries (other than, for some reason, the UK).  To all you fellow-watchers of American sitcoms, it’s  &quot;&quot;&quot;a physical&quot;&quot;&quot;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But the REAL headline of the week is: Monday I showed up bright and early at the Shibaura-konan ward office to finally collect my MyNumber card. The whole process was pretty fast: I had to review some documents, set some passwords and then I walked out with the future of paperwork.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Starting to think that Next.JS belongs in the same part of my resume as Magento, IYKWIM.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At work we had a new-starter lunch with leadership, which gave the opportunity to submit questions ahead of time.  Thinking they would be anonymised, filtered or moderated, I submitted far too many to count.  I came to regret this — because on the print-outs I saw that nearly all…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/38a52047-9cac-45a3-886e-3e832421ee01?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Clicking — Week 3, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Busy week evenings-wise, but I really needed the social battery recharge it gave me - it’ll really help me lock-in on this whole language-learning thing, as well as my yearly theme. Bank holiday Monday I stayed in doing…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/de892dbd-fbf7-4e3e-956c-11ddfd6df546?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/de892dbd-fbf7-4e3e-956c-11ddfd6df546</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 13:14:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Busy week evenings-wise, but I really needed the social battery recharge it gave me - it’ll really help me lock-in on this whole language-learning thing, as well as my yearly theme.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bank holiday Monday I stayed in doing a few chores including a lot of laundry (first load of the year if you can believe it).  Some of the NA team were visiting town so I traded some texts and we met up for a little catch-up and an Okonomiyaki dinner in a Hiroshima themed restaurant.  Reminisced about a few things.  I’d been meaning to do this in the UK for yonks.  Probably my favourite moment of the week - which for this week was a feat.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I bought a radio-controlled clock.  It also has a feature where it beeps and flashes bright red every few minutes when it thinks that I’m likely to catch a cold.  It took me 30 minutes to figure out the pattern, and to figure out how to turn it off.  No, that’s it, no other anecdotes here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuesday evening, TPC was in town with S so we tore up the izakayas (and their…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/de892dbd-fbf7-4e3e-956c-11ddfd6df546?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Hauling — Week 2, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cleanly breaking weeks with travel seems to work great for me: It creates a neat time-bounded window, or a context if you will. But long-distance travel — which can span days — are a lot fuzzier.  These journeys can form…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/ea01a831-6b81-424a-b97f-369da32eccf5?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/ea01a831-6b81-424a-b97f-369da32eccf5</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 12:36:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cleanly breaking weeks with travel seems to work great for me: It creates a neat time-bounded window, or a context if you will. But long-distance travel — which can span &lt;em&gt;days&lt;/em&gt; — are a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt; fuzzier.  These journeys can form their own chapters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leon wraps consumed: 0&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hours slept: Not enough. :(&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my case, a chapter involving some extremely pointy elbows  and my rib-cage on the the first long leg of my journey back: Being allocated a middle-seat is the opposite of winning the lottery.  And it involved some &lt;em&gt;extremely&lt;/em&gt; tasty soup (at the pop-up Tin Kee) in Hong-Kong airport which almost made up for everything else...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Long-haul flights get the travel out of the way, but, after you’ve done one or two (ever) they aren’t exactly exciting. You learn rules, tricks, optimisations to make the lost time  easier to manage.  You begin to trade these with your fellow travellers: This route has better food, this seat is easier to sleep in, this airline is much cheaper, this airport is to be avoided at all costs.  Long-haul travel becomes a part of the identity - and not one I enjoy embracing.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ea01a831-6b81-424a-b97f-369da32eccf5?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Shipping — Week 1, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Back in London this week to do, as I put in an email, the “grown-up parts of moving out”.  Also to celebrate the new year. Or at least, that was the plan.  You know what they say about the best laid plans?  Well lots of…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/acbeea07-f027-4ba8-a9cf-6b4b6f0f3b10?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/acbeea07-f027-4ba8-a9cf-6b4b6f0f3b10</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 10:58:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back in London this week to do, as I put in an email, the “grown-up parts of moving out”.  Also to celebrate the new year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or at least, that &lt;em&gt;was&lt;/em&gt; the plan.  You know what they say about the best laid plans?  Well lots of things did &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; go to plan this week, but we still executed on all the important bits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Firstly, and most importantly, I neglected to review the in-flight entertainment over from Hong Kong.  I watched &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt11057302/&quot;&gt;Madame Web (2024)&lt;/a&gt;.  It was everything I hoped it would be, everything they said it would be, and so much less.  Lots of things happened for no coherent reason.  Solid cast though.  2/5.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🗑️ Visits to a bin: 16 round-trips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;💉 Blood tests: 1 draw&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🍻 Spoons visits: 4 meals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Secondly, Happy New Year!  I hope you enjoyed all the AI-generated HNYs.  I know I did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No, that other jigsaw wasn’t me, I honestly don’t know who put it there.  Please keep me posted: I’m ever-so-curious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After getting into my old flat, I went to say hi to CR.  Before I left, covered in sweat and airplane grime, I changed shirts — donning my “let’s get relfed” shirt — a moment of foreshadowing I would come to regret.  A coffee turned into a chat turned into a crawl, and before I knew it, we had made it into deepest Bermondsey and to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.poulet.biz/&quot;&gt;Poulet&lt;/a&gt; with some friendly Americans talking about tax.  At some point I got home having fulfilled the shirt’s prophecy.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/acbeea07-f027-4ba8-a9cf-6b4b6f0f3b10?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Spiriting — Week 52, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Oh gosh OK there’s quite a lot to get through. One of my most received message all week was, “Did you do KFC for Christmas?”.  Let’s cut straight to the chase so you can close this tab and get back to doomscrolling: the…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/c363c1fb-8348-4502-8a65-3ed904f858e4?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/c363c1fb-8348-4502-8a65-3ed904f858e4</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 23:58:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh gosh OK there’s quite a lot to get through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my most received message all week was, “Did you do KFC for Christmas?”.  Let’s cut straight to the chase so you can close this tab and get back to doomscrolling: the answer is &lt;strong&gt;no&lt;/strong&gt;.  I considered getting the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.timeout.com/tokyo/things-to-do/whats-the-deal-with-kfc-and-christmas-in-japan&quot;&gt;“Party Barrel”&lt;/a&gt; but — for the price it seemed like &lt;em&gt;horrible&lt;/em&gt; value (as well as a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt; of food) so I let it sell out.  Instead I picked up some Family Mart &amp;amp; Lawson fried chicken on the day, since they were still discounted but could come in &lt;em&gt;much&lt;/em&gt; smaller servings and I had that instead.  It was OK, and the roast chicken was borderline good (and not on KFC’s menu) but the fried chicken is - just that - fried chicken.  Picture in the little collage at the bottom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🎵 Number of times WHAM!&apos;d: 13 Last Christmasses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🎄 Christmas trees observed: 12 trees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🎅 Occurrences of the word &quot;Christmas&quot; in this article: 10&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For lack of any carols I pulled up the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/m00268s1&quot;&gt;Salvation Army’s yearly shindig on the BBC Sounds app&lt;/a&gt;.  I tried to listen to King’s College Chapel service about some number of carols and lessons — but it’s locked-up, gated and paywalled in so many ways outside of the UK that calling it a &lt;em&gt;religious&lt;/em&gt; ceremony seems &lt;em&gt;slightly&lt;/em&gt; inaccurate?  First year without hearing “Once in Royal David&apos;s City”. :^(&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/c363c1fb-8348-4502-8a65-3ed904f858e4?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Triangulating — Week 51, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Spent a bit of this week debugging an infrastructure problem in an unfamiliar stack, and I’m really enjoying this period of discovery. Finding the problem was super affirming. Did a little intro in the engineering all…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/06fd4e46-dd48-4650-90aa-ec4ecde32479?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/06fd4e46-dd48-4650-90aa-ec4ecde32479</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 13:48:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spent a bit of this week debugging an infrastructure problem in an unfamiliar stack, and I’m really enjoying this period of discovery. Finding the problem was super affirming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did a little intro in the engineering all-hands. It’s hard to distill yourself into a slide but I think I got away with it.  (it had pictures and I got distracted mid-sentence by the chat trying to identify one!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Closed the week with the really big yearly all-hands. My head is still spinning!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Met up with JK &amp;amp; FT for dinner in a wine bar in Shimbashi to reminisce, and learned more about how all these visas work in the process. Also walked away slightly more optimistic about learning the language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The 21st was the winter solstice, and marking the occasion I went to the incredibly packed Hōjōji in Waseda to pick up a &lt;a href=&quot;https://katnsatoshiinjapan.blogspot.com/2020/12/ichiyo-raifuku.html&quot;&gt;Ichiyo Raifuku&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It needs attaching to the wall, facing the right direction at exactly midnight.  Unfortunately I didn’t have a surface facing the right direction, so instead it is now sitting on a…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/06fd4e46-dd48-4650-90aa-ec4ecde32479?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Verifying — Week 50, 2024]]></title><description><![CDATA[Over the course of this week I made a few small break-throughs culminating in the realisation that: If after one week I suspected that cleaning, sorting and separating garbage was about to become a big part of my life…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/b61e1e29-750d-4cb2-87e3-37411b6c716b?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/b61e1e29-750d-4cb2-87e3-37411b6c716b</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 13:01:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the course of this week I made a few small break-throughs culminating in the realisation that: If after &lt;em&gt;one&lt;/em&gt; week I suspected that cleaning, sorting and separating garbage was about to become a big part of my life - Now after &lt;em&gt;three&lt;/em&gt; I know the remainder will become all about points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week in data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🤑 PayPay points earned: 1215pts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🍋 Vitamin C consumed: 3690mg&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🏬 Second-hand stores searched: 7&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before I left  I asked around a bit, “If I’m bringing a &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Omiyage&quot;&gt;souvenir/gift from our culture&lt;/a&gt; what should it be?”  The answers were many, but a consensus formed split somewhere between M&amp;amp;S Shortbread (you know, the blue tin? yes &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; blue tin. You know.) and tea.  Shortbread seemed more practical.  Anyway I brought it in this week and it went down a treat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally booked into some language lessons, starting in January...  I&apos;m excited!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One big change this week is that after a lot (and I mean a lot) of wrangling, my Apple account is now a Japanese one.  Meaning that at the cost of losing access to a few apps, I now have access to some incredibly useful ones: Such as PayPay.&lt;/p&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/b61e1e29-750d-4cb2-87e3-37411b6c716b?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>