<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Alex Wilson's writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alex on engineering, products & everything in-between]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/</link><generator>alexwilson.tech</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 06:07:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><ttl>360</ttl><atom:link rel="self" href="https://alexwilson.tech/feed.xml" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Primordial — Week 42, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[What a week, huh? Monday was a bank holiday.  I wanted to find spicy soup and I’m pleased to say that I found some. Still recovering.  Each day I felt more myself, and each day returned some clarity which I hadn’t…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/e3232bc6-6ac7-401e-a325-ce2cd630a44d?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/e3232bc6-6ac7-401e-a325-ce2cd630a44d</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 14:17:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What a week, huh?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monday was a bank holiday.  I wanted to find spicy soup and I’m pleased to say that I found some.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Still recovering.  Each day I felt more myself, and each day returned some clarity which I hadn’t noticed I lost.  Unfortunately not in time for me to have potentially bungled something.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At work I held a kick-off meeting which went OK, although my facilitation skills feel very rusty.  Gotta re-sharpen them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Built an “AI Agent”. Can honestly say I’ve worked on nothing quite like this before - and the results are good - although integrating it into workflows is proving challenging: Sometimes I miss Bertha.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had my second annual health check this week. It ran smoothly albeit long even if the phlebotomy left me feeling woozy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday the Yotsuya lxds drank orange wine and practiced zen buddhism.  I spelt my name right this time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/p/DPc7v_wiZje/&quot;&gt;“Ephemeral” at Such As&lt;/a&gt; which was a hybrid data-visualisation &amp;amp; art installation.  It charted bloom dates in Japan, and shows how changing…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/e3232bc6-6ac7-401e-a325-ce2cd630a44d?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Shin-can’t-sen or shin-won’t? — Week 41, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi, it’s me, I’ve been properly in the weeds of Google Docs and YAML.  Alas I will continue to primarily exist in these for a little while longer. I really liked this post on using AI to generate image captions by Matt…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/56a25482-5d02-4c96-b848-cc943bd431ed?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/56a25482-5d02-4c96-b848-cc943bd431ed</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 14:55:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hi, it’s me, I’ve been properly in the weeds of Google Docs and YAML.  Alas I will continue to primarily exist in these for a little while longer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I really liked this post on &lt;a href=&quot;https://tk.gg/posts/ai-alt-text&quot;&gt;using AI to generate image captions&lt;/a&gt; by Matt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Now that I’ve got the equipment I cooked at home a lot this week, which meant braving buying ingredients I didn’t 100% understand and re-learning how to cook without the luxury of counter-top space.  Never before have I missed owning a dishwasher as much as I do now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Didn’t do much last week, which is why there’s no week 40.  What began as feeling run-down blossomed into full blown sickness.  By the time I saw my doctor I tested negative for everything, but whatever this was took a serious toll on my energy levels, mood and focus and I’m still recovering bit-by-bit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;That meant staying in and playing &lt;a href=&quot;https://thegamesdb.net/game.php?id=85013&quot;&gt;The Great Ace Attorney&lt;/a&gt; which is cheesy as all hell and goes hard on stereotyping England.  Doubling-down, I watched some &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/name/nm0005363/&quot;&gt;Guy Ritchie&lt;/a&gt; movies: It &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; wasn’t a good week…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/56a25482-5d02-4c96-b848-cc943bd431ed?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Hundo — Week 39, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Three-day work week this week.  I begin in Osaka, following my defeat (or victory?) at the Queueing Olympics. Originally my plan is to be back in Tokyo quite early, but I cancel my plans on Tuesday to instead spend the…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/dd7d2079-c30f-46b9-b73c-08f0ee621658?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/dd7d2079-c30f-46b9-b73c-08f0ee621658</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 14:39:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Three-day work week this week.  I begin in Osaka, following my defeat (or victory?) at the Queueing Olympics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Originally my plan is to be back in Tokyo quite early, but I cancel my plans on Tuesday to instead spend the day pottering about Osaka and looking at and eating things.  The city has a very different atmosphere which I love.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This also includes possibly the most unhealthy Tonkatsu lunch I will ever eat.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I spend some time over the week iterating on a design-document and corresponding schema, which involves going back to the drawing board a few times.  The combination of short week and many iterations means I make less net progress than I’d hoped to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New 5K PB is a nice small win.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the context of journalism, I learn a fair bit about financial reporting obligations in Japan, which for a place with so much paperwork turn out to be surprisingly difficult.  Or maybe I’m too used to Company House?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m introduced to a new spot which I’m afraid I have to gatekeep because I will be…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/dd7d2079-c30f-46b9-b73c-08f0ee621658?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Exposition — Week 38, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[The two big themes of this week are: Kafka and the 2025 World Expo.  Both have been prompted much thought. Kafka is a technology I’ve used indirectly a lot over the years. A deep dive this week helped me understand it…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/904396c1-32e8-4cd6-a491-1afa98b74b34?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/904396c1-32e8-4cd6-a491-1afa98b74b34</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 14:20:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The two big themes of this week are: Kafka and the 2025 World Expo.  Both have been prompted much thought.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kafka is a technology I’ve used indirectly a lot over the years. A deep dive this week helped me understand it better, and so I’ve been reimagining how some big systems might work if built on Kafka with Event Sourcing, which has been very exciting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A big dinner during the week turns out to be a big miss, which is a good thing because it reminds me just how good the service and food is in most places.  Important not to take anything for granted!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday night karaoke is pretty good.  We start at dinner and end up in a booth where I discover Pendulum is on the docket and that it &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; possible to do Karaoke to Drum ‘n Bass.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My subsequent adventure to find hard techno starts on a high note: I meet interesting people and have eclectic conversations.  But one interaction brings me vividly back to a night in Germany, which raises the question: Is this still fun?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Over the week I also go on…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/904396c1-32e8-4cd6-a491-1afa98b74b34?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Banking — Week 37, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[This was a good week?  22.53km of running. Part of this week went into a messy incident and data-recovery operation.  I’m actively thinking about architectural interventions to prevent scenarios exactly like this one, so…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/8a12f155-bdf5-4b5e-9d92-7ee4ad0f0513?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/8a12f155-bdf5-4b5e-9d92-7ee4ad0f0513</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 14:13:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This was a good week?  22.53km of running.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Part of this week went into a messy incident and data-recovery operation.  I’m actively thinking about architectural interventions to prevent scenarios exactly like this one, so this was very timely.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With my plate clearer, I had an uninterrupted day to work on strategy, and made good progress.  The hardest part is always starting, so I’ve begun with Will Larson’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://lethain.com/good-engineering-strategy-is-boring/&quot;&gt;“Write five, then synthesize”&lt;/a&gt; approach which is &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; JFDI-minded.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One afternoon, instead of lunch, on the way to the office I make a pit-stop in Toranomon Hills for a long-anticipated coffee where I learn a lot about fin-tech, a lot about founding a company in Japan and also get a great pep-talk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amongst serious songs, at karaoke I do &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZZ5LpwO-An4&quot;&gt;the He-Man duet of “What&apos;s Up?”&lt;/a&gt; with DS.  Later I pray that the only recording of this moment is the one now forever etched into my brain.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After two false starts - which involve walking to okubo and helping set up a bunch of accounts - Friday night we…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/8a12f155-bdf5-4b5e-9d92-7ee4ad0f0513?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Painting — Week 36, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[September is here, meaning I’ve now been here 9 months.  September also means summer is ending, but nobody has told the cicadas yet, or thought to turn down the temperature-dial outside. Self-introductions this week in…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/cb4e8d65-7cfd-440e-acc5-04801be33427?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/cb4e8d65-7cfd-440e-acc5-04801be33427</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 11:57:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;September is here, meaning I’ve now been here 9 months.  September also means summer is ending, but nobody has told the cicadas yet, or thought to turn down the temperature-dial outside.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-introductions this week in my new class.  Did you know that the word for clown is ピエロ or pierō?  Derived from a French cartoon and since enshrined in katakana.  Useful word to know for my future self-introductions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Levelled up my home coffee game: This week I made my first &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hometown_tax&quot;&gt;furusato nōzei&lt;/a&gt; contribution (to Aichi, obviously, since it’s the closest thing to West Midlands), and received a mahoosive bag of coffee for my troubles.  Procured an Aeropress to make it with, and I’m pretty chuffed with the results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m running again: It’s going OK, and I’ve nearly caught up on all the progress I lost this past month.  I’ve worked out why I keep injuring myself — my right heel strike is off — and so now am looking for a coach &amp;amp; physio to correct it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finished a big migration: It happened piece-by-piece and…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/cb4e8d65-7cfd-440e-acc5-04801be33427?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Hazing — Week 35, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Memorable week. Managed a 3 day Tantanmen streak: One in Shibaura, one in Ebisu and one in Tamachi.  All were different but all were good. Reconnected with a few key people this week.  One night in Ebisu over tacos and…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/e1abdf65-9ebc-42a6-8c71-f485307e844e?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/e1abdf65-9ebc-42a6-8c71-f485307e844e</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 14:37:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Memorable week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managed a 3 day Tantanmen streak: One in Shibaura, one in Ebisu and one in Tamachi.  All were different but all were good.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reconnected with a few key people this week.  One night in Ebisu over tacos and pineapple highballs, and the other near Tokyo station.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tokyo station was me breaking my “no-meetups” rule, because I was invited.  It was great!  Had a few nice conversations, remembered why the “Always try to ask a question” rule carries important nuance and later received some overdue and worthy validation on how I approached a technical project many years ago.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experimentally I have trialling a new type of aggressive prioritisation (where 80% of other work is either deferred or delegated) instead of time-blocking, and I’m finding it both enjoyable and useful.  It’s something like a more extreme version of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Time_management#Eisenhower_method&quot;&gt;Eisenhower matrix&lt;/a&gt;, inspired by some highly effective former colleagues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But as an exception to these priorities, I’m preparing a new &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/ft-product-technology/thinking-through-our-changes-with-design-documents-35c93bf0938b&quot;&gt;Tech-Design-Document template&lt;/a&gt; and have been pleasantly surprised at the diversity of feedback I’ve received, and how much this has taught me about different ways-of-working and engineering philosophies.  Ranging from the naming &lt;em&gt;(TDD is a bit like test-driven-development, ne?)&lt;/em&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/e1abdf65-9ebc-42a6-8c71-f485307e844e?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Carding — Week 34, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lately I’ve been distracted.  In previous chapters of life I prioritised work above all else and I tied it to my sense of self-worth.  There’s lots to say on that subject, but, not today.  Lessons in-hand, in this…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/ad4581f8-b83b-422d-bf5b-c44b1eb8d78f?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/ad4581f8-b83b-422d-bf5b-c44b1eb8d78f</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 14:31:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lately I’ve been distracted.  In previous chapters of life I prioritised work above all else and I tied it to my sense of self-worth.  There’s lots to say on that subject, but, not today.  Lessons in-hand, in this chapter I’m now prioritising life too, and am re-learning some things including my self-worth, which is bringing new ups-and-downs.  But I’m enjoying them, a lot.  So, yes, I’ve been distracted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My highlight of the week was a team dinner with one of my teams, which we realised was the first time we’d all assembled in person.  We discovered many things including a shared love of Mexican food - which led to a recommendation of &lt;a href=&quot;https://tabelog.com/tokyo/A1303/A130302/13309222/&quot;&gt;3 Hermanos&lt;/a&gt; - and to my discovery of a new lunch spot near the office.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Getting a chance to learn about more advanced framework features in &lt;a href=&quot;https://rubyonrails.org&quot;&gt;Rails&lt;/a&gt; has been fun.  After I clocked out for the week, I connected some dots and realised a mistake in my work which I now get to fix.  It’s been a while since I had a moment like this with a novel tech-stack, so this…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/ad4581f8-b83b-422d-bf5b-c44b1eb8d78f?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Suffocating — Week 33, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[A while ago I said that my tag-cloud would’ve highlighted “Lunch“, this week it would’ve highlighted “Coffee”.  Several memorable coffee catch-ups (without incident, this time).  My current side-quest involves one of the…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/a767410e-0706-4a55-bb67-091b6a31f7fb?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/a767410e-0706-4a55-bb67-091b6a31f7fb</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 14:55:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A while ago I said that my tag-cloud would’ve highlighted “Lunch“, this week it would’ve highlighted “Coffee”.  Several memorable coffee catch-ups (without incident, this time).  My current side-quest involves one of the less walked (and, documented?) roads of being a senior IC: networking.  More about this another time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nothing too exciting to report.  Got involved in some discussions, and tried to create focus-time to ship something.  Made some progress.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tragedy struck at Sonicmania after the epiphany that I was dancing to Drum ’n Bass but I hadn’t brought my brand new &lt;a href=&quot;https://kneecap.backstreetmerch.com/products/logo-bucket-hat&quot;&gt;Kneecap bucket hat&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But, it was was &lt;strong&gt;brilliant&lt;/strong&gt;.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.summersonic.com/sonicmania/&quot;&gt;Sonicmania&lt;/a&gt; is the all-nighter pre-party for &lt;a href=&quot;https://summersonic.com/&quot;&gt;Summer Sonic&lt;/a&gt;.  It was mostly electronic acts, and it let me finally tick &lt;a href=&quot;https://theprodigy.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;The Prodigy off my bucket list (somehow I missed them completely when I lived in London).  I &lt;em&gt;loved&lt;/em&gt; their set.  Many memorable moments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I saw... &lt;em&gt;sharp inhale of breath&lt;/em&gt; ... &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Perfume_(Japanese_band)&quot;&gt;PERFUME&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2hollis&quot;&gt;2HOLLIS&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kyary_Pamyu_Pamyu&quot;&gt;Kyary Pamyu Pamyu&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/floatingpoints&quot;&gt;Floating Points&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/prodigythe&quot;&gt;The Prodigy&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/gesaffelstein&quot;&gt;Gesaffelstein&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/shioriybradshaw&quot;&gt;Shiory Bradshaw&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ra.co/dj/minna-no-kimochi&quot;&gt;Minna-no-Kimochi&lt;/a&gt;.  All were great performances with high production value, and great energy in the room.  I had major FOMO for the acts I &lt;em&gt;couldn’t&lt;/em&gt; see.  [&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/stories/highlights/18073701635098980/&quot;&gt;highlight reel&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/a767410e-0706-4a55-bb67-091b6a31f7fb?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weeknotes: Blues — Week 32, 2025]]></title><description><![CDATA[I really enjoyed this week, but, I didn’t have a good week.  Looking back, in many ways it reminds me of that week when we went to the Wolf. This week I shipped some code, wrote some documents and chatted with some other…]]></description><link>https://alexwilson.tech/content/41ef9228-75ba-4a91-8a20-78149d2e5f74?utm_source=feed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alexwilson.tech/content/41ef9228-75ba-4a91-8a20-78149d2e5f74</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[alex]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 12:37:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>
                  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I really enjoyed this week, but, I didn’t have a good week.  Looking back, in many ways it reminds me of that week when we went to the Wolf.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This week I shipped some code, wrote some documents and chatted with some other teams about their problems.  Spoke a bit with some colleagues about a monkey’s paw I’ve been offered and came to a conclusion.  (This is the post I put on &quot;&quot;&quot;The Gram&quot;&quot;&quot; the other week)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had an unfortunate incident involving a Starbucks Venti latte.   The less said, the better, but it happened in an &lt;em&gt;incredibly&lt;/em&gt; public place and now I keep chatting to people who “heard about [it]”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attempted to check out fireworks this weekend, and here’s how that went: Saturday - cancelled due to heavy rain.  Sunday - cancelled due to a fire.  Sign from the universe?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seems like everyone is sick this week.  Hope it’s nothing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.asagaya.or.jp/tanabata/tanabata.html&quot;&gt;Asagaya Tanabata festival&lt;/a&gt; at the weekend which was hella crowded but was lined with good food.  That’s where the paper-mache statues were.  [&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.asagaya.or.jp/tanabata/100selection.html&quot;&gt;It goes back ages&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                  &lt;a href=&quot;https://alexwilson.tech/content/41ef9228-75ba-4a91-8a20-78149d2e5f74?utm_source=feed&quot;&gt;Read the full post here...&lt;/a&gt;
                </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>